- Thanks for a great year.
- You got it.
Mr. Winger!
I hope you will be seizing
the day this summer.
Thanks, Professor Whitman.
And I hope you'll be seizing
a more contemporary movie.
Looking good, Leonard.
Stroke or tai chi?
Tai chi.
Keep it up.
And keep up whatever
it is you're doing, Garrett.
It's called "chillaxing".
Duh!
Hey... hey, what's up, Jeff? Hi.
Hello, good morning, howdy.
Wait, Jeff. I'll walk with you.
Uh...
I got class in, like, five hours, so...
All right, I'll see you, babe.
Sayonara.
I can't believe I made it
through my first year of college.
I finally get to click send
on so many "I told you so" emails.
Yeah, it's pretty great.
Not much could ruin today.
Hi!
Oh, shoot. I forgot saying
that summons him.
Will you two be attending
tomorrow's, uh, transfer
ceremony to send off
all the students leaving
for so-called real schools?
There's a formal dance afterward.
How many dances is
this school gonna have?
Five.
If you come to all of them,
you get one of these.
I assumed your whole posse
would be coming to the dance,
having heard the exciting
news about Britta.
Banana rhino.
Banana Sam Elliott.
LeVar "Banana" Burton.
Banana King Tut.
Here, give me that.
It's more like this.
B... banana penis.
Sure, you would've
loved it if he did it.
What?
What's happened to you and me, Troy?
Remember how hard we laughed
When we first heard the
term "teacher's aids"?
Yeah.
And then we found out
a teacher did have aids.
So what's everybody doing this summer?
I'm taking the boys on a trip.
Money's tight, so I hope
I can convince them
for one more year that motels
are tiny, little theme parks.
Yeah, I got to find
a new place to live.
My dad wants me to leave the nest,
so he feels less weird
that his girlfriend is 20.
You could live in a pyramid.
Oh, wait.
Abed, your dorm room's
got a bunk bed, right?
Yep.
Um, everyone has to go to
the transfer dance tomorrow.
I'm going.
My friend Gary's transferring.
Oh, good.
- Finally.
- Thank God.
Hope he transfers to hell.
More importantly,
our very own Britta Perry,
it turns out,
has been nominated for transfer queen.
Oh, that's nice!
What the hell is a transfer queen?
It's like prom queen.
You wear a sash.
And there's a vote, and if you win,
they put a crown on your head,
and I am so jealous, Britta,
I want to murder you.
Aren't you excited?
No.
How did I get nominated?
Don't let it upset you, Britta.
It's the last day of the semester.
Nothing can ruin that.
Hi!
Amazing. He's like an evil genie.
Just spreading the news.
Some folks say "transfer formal"
isn't really rolling off the tongue,
so we're just gonna call
it "The tranny dance"!
Much more Greendale.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Corrected by 4be1
What kind of community
college has a prom?
Proms weren't even cool in high school.
It's that kind of crap that made
me drop out in the first place.
You know, you don't actually have
to lie on a sofa like
it's a Woody Allen movie.
Thank you for telling me that
in the last session, dumbass.
Now, look...
There are bugs on the
windshield of your mind
you may never be able to squeegee,
like a certain birthday party
attended by a rather
enterprising transient
in a dinosaur costume.
But there are other more recent streaks
that you might yet
be able to wipe clear,
like your adolescent fear
of being a so-called blow-up doll.
I really think this nomination
may actually help that.
So you think I'd feel
better about myself
if I got all sexed up, went over there,
and really tried to be crowned
queen of the dingbats?
- Precisely.
- Wow.
Guess you really get what
you pay for with free therapy.
Ouch. That stung a little bit.
Thanks.
- Oh.
I'll save you some time.
He listens to you talk for a year,
then recommends a makeover.
Well, don't wear as much lipstick
as you did on Valentine's Day.
Your mouth looked like a coin purse.
Senor Chang...
Greendale's foremost,
if only, Spanish teacher.
What can I do for you?
I am actually a student now.
- Oh.
- But I was thinking,
as a teacher and as my friend,
um, if you could help me...
Cheat my way through school.
I have a counterproposal.
How about...
I point out to you that we've
never actually been friends,
then laugh at your very
well-deserved misfortune?
Let's just try that a second.
No, Jorge, you killed it.
Are you going to Abed's kegger?
Sweet.
You probably don't want to talk to me.
Well, it's not junior high.
We're mature adults, Michelle.
We can talk.
I think I handled our breakup poorly.
Before I respond to that,
I'll have to take a
extra-strength vitamin duh.
Duh.
We started getting serious,
and I got scared,
and it's possible I made a mistake.
Maybe we can talk about it sometime.
I miss you.
Mm-mmm.
Why don't you take a picture?
It'll last longer.
Cool.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
- Dope kegger.
- Thanks.
Funny...
You know, I... I spend
so much time here,
I forget that we don't live together.
Then I think...
"What if we lived together?"
Here, I'm gonna check on the other keg.
Hey, Troy, you ever seen one of these?
It's called a beer bong.
You're not supposed to inhale, though.
I almost died outside.
Why does abed hate me?
What, are you kidding?
Look at him.
He probably hates America.
Hey, babe, babe.
Guess what.
Your boyfriend just got offered a spot
on the number-one
community-college
hacky sack team in the nation.
- Oh, my God! Sweetie!
- Oh, my God.
I'm assuming that's huge.
Of course it's huge.
Are you kidding me?
I mean, you know,
I'm not into the fame and stuff,
but I could be the next
Yngwe Mackadangdang junior.
I know.
There's just one thing,
mountain flower,
and that's that the, uh...
the school's in Delaware.
Thank you.
You know...
If you don't go to this dance tomorrow,
we are not gonna see
each other for months.
It's not a Jane Austen novel.
We have cell phones.
- What? Aah! Oh.
- Oh, jeez, sorry.
What are you doing?
Well, you had hair I was gonna move.
- You were gonna move my hair?
- I don't know.
Have you ever thought of yourself
as a guarded person, Britta?
Am I?
Watch.
See? It's alarming, right?
Right?
Oh...
Professor Slater, hi.
What are you doing here?
Oh, you know, end of the year,
randomly wandering.
Hi, Jeff.
Are you two...?
- No.
The two of you aren't...?
- No, just friends.
- Same here.
Good... for you.
Will I see you at the dance, Britta?
Kind of obligated,
seeing as I'm nominated for queen,
- so...
- Oh.
I thought you were all
into female empowerment.
What's more empowering
than a woman in a crown?
Just did my first keg stand!
Ha ha!
Can't feel my legs.
Mm!
* Dancing in your underwear,
taking air conditioner repair *
* So you can get a job *
* Greendale's the way it goes *
Whoo! Ha ha!
Our original school song by
the venerable Pierce Hawthorne.
He made that up. Hmm?
Everyone remember to vote
before the coronation.
The nominees are identified with sashes
that say "Tranny Queen".
By the way, we do offer summer classes,
which are a great way to, um...
Um, broaden your mind.
Have fun.
Hi. You're here for me.
Guys! Guys...
Vaughn got recruited to
a college in Delaware.
I'm gonna go with him for the summer.
Finally, a classic
last-day-of-school plot twist.
He's gonna be the next
Yngwe Mackadangdang junior.
It's a hacky sack guy.
Hey, you don't have to tell us who
Ingmar Mackadingdong junior is.
Jeff, help me with some refreshments.
Please don't tell anyone
until after I'm gone.
I'm not just going to
Delaware for the summer.
I'm transferring with Vaughn.
What? When did you decide that?
I spent three months
researching backpacks
before I chose the one that I use now.
I don't want to be that person anymore.
I want to live in the moment.
Well, for your and Vaughn's sake,
I hope it works out.
But on behalf of the rest of the group,
I hope it's a catastrophe.
- You better visit.
- Whoa!
I can't believe nobody's
taken this cookie.
Senor Chang...
Is there a word in Spanish
for someone who used to
pretend to be a professor,
but was a teacher,
but wasn't actually a teacher,
and he's now a student?
Is there a word for that?
Oh, if it was in Spanish,
you wouldn't know, would you?
Ah, bup, bup, bup.
Hit a professor, you'll get expelled.
I will find a loophole.
Oh, good luck with that.
Then I'll kill you.
- Good.
- Dudley Moore.
Spray tan.
I'd go easy on that punch if I was you.
I've put in a little... hot person.
Hot people.
There are two of them coming this way.
Which one do you want?
- Hi, Jeff.
- Oh.
Britta, you look great.
Such a stunning improvement.
Thank you.
God, you look gorgeous.
It must've taken all day.
Oh.
Oh, Jeff, you've got a...
Oh. It's right there.
- I do? What?
- Actually...
Guys, guys...
Cleanest face ever.
Hey, am I okay?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
You know, Troy, uh,
our study group...
After all we've been through,
we got to stick together.
You, me, and Jeff and rain man
and big boobs and medium
boobs and black boobs...
We're a family.
What's your point?
I've been looking at your situation,
and I'd like to make an offer.
Okay.
Am I black boobs?
Last call.
Study over.
What are you doing?
Just giving things a finale vibe.
Well, how's this for a finale vibe?
Pierce asked me to move in with him...
in his mansion.
More of a spin -off vibe,
but you should do it.
- I thought we were friends.
- We are.
Best friends... That's why
we shouldn't be roommates.
We'll end up fighting and
putting a masking-tape line
down the middle of our room.
We just won't get masking tape.
Troy, you should live
with someone who you like,
but whose friendship
wouldn't be altered
because of constant
irritation... that's Pierce.
If you and I move in,
we jump the shark.
That'll end it.
Well, maybe you're ending it.
Oh, and for the record,
there was an episode of Happy Days
where a guy literally
jumped over a shark,
and it was the best one.
I think I'm winning.
- Winning... Tranny Queen.
- Yeah.
So, uh, isn't it nice
that Jeff and Slater are
getting back together?
- What?
- Aha! And psych!
But they will get back together
if you don't stop competing with her
and start communicating with Jeff.
She already has a head start.
They slept together.
Holy macaroni with pepper Jack.
When? Where?
During paintball
in the study room with colonel mustard.
Does it matter?
Well, now it does matter.
Where... where in the study room?
On the couches.
- We use those!
- Oh, get over it.
I've seen you shake the Dean's hand.
Who knows where he's been?
Do you believe in soul mates?
Oh.
Um, okay, now, don't be mad at me.
I didn't think that more than
one person would answer the ad.
Yes, dream coming true.
You guys are leaving already?
Yeah, got to be in Delaware
by tomorrow night.
First practice is Monday morning.
See you soon.
Have a good summer.
I'll see you in the fall, Annie.
We're gonna miss you.
Yeah, you're the one
that didn't even want me
in the study group.
Come on, that's not true.
Yeah, none of us did.
I say things others won't.
That has value.
Well...
Bye.
See ya.
Lates.
Good evening, Michelle.
Or may I say, "meow-chelle"?
- Who has your car keys?
- They're in the taco meat.
Now, what say you and
I blow this pop stand
and head off for a
spot of slap n' tickle?
I mean sex,
in case the lingo hasn't
made it to the States.
I think I'm probably
leaving here with Jeff.
Really? I'm sorry, I just...
just assumed that you two were done,
since, uh...
Jeff and Britta did, uh,
the Yankee Doodle.
Oh, don't tell me that
didn't make it to the States.
It clearly originated here.
Okay, we finished
tallying all 36 votes,
so everyone get ready!
Yo, Goldilocks.
Drop the smirk.
I know about your grungy tumble,
and I'm sure it was the
highlight of your diary,
but it was during a pit
stop in something real.
You were the pit stop.
He used you to numb the
pain of not getting with me.
Jeff needs a girl who doesn't
just not wear underwear
because oprah told her
it would spice things up.
He needs a girl who
doesn't wear underwear
because she hasn't done
laundry in three weeks.
He's been to flavor country now.
They should retire
the table we did it on.
Table?
Miss britta perry!
Oh, I'm sorry. I have to go.
I just won a contest for being hot.
Oh, wow.
This is a huge honor.
This may come as a surprise to you,
but I've never actually
won anything before.
Okay, well, you still haven't.
I'm just listing the nominees,
so not a great time to get cocky.
Okay. Christine Hollinsworth!
Britney Baker!
Mary Jones!
Amy Sm...
Jeff Einger, do not
get back with Slater.
I love you.
Psst, psst, Britta.
Britta!
Your lipstick looks better.
Hey, man.
How's it going?
Uh, don't shoot the messenger,
but everyone at this dance
is kind of waiting for
your reaction to all this.
Look, I'm trying to think, okay?
Yeah, that's cool.
Take your time.
Hey, how's it going?
You look great.
Very fatal attraction.
Ah.
- What's wrong with you?
- I'm sick.
I don't know why.
Have you considered
the 60-inch-diameter
cookie you're eating?
How can something that's delicious
make me sick?
Unless too much of a good thing...
is actually a bad thing.
My friendship with Abed
is a giant cookie.
Look, I kind of got my own
thing going on right now.
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
First of all...
I'm flattered.
Second...
Have you ever heard of...
email?
You love me?
Do you love me?
I have something to say.
Jeff...
I love you.
I wonder where she got that from.
I'm sorry. Do you have a
patent on loving people?
Would you like a patent
in getting your ass kicked?
Okay, okay.
Can you stand over there?
And can you sit down...
please?
Jeffrey...
Choose Britta.
- Yeah, Team Britta.
- Yeah, that's right.
Britta's lame.
Team Slater.
- Team Slater.
- Choose Britta.
Bring Conan back!
Shh.
Ye... It's been a... a great year.
Can't hear you.
No one can hear you.
Uh, hi, it's, um...
Oh, come on, who are you choosing?
I... I don't know.
Oh.
Everybody sh...
Everybody close their faces.
All right, he's got a lot on his mind.
Leave him alone.
Oka... I got it from here.
My name is Professor Ian Duncan,
and I would like to rap for you.
Drop a beat.
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
* My name is Ian Duncan,
and I'm here to say*
* I'm going to rap to the beat
in a rapping way *
* I've got a real big penis,
and I drink lots of tea *
Oh, okay. Okay, okay.
No, no, no, you know what, Duncan?
- What?
- That's enough.
- Why?
- You have a problem.
- Oh, I have a problem?
- Yes.
Who is it here who
has a dalmatian fetish?
Oh, ok... okay.
Well, that is a oversimplification,
and you are suspended.
Oh, come on.
Oh, not a teacher anymore.
What's this?
A roll of quarters. Why?
Funny question. Oh, man!
- Friends, help me, friends!
- Help me!
He's on me! He's on me!
I'll do it. I'll move in with you.
Fantastic, buddy!
Why don't you come over on Saturday?
My tailor will fit you for a uniform.
Guys, let's break it up.
Come on, let's not fight.
Let's not fight.
No, no!
I thought you left.
I couldn't go.
What happened?
I guess as we were driving away,
I finally started living in the moment,
and I realized that, in the moment,
greendale is where I belong.
What are you doing out here?
Oh, you know...
Britta and Slater told me
they loved me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- What did you do?
- I ran away.
I don't know. It's hard.
Slater makes me feel like I do
when I write my new year's resolutions.
She makes me feel like
the guy I want to be.
And britta makes me
feel like the guy I am
three weeks after new year's,
when I'm back to
hitting my snooze button
and screening my
mom's phone calls...
back to who I really am.
So...
Do you try to evolve...
or do you try to know what you are?
I don't know.
I wish I could live two lives.
One of me would go with Vaughn,
and one of me could stay here.
Yeah, one of me could
be back with Slater,
and the other could try it with Britta.
And then we could all get together
for some weird foursome.
Um, I guess I got to...
got to deal with it.
Good luck.
Um...
I'm glad you're staying.
sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Oh, my God.
I'm finally popular enough
to be in the yearbook.
What do you mean "video yearbook"?
Where do I sign?
Photo not available.
This better not be one of those
take-your-top-off videos.
I don't believe in yearbooks.
I just want people to remember
there's a guy in between these things.
What a year.
Only two pregnancy scares.
I give this year a "D"
for "delightful".
I can't believe
I spent ten bucks on this.
I don't know any of these people.
Corrected by 4be1
www.addic7ed.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org