Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
- hey, man.
my name's jeff.
I'm trying to lock down
the rest of my schedule
Before the deadline.
I heard this class
was a cakewalk.
Are you passing it?
Do you like dane cook?
- yeah, he's awesome.
- so far so good.
- death...
So-called...
Is a thing
that makes men weep.
And yet a third of life
is spent
In sleep.
Open your textbooks
to page 37.
Now...close them
and throw them away.
Throw it away!
[laughs]
For those of you
who are new,
The motto of this class:
carpe diem.
"seize the day!"
No tests! no papers.
You want an "a"?
Live in...
The moment.
- jackpot.
- take off your shoes.
Quick. take off your shoes.
everyone, take your shoes off.
Throw them away.
Throw them across the room
over there.
Today, we learn to walk!
Get up and walk out the door!
This day could be your last!
You could die in your sleep.
You could get hit by a bus.
You, that mole is raised
and dark.
It's not a good combo.
You are new.
- yes, i'm new.
But i'll be old too soon.
Carpe diem, sir.
carpe diem!
- [laughs] i like it!
- voice command.
[phone beeps]
Voice command.
[beep]
Voice command!
[clears throat]
Voice com--
[beep]
- would you please use
the buttons?
- okay, grandpa.
- [high-pitched sneeze]
- oh, god bless you, dear.
[laughter]
- what's so funny?
- you guys, i found it.
the ultimate blow-off class.
Professor whitman.
he thinks
he's in dead poets society.
There's no tests.
there's no work.
It's just "day seizing."
The deadline to enroll
is tomorrow.
I suggest you all do it.
- well, some of us are here
to actually learn things.
- i'm in.
- me too. it sounds educational.
- i'll do it.
i love robin williams.
- abed?
- not a fan.
In every movie,
there's an authority figure
That gets mad at him
for making people laugh.
- no, are--are you going
to take the class?
- oh, can't.
My dad will only pay
for classes
That will help me run
the family restaurant.
It's been struggling
since 2001.
9/11 was pretty much the 9/11
of the falafel business.
- so your dad has your whole
life planned out for you?
Are you even interested
in falafel?
- i'm interested
in making movies.
But my dad says
all media's western propaganda
That negatively stereotypes
arabs.
- then he should see aladdin.
jafar was a bad-ass.
- yes, he was.
- abed.
- mm.
- how much
does a film class cost?
- $70.
- britta.
- jeff.
- isn't abed's dad
a hardcore muslim?
They're not as understanding
as christians.
You can get your head cut off
with a salami sword.
- shirley!
That's the most racist thing
i've ever heard.
- pierce will beat that
in one minute.
[watch beeps]
- this is really nice of you.
the memo says "for dreams."
- oh!
- you guys, are we going
to study spanish
Or keep getting involved
in each other's personal lives?
- [high-pitched sneeze]
- hey, troy sneezes like a girl.
- and how about i pound you
like a boy?
That didn't come out right.
- why don't you all
just leave him alone
With his cute little
baby sneezes.
- you're not my mother.
- she's not?
- 29 seconds.
- * give me some rope,
time in a tree *
* give me the hope
to run out of steam *
* somebody said
we could be here *
* we could roped up, tied up,
dead in a year *
* i can't count the reasons
i should stay *
* one by one they all
just fade away *
- what's your name?
- my name is shirley bennett.
- shirley, you get an "a"...
- oh.
- if you can tell me
why you are here at greendale.
- what'd i tell you?
Okay, but, uh,
never again.
- shirley?
- to get a degree in business
So i can sell my baked goods
and whatnot on the internet.
- why...are you here?
- to get a degree
in business
So i can sell my baked goods
and whatnot on the internet.
- why are you here?
- because i wasted 15 years
of my life on a man
Who left me with nothing
but stretch marks
And a foggy memory
of two bland orgasms.
And now it's time to get
what's mine.
- day seized.
[applause]
Only when we stop
stopping our lives
Can we begin to start
starting them.
Ms. edison here, for example,
would rather write
About what happens
to other people
Than live
what is happening to her.
- i thought there might be
a quiz.
- well, here's a quiz for you.
Why did the pretty young girl
die alone
Surrounded
by sweater-wearing cats
Who are trained to use
human toilets?
Get up on your desk.
Come on.
stand on your desk.
Up on your desk.
She made it!
ha ha!
Everyone stand
on your desks!
Up, up, up, up, up!
come on.
Rise, rise, rise
above the programming.
All your lives you were told
don't stand on your desks.
Well, why not?
[desk collapses]
- ooh! ooh! oh, heaven.
My.
- she's okay.
Go to the nurse.
seize the day.
- you know, i was really moved
by your honesty earlier.
Particularly the part
about your husband
Not being able,
you know...
- your homework. ah.
I want you to swim in a lake
And tell ten people
that you love them.
Mr. winger,
can i have a word, please?
- are you okay.
- oh, maybe i'm not.
- hi.
Mr. winger, i like to think
that every life
That passes through this class
is changed.
But every year, there's always
one cocky opportunist
Who's just here to coast
and grab an easy "a."
- oh, yeah.
his name's pierce.
I-i can talk to him
for you.
- 's actually you,
mr. winger.
You have no intention
of seizing the day.
- what? listen,
i-i have never lived
Until i met you.
I-i love you.
Oh, there's one down.
nine to go.
Not that i need the grade
or even want it!
- well, i'm glad to hear it.
Because if you don't genuinely
seize the day
Before the end of the week,
Then you will be seizing an "f"
for the semester.
- you...
This is no way
to teach accounting!
- i have to plan
in advance
How to prove that i live
in the moment.
I mean, i'd rather take
an actual class,
But now it's too late
to drop or add.
- it is not fair how hard it is
for you to cheat here.
[inhales]
hey, how's it going?
How's your film class,
buddy?
- it's cool. our first
assignment is a documentary.
They're like real movies,
but with ugly people.
I'm learning a lot.
- that is so wonderful.
Some people don't like
getting involved
In other's lives.
I think it's great.
- hey, if you're making
a documentary
About britta patting herself
on the back,
You're gonna need
a backup battery.
- actually, i'm doing a movie
about my dad.
- that is brilliant.
How did he react to you
signing up for the film class?
- that part hasn't happened yet.
here he comes.
- hey! you want to get involved
in my family's business?
- holy...war.
- where do i find mr. britta?
- i'm mr. britta.
That's right.
i'm a woman with rights.
And you can see
my whole face.
- oh, i get it!
Because i'm arab,
i must hate women.
Let me tell you something,
i love women.
But i'm getting a major
b-word vibe from you.
- wow, i can't believe
i missed out
On getting involved
in this.
- you go host american idol
And you stop messing
with my son.
He's a special boy.
I raise him, okay?
you don't raise him.
- raising him means letting him
follow his dreams.
- dreams are for sleeping.
- you don't know that.
- it's clinically proven.
- so's polio.
- you lost me!
- abed wants to study film.
- [speaking arabic]
- wait, what is he saying?
- he says "we're leaving."
- tell him that you want
to stay and study film.
- i don't think i'm really
in the scene.
- see, it was hard enough
to talk to him before.
Now we have this between us!
Let's go!
- hey! hey!
- hey, don't touch me!
- guys, guys, stop it.
stop it.
- you don't touch me!
- britta back up. stop.
Sir, you have a right
to your faith
And your family's privacy.
But abed is an adult
and a u.s. citizen.
Right?
- yeah.
- and he has the right
to stay.
- fine. you want to raise him,
you raise him.
I'm out!
- wait, what?
- you know, i had a father
like you.
And the day i finally
cut myself loose
[crying] is the day
i finally started being happy.
- well, that went well.
- i'll have to make
some adjustments to my film.
Jeff, i think you should play
the role of my father.
- i don't want to be
your father.
- that's perfect.
you already know your lines.
What?
Why are you dressed
like an '80s rapist?
- professor whitman
comes by here every morning
And i need him to see me
celebrating life.
What's all that?
- i am calculating
abed's expenses
For the semester.
You know, there's books.
there's meals.
He's renting that camera.
And, you know, he needs
a little spending money.
- um, all money
is spending money.
- britta, um, it's amazing
what you're doing for abed.
I mean, a lot of people talk
a good game.
But you, you follow through.
love you.
- shirley, thank you.
Bet that doesn't happen
to you a lot.
- happened yesterday.
Shirley's just doing
her homework.
- hillary, thank you
for getting people coffee.
I love you.
- abed,
how's it going, buddy?
- good. my film
is coming together.
Cool tie, jeff.
Are you wearing that
Because you're playing
the role of my dad,
Or is it really christmas?
- definitely christmas.
- is that a new camera?
- yeah.
It's more expensive,
But it lets me adjust
really specific settings
That most people don't notice
or think about.
Hi, i would like a latte.
And, jeff,
let me get you something.
- i'm okay.
- oh, come on. i got you.
- no, really.
i don't need anything.
you're insulting me.
Look at all this cash.
- okay, i will get
a small, black coffee.
- boo. an ordinary coffee
for an ordinary life.
- [perky] good morning,
professor whitman.
- sorry, mr. winger,
these won't cut it.
- shazbot!
- i shall have...
A birthday cake!
- [high-pitched sneeze]
[laughter]
- i've seen men
in your situation, troy.
No, those are both for me.
You were
on top of the world before
And now no one
gives a rat's ass.
I can help you
with your image.
First, lose the jacket.
You look
like a high school bitch.
But more importantly,
it's your sneeze.
When i was a ceo,
I had an array
of masculine sneezes
That asserted dominance.
You know, like,
the explosive,
Shock-the-room-into-silence
sneeze.
The [deafening sneeze]
[shouts incoherently]
Or the draw-them-in sneeze.
You know...
[gasping convulsively]
And maybe i wouldn't sneeze
because i'm in control.
You could even use a sneeze
to drive home a point even.
Like, i think--
i think the cubs
Are going to win it all
this year.
[violently clipped sneeze]
[sniffs]
What do you think?
- tell me more.
- it's showtime.
Hey, everybody.
good morning.
Good morning, sir.
Good morning, greendale!
hi! good morning!
Watch the kite.
uh-oh.
Mind if i get a chance?
oh!
Look at this.
one foot.
[laughing]
Thanks, you guys.
bring it in here.
Nice. thank you so much,
you guys.
That was really fun.
- sloppy.
And considering the age
of these girls,
Unwittingly creepy.
- damn it.
Beat it.
Professor, will you look
at the amount of work
That i'm putting into this?
I mean, throw me a bone!
- had i not already cried
at the sunrise this morning,
I would be weeping right now.
- what does that mean?
- what do you mean, jeff?
What does your life mean?
How long does it take you
in the morning
To--to make it look
like you have bed head?
How many sweat pants,
sport jacket combos did you try
Before you found the one
that said "i don't care"?
Seize the day, jeff,
for real.
Go running naked
in a hailstorm,
Kiss a girl in the middle
of the day,
Fly a kite,
but do it for yourself.
Or you won't just fail
my class,
You'll fail life.
- thank you.
That guy's
really got your number.
- drop the flower.
- look, i really need
to talk to you about abed.
I went by his film class today.
he wasn't there.
He's cutting.
I want to know why he would do
something like that.
- ask him.
- every time i try to ask him
about it,
He just keeps filming me
and telling me
That i'm playing the role
of his mother.
- abed is not normal.
That's what you bought
When you intentionally tangled
yourself in his life.
- look, will you just--
will you please talk to him?
- i've got problems of my own!
I'm out here trying
to seize a day!
What in the hell?
Is he gonna kill us?
- thanks for the pizza, abed.
i was starving.
- yeah, it's nice.
like a--like a picnic.
- or a family dinner.
- it's a study group
and a pizza.
Let's not get carried away.
[britta clears throat]
[clears throat louder]
- so, abed,
how's film class?
- good.
- yeah? did you go
to class today?
- not really.
Well, britta's paying
for those classes.
Don't you think
maybe you should go?
- i was shooting my movie.
- yeah, but your movie's
for class.
- my movie's more important.
- well, ooh la la.
- someone order
seven lattes?
- i got that.
- no, you don't got it.
I got it, abed.
i got everything.
What is wrong with you?
All i want to do
is take care of you.
I know you're not stupid.
are you doing this on purpose?
Why won't you answer me?
- 'cause this is the scene
where you leave.
- you better believe it.
- britta.
- what do you think, dad?
- i think you are
really weird, abed.
And i think the wrong person
just left.
- perfect.
that's a wrap.
- that guy was your dad?
- hey.
You don't really have tickets
for ravi shankar, do you?
- i lied to get you here
Because it's time
to communicate.
- communicate.
have you met abed?
- it's not the two of you
that need to talk.
- hey, wait a minute,
where's weezer?
- they're coming.
All right, now,
the only reason
Why this whole mess
got started
Is because both of you wanted
the best for abed.
And i think the lesson
we can all take away from this
Is that everyone
should always do
Whatever they want
and leave each other out of it.
- is that your take?
let me give you mine.
You and your pillow-lipped
girlfriend
Got all up in my stuff
because you wanted to be cowboys
And then you turned chicken
when you found out
It will take more than speeches
and guided missiles.
- interesting. hadn't seen
the iraq metaphor, but--
- what iraq metaphor?
I am talking
about your speeches
And her guided--
- got it!
The point is is that britta
is sorry, right?
- wrong.
- crap.
- abed may not be
a great filmmaker,
But that doesn't mean
that he wants to make falafel.
You need to let him make
his own decisions.
- make his own decisions?
Have you met abed?
you know who he is?
- guys.
- yes.
- guys!
- he loves--
- i'm finished.
Britta, jeff, dad.
Dad.
[presses key]
[noisemaker tooting]
[baby crying]
- how's it going, buddy?
- i don't want to be
your father.
[baby crying]
I think
you are weird, abed.
- okay, look, i need to talk
to you about abed.
- he's not normal.
[man screams]
- what is wrong with you?
All i want to do
is take care of you.
Why will you not answer me?
[horse neighs]
[heart monitor beeping]
[flatline]
- what do you think, dad?
- i think you are weird,
abed.
And i think the wrong person
just left.
- it's not exactly
citizen kane.
- [crying]
- i feel a little out
of the loop here.
- that feeling is called
the joy of freedom.
- my son is hard
to understand.
If making movies help him
be understood,
Then i pay for the class.
- [whispering]
i made this all happen.
- with falafel as a fallback.
- abed.
- yeah.
- did you do all of that
to me on purpose?
That's not a very nice way
to treat your friends.
- well, britta, it isn't called
friend business,
It's called show business.
- he's smoking.
- honey, let him leave
the nest.
- get your hand off my knee.
- sorry.
- [clamorous sneeze]
- god--god bless you.
god bless you.
- thank you.
- for someone who doesn't like
getting involved,
Well, i owe you.
- you owe me.
That cannot be comfortable
for you.
- hey, um, you should kiss me
right now.
- day seized!
- we're even.
- [laughs]
"a" plus, winger.
I know a life-changing kiss
when i see one.
Wowee! ha ha!
[laughing]
- yeah. fooled you.
Captioning by Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org