I had to get up so early for my bus
I caught what Cinemax
gets up to at night.
Subscription cancelled.
I got that channel for
Eddie Murphy movies,
not stimulation.
Why are you taking the bus?
What happened to your minivan?
My ex-husband needed it.
The person he's dating
works at a club
an hour from the city.
Oh. Well,
I'll play a violin for them
and maybe she can strip to it.
Kind people are
always kind, Britta.
Not just when it's easy.
As we stand, once again
upon the deadline
to drop or add classes,
I hereby present this semester's
Jeff Winger pick
for ultimate blow-off class:
Beginner Pottery.
Your last "blow off" class
ended up teaching me
to live in the moment.
Which I will always regret
and never do again.
This one's different.
I researched.
You don't have to make
a good pot.
You get an art credit
for participation.
This class is like a redhead
that drinks Scotch
and loves Die Hard.
I suggest you all get her number.
Ahoy.
Guess which class I signed up for.
Singing with Tennille?
[LAUGHlNG]
Sailing.
The nearest body of water
is two and a half hours away.
Leagues, Abed.
We don't measure water
by hours.
It's a one-week intensive
that gives you hands-on
experience on a real boat
right here in the parking lot.
I'd rather learn boats
than pots.
I was gonna take a class
on how to put together
an online dating profile.
But I think sailing
in the parking lot
is less pathetic.
A black person on a sail boat?
I gotta see this. I'm in.
How about you, Abed?
You wanna sail with us?
There's black people.
Mm-hm. Two.
[§§§]
JEFF:
All right.
Hello, ladies.
What you guys making,
big balls here?
Oh, yeah.
You guys getting dirty?
Nice.
What are you looking at?
Heh, heh. All right.
Hey, Laura lngalls.
Home Depot guy.
Who's making pots, huh?
Let's participate this thing.
Let's do this.
Ladies, I don't know
why you're laughing.
I do wanna make
my mom an ashtray.
Okay.
[RlCH LAUGHlNG]
Hello, my precious blueberries.
Hello.
Hi.
All right,
let's spin those wheels
and play with some clay.
Now, there's one
and only one rule
in this class.
I will tolerate no reenacting,
whether it's ironic or sincere,
of the Patrick Swayze-Demi Moore
pottery scene in Ghost.
Ever since that movie
was released in 1 990,
I have seen every conceivable
variation of what I call ghosting.
This can be guy-on-girl,
girl-on-guy.
The hilarious guy-on-guy.
[LAUGHlNG]
[lMlTATES GUNSHOT]
So since it never stopped,
I had to adopt
a zero-Ghost-tolerance policy.
If you so much as hum
three notes from that
Righteous Brothers song
with God as my witness,
I will come at you
with everything I've got, okay?
Let's have a great time.
[CLAY THUDS]
[§§§]
I'm making falafel.
Mm.
Not edible.
What are you making?
A vase.
Hey, guys.
Yep?
Look what I made.
A participant badge.
[GASPS]
[CHUCKLES]
I don't know how.
I mean, I just stuck my hands
into the clay and it happened.
You look at me.
You have a gift.
ABED:
Jeff's competitive side
had come out before,
he had even displayed envy,
but on that first day of Pottery class--
Abed.
Yeah?
What did we discuss?
No voiceover. I'm sorry.
It is kind of a crutch.
[THE 88'S "AT LEAST
lT WAS HERE" PLAYlNG]
I've never been
on a boat before.
I didn't know what to wear.
TROY:
Yeah, it's intimidating.
We're in Pierce's world now.
He's got all the boat clothes,
and look at him christen.
If that were me,
I would have broken the bottle.
I'm Professor Slaughter.
Welcome aboard
the S.S. Nose Candy,
purchased through
government auction.
Oh, that's nice.
It's not nice.
It's your only weapon
against the raging sea.
If you don't know how to use her,
you're dead.
Together, you will work as one crew.
You will succeed or fail as one crew.
You will consider this parking lot
the ocean.
Whatever you drop, you lose.
Mishandle the sails,
you capsize and die.
Now, does Little Miss Nice
have a name?
Shirley Bennett.
Well, now you're
Captain Shirley Bennett.
Aw, man.
You will follow her every order.
Oh.
I've never been a captain before.
I have.
I commanded a jet ski
through an electrical storm
and only had one casualty.
Jet skis only hold
two people.
Exactly. Saved half the crew.
Pottery is much cooler than I thought.
And harder.
Well, except for that guy Rich.
He's like a natural.
Yeah. I'm worried
about the effect that
it's having on Jeff, though.
Yeah, someone call a shrink.
What?
Well, you're usually
the cool one.
Abed, you understand the point
of a blow-off class is to blow it off?
Not to be cool at making
really important mud pies.
Not willing to admit he's talented?
No, because he's not.
If I ever make an effort in that class,
you'd think I was the cat's pajamas.
"Cat's pajamas"?
Okay, Pierce.
Wow.
Somebody's mommy gave him
too much praise.
Man, so did someone's
psych teacher.
[§§§]
[GASPS]
Oh, Señor Chang.
Yes, I was robbed
at the YMCA. Again.
[§§§]
All right, let's do this.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
JEFF'S MOM:
Jeff, do you know what you are?
You're special.
You're very special, Jeff.
You're the most special
little boy in the world.
[WHlSTLE BLOWS]
Take her back to harbor.
SHlRLEY:
Flank the sheets
and trim the headsail.
Eyes on me for a moment.
I don't see students here,
I see seamen.
And I didn't create them.
From the moment
you climbed aboard,
I saw seamen inside you.
More importantly,
you've stopped giggling
at the word "seamen."
And that's the mark
of a real seaman.
All right, as you were.
Okay, then.
Crew, make fast the topping lift.
PlERCE:
I'll get the rope.
[PlERCE GRUNTS]
BRlTTA: Oh, my God.
Damn. He's ghost riding the jib.
Pierce, hang on.
That hat's gone. Lost at sea.
I might be able to reach it.
it landed on that Hyundai.
I mean, mermaid's car.
Get back on this boat.
No, no, no.
Well, I spoke too soon.
Everybody gets a D.
If I had chosen to hit you
with a storm just then,
you all would have failed.
You better get your crew in line,
captain.
Permission to speak?
Mm-hm.
You really screwed the pooch
on that one, captain.
And I can't swim.
RlCH:
So, you see, ladies,
it's actually a working fountain
with a bird.
[lMlTATlNG BlRD CHlRPlNG]
Heh, heh, heh.
Hey, Jeff,
ready to make some art
in the shape of a vase?
No, can't.
Ooh, ouch.
Let me take a look.
Rich, being good at
Beginner Pottery doesn't
mean you can heal people.
That's true.
But my medical degree does.
I'm a doctor.
A doctor?
I just take pottery to unwind.
I haven't lost a patient in five years.
Puts a lot of pressure on a person.
So the good news is
this is neither sprained
nor broken.
Oh, thank God.
But I'll have to get
a second opinion
from a guy in my
basket-weaving class.
[LAUGHS]
That's great. It's funny.
Good to see you
getting along with Rich.
What's he like?
He's a ringer.
A what?
You know, a con man,
a grifter, a ringer.
He's an expert potter who
signs up for novice classes
to impress people.
If he wants to impress,
why join a pottery class?
Why not just say,
"Hi, I'm a doctor"?
Because he's crazy.
And fancy jobs
don't impress people.
You weren't impressed
I'm a lawyer.
Anyone can be a lawyer.
You can even represent yourself.
You can't do surgery on yourself.
It's illegal. You'd get arrested.
And then you'd get a free lawyer.
Rich showed me
how to make a flared lip
on my pot
and check for breast lumps.
Ha.
I don't know how,
and I don't know when,
but one day that guy
is gonna slip up
and when that happens,
I am gonna be there
to expose him.
Jeff, check it out.
If your finger's still
bugging you,
just get creative.
I wanna kiss you on the mouth.
I'm sorry?
[§§§]
Hey, Rich. Hey.
Don't run so fast,
you're among friends.
How you doing, Jeff? What's up?
Not much, nada mucho.
Noddily Merchant.
Just want to thank you,
Doc Potterywood,
for taking a look at my finger.
Anytime.
Doc Potterywood, I like it.
Have you taken
many pottery classes?
No, this is my first.
Of the year?
Ever.
No pottery at doctor school?
Medical school?
Pottery school.
Pottery school?
Oh, pottery school?
How long?
Jeff, it's kind of weird,
I feel I'm being interrogated,
but by someone who doesn't really
wanna know anything important.
[BOTH LAUGHlNG]
Oh, hey, New Mexico.
Long way from home.
Yeah. Well, I did my residency
in Santa Fe.
Santa Fe.
Yeah.
Can I give you a lift somewhere?
Oh, no, thanks.
I'm getting there.
[§§§]
[MUMBLlNG lNDlSTlNCTLY]
Did you sleep here?
Only for a few hours.
Guess where Rich is from.
Couldn't have been Crazy Town.
You'd have gone to school together.
Santa Fe, New Mexico.
Nobody gets out of Santa Fe
without learning to make a pot.
Forty-five percent Hispanic.
Fifth-highest Native American
population.
They eat and breathe clay there.
I think some of this research
may have been done
on Wikipedia.
You're mocking me? You?
No, you, fine, go ahead, mock me.
Oh, Jeff, you're Goldblum-ing.
JEFF: Goldblum-ing?
Heh. What? I, uh...
I don't even know what that means.
Look, I have work to do
before class
because I wanna catch Rich
when he slips up.
But who even cares
if he's pretending
to be a beginner?
Pottery cares. Integrity cares.
Look, I don't care.
I just care that he cares.
It's lame that he cares.
Shoelace came untied.
Could happen to anybody.
That's your excuse?
Britta weighs 5 pounds.
Troy can't swim.
I've never seen the ocean.
Uh, I can swim, racist.
Listen to me.
On my boat,
the crew comes first.
No single person is above it.
You either shape up
or ship the hell out.
Now I know what the C
in captain stands for.
Crab apple.
Shirley, I thought you said
that kind people were always kind.
Yes. And strong people change.
If the sea was always still and calm,
nobody would respect her.
I'm like the sea.
Hey.
Cuckoo birds, do you mind?
This is important.
College is where most
mental problems activate.
I hope I get
multiple personalities.
I get lonely in
long showers.
SLAUGHTER:
The barometer's dropping.
The temperature is warm,
but we're heading
into a high-pressure flow.
That's a perfect storm.
Reef the mainsail and furl the jib.
Is that nautical talk
or urban speak?
We have to turn back.
Accidental jibe.
Hit the deck.
[GROANS]
Oh!
Man overboard.
BRlTTA:
Oh, my God, Pierce is dead!
No, wait.
His stomach is moving.
BRlTTA:
Oh, my God. Pierce.
That's it. Pull me in.
The storm is overtaking you,
captain.
We don't have time.
I'm trying as hard as I can.
I have skinny arms
for a quarterback.
I said, we don't have time.
[§§§]
What? No. Pull--
Wait. Pull me in.
What do you mean, "time"?
That's it.
What? No.
No!
Bring the boom amidship.
What in God's name have we done?
[PlERCE CRYlNG]
Hey.
Get out of my parking spot,
dipwad.
Security.
I mean,
take an intermediate class
if you're an intermediate.
Don't come in here making
your fear of failure our problem.
I mean, it's crazy.
It's crazy.
I mean,
he's a crazy person.
[WHlSPERlNG]
I'm scared.
It's okay. This is good for him.
He's confronting his own limitations.
Busted.
Fatal mistake, Richy boy.
You are busted.
I am?
You just used the
"throwing off the hump"
method.
That's an advanced pottery
technique, which I know
because last night I read the
entire Encyclopedia of Pottery.
What are you talking about?
You are no beginner, Santa Fe.
Hey, what is going on,
my blueberries?
Show him what you did.
No.
I rest my case.
What case?
Throw the freaking hump,
imposter.
RlCH: What are you doing? No.
Hey! Hey!
It's the hilarious
guy-on-guy.
One rule I asked you to follow.
One.
Look.
ANNlE: Oh!
I had it made before he died.
It's not in bad taste.
Out, Winger.
Fine. That's fine.
No, that's fine.
[PEOPLE GASP]
Congratulations.
You've failed a class
so easy
that people passing
in the hallway
get a contact credit.
[SlNGlNG
"UNCHAlNED MELODY"]
No, this is abuse!
This is abuse!
Pierce. Do you still have
the number of that private
investigator you used
when you thought Ross Perot
was sleeping with your mom?
Is this about that guy in your class?
Yeah.
Face the facts.
This kid's got some natural talent
you just don't have.
How would you know?
It's all over the school.
Great.
Why aren't you in sailing class?
They drowned me.
Why?
For a better grade.
But weren't we discussing
your flaws, Jeff?
Why are you letting
this guy get to you?
What's really going on?
I made a bad pot.
For some reason,
I always thought that
I was special and different.
And I guess I just have
a really hard time
when I want to be good
at something and I suck.
Uh-huh.
Here, give me a hand.
What are you doing?
I'm going back to my sailing class.
After they murdered you?
Jeffrey, when I was born,
I got my umbilical cord
wrapped around my neck,
both arms and one of my ankles.
Mom said there came
a point when the doctors
stopped delivering me
and just started laughing. Heh.
I mean, if I ever let being bad
at something stop me,
I wouldn't even be here.
That thing some men call failure?
I call living.
Breakfast.
And I'm not leaving
till I've cleaned out the buffet.
Now, how about a shove?
[§§§]
Good luck, Pierce.
Don't need it.
Never had it.
Britta,
trim the boom flat.
Troy, sit windward
to heel the boat.
My, the sea has a worthy opponent.
Oh, my God, it's Pierce.
[§§§]
Man, that guy's life
is one big joke.
I mean, I feel bad for him,
but things have been running
smoother since he drowned.
I bet he gets that
all the time.
[GRUNTlNG]
[SPRlNKLER HlSSES]
Oh. Oh. Hey. Hey.
TROY: Oh, my God.
PlERCE: It's going down.
Pierce is going to be the only person
ever to drown in a parking lot,
twice.
[LAUGHlNG]
Help!
Damn the storm.
We're going after Pierce.
Jump the halyard.
Star-Burns, get down there
and man the iron jinny.
There's a man overboard.
That's an order.
PlERCE:
I'm gonna sink.
I'm about to get the only A
I will ever get,
and Pierce isn't even dying.
Bailing.
You don't have to do this.
I know.
But I'd rather be kind
and get stepped on
every once in a while
than be a hard-ass
and turn my back on a friend.
Hoist the mains.
[CRYlNG]
I don't want to go this way.
[§§§]
SHlRLEY:
We're coming, Pierce.
PlERCE:
Help.
SHlRLEY: How's it looking?
BRlTTA: We've gotta go faster.
Okay, come on, Star-Burns.
BRlTTA:
It's filling with water.
It's going down.
Pierce, we're coming.
Dear God. Dear God.
Oh, yes. Oh, Britta.
Troy.
Here you go. We gotcha.
Here you go.
Okay.
[LAUGHS]
SHlRLEY: Are you okay?
You all right?
You just steered
your boat into a storm.
Any last words?
The sea may be cold
and unforgiving,
but I'm not.
The ship might go down
but at least she'll go down
with honor.
Then I'll take
your captain's hat
because I'm promoting
you to admiral.
You all get an A.
Oh.
Admiral Shirley. I like that.
Well, it means nothing,
really, the class is over.
But you deserve it.
Hey, somebody has to do this.
I'm king of the--
[WHlSTLE BLOWlNG]
Don't ruin a perfect week.
[§§§]
I'm not gonna spoon you again.
I appreciate that.
Yeah, I can't fully explain
my behavior.
I'd love to blame booze
or demon possession--
You know what?
Don't worry about it.
I'm bad at holding grudges.
Well, I'm bad at pottery.
I'm an amateur pottery enthusiast
trying as hard as I can
at something I suck at.
It's great.
And the teacher said
I could stay if I don't have
any more Ghost bursts.
Fantastic. Well, good luck.
Don't need it.
JEFF'S MOM:
Jeff, you're a normal person.
There's nothing very special
about you at all.
You're going to be great
at a few things
but really crappy
at many more.
And that takes a lot
of the pressure off
so you can live
a full, happy life.
Oh, and sorry it took me so long
to tell you that
and it was only
in your imagination.
My bad. Kind of a sloppy mom.
That's okay, Mom.
Nobody's perfect.
I'm still scared.
[§§§]
RlCH'S MOM:
A clay ashtray. You're an idiot.
Why do you have time
to make pottery?
Couldn't you use a little more
practice being a doctor?
Not that it'll ever bring your brother
back to life.
It was supposed to be you
on that roller coaster, Richard.
It was supposed to be you.
Whoo!
Oh, come on. Again?
Good grief.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org