I don't want to be late
for lunch.
"amar" is "to love," right?
Oh!
Speaking of love,
Shirley, how's it going
with the sexy dreadlock guy?
Oh, I'm sure I don't
have a chance with him.
Abed and I talked to him
by the vending machines.
He asked about you.
He specifically asked about me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Sure.
When Annie brought you up,
he specifically asked,
"who is that?"
Abed.
- Oh.
- What? That's what he said.
Abed, your social skills
aren't exactly streets ahead.
You know what I mean?
- I don't.
- You're not alone in this case.
Pierce, stop trying
to coin the phrase,
"streets ahead."
Trying?
Coined and minted.
Been there, coined that.
"streets ahead"
is verbal wildfire.
Does it just mean "cool,"
or is it
Supposed to be,
like, "miles ahead"?
If you have to ask,
you're street's fine.
Okay, we can banter
if we want to banter,
But I'm warning you
I am leaving for lunch early.
- Me too.
- Me three.
Streets ahead.
Man, you guys really love
These stupid
chicken fingers, huh?
Uh, they're not stupid.
They're the only good thing
in the cafeteria.
I haven't had one in weeks.
They run out so fast.
If God were edible--
not that I'm catholic,
But if it was cool to eat God,
He'd be a chicken finger.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, I wouldn't know.
I'm a vegetarian.
- Shocker.
- Yeah.
And if you guys knew
how they treated
The animals
that you are eating,
You would eat them even faster
Just to put them
out of their misery
And then you would throw up.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm feeling
extra protective
Of animals today because
my cat is sick.
- Oh, a cat?
- That's awful.
He has diabetes.
He can't even make it
to the litter box--
- Chicken run!
- Whoo!
Ow!
I'm afraid that I'm gonna
have to put her to sleep.
Ah, go on.
God bless you.
Save some for me!
Watch out!
Sync By YesCool -
Resync for 720p by Baqinardo
~ iSubs.coil.us.to & Addic7ed.com
Oh, I can hear those fingers
calling my name.
"Troy!
Troy!"
Troy, did you get
my text message?
"did you get my text message?"
Um, I think it's--
I got to stop hanging out
with her.
She sounds like
a chicken finger.
Again?
Outrageous.
At least apologize.
How can you just stand
there like a mute idiot?
- Ooh.
- Well...
Throat surgery
might humanize you,
But it doesn't
make this acceptable.
So cute.
And I don't even normally
like dreadlocks.
Hello.
His dreadlocks remind me
of the predator,
Which is weird, because
you're doing the actual hunting
And you seem invisible to him.
- Abed, you know what I do?
- Hmm?
Before I talk, I ask myself,
"what am I about to say
And how might it affect
each person listening?"
I'm really glad
you said that, britta.
The idea that you compulsively
filter yourself
Makes your lack of flavor
kind of a flavor.
Sorry, guys.
They ran out again.
Something's gotta be done.
Hey!
What the hell, man?
That's half our problem
right there.
Star-burns works the fryer
and skims fingers.
No way.
He gives them to people just so
They'll act like
he isn't star-burns
Well, I may not eat meat,
But I am not gonna
eat that injustice.
Let's complain.
If we complain,
he gets a warning
And learns to be sneakier.
I say we knock him out
of the kitchen
And replace him with one
of our own
All in one move.
Then we're the ones
with the chicken.
It's like a mafia movie.
As far back as I can remember,
I always wanted to be
in a mafia movie.
Cool.
That's exactly
what it's like, Abed,
And you get the most
important job.
You're gonna be fry cook.
We may be watching
different mafia movies.
You worked in your
dad's restaurant, right?
Well, you'll apply for the job
After we get star-burns fired.
I don't know about that.
I don't know about the firing.
I think he really relies
on that income.
Yeah, man.
Every day you flock here
like sheep
And wait in line for a broken
promise from a dirty system.
Back in those days, Jeff winger
Was the guy that
made things happen.
He always knew what to say
And he always knew when
to slap the table.
You want to be sheep,
keep flocking.
You want to be wolves,
form a pack.
And that was it.
It was that simple.
At that moment,
we stopped being a family
And started being a family...
In italics.
Britta got cozy
with star-burns.
- Can I touch both at--oh!
- Yeah, do 'em both.
He lowered his guard
and just like that,
He was gone.
I mean, the way Jeff saw it,
by not respecting us,
Star-burns had basically brought
it on himself.
And when his job opened up,
we did what we had to do
To keep the list
of applicants to a minimum.
I had worked in my dad's
falafel restaurant,
So I had a pretty
impressive resume.
It's very impressive.
Especially your reference.
Just give 'em a call right now.
But we weren't taking
any chances.
The fix was in.
Trump tower, this is Donald.
Well, he can deep-fry
the hell out of chicken.
I can tell you that.
Troy even applied
for the same job
And gave the world's
worst interview
Just to make me look better
And that was that.
This was the glorious time.
No more racing
to the cafeteria.
No more lines.
To us, lines were for suckers,
Hacks, sheep.
We were wolves.
And we had the chicken
to prove it.
- Oh.
- Ooh.
To victory.
It feels unfamiliar,
But it tastes like chicken.
Mm-hmm.
Hi.
- Hello.
- You guys are lucky.
They're always running out.
Would you like one?
Name's Shirley.
Memorize it.
I will, Shirley.
Eee!
See that, girls?
The universe goes
by supply and demand.
The more you take and use,
the more it sends.
Somebody's been taking
a little extra.
What's in that container?
- Eight fingers.
- Abed.
Abed's study group.
Why are you giving
Chang chicken?
We have an agreement.
But, Abed,
if you get caught skimming,
You get fired and we all go back
to eating like britta.
Yeah, we put you in that job.
I dressed like a crazy pharaoh
for you, man.
You make the fingers, Abed,
not the decisions.
I'm sorry.
It's okay, buddy.
But just remember
these things have power.
So just let me know next time
You have any more agreements,
all right?
Yeah, I agreed to give Cheng
eight fingers per lunch
In exchange for a 10% bump
on every Spanish test
For each of us.
- Oh!
- Okay.
Abed makes the fingers
and the decisions.
- Yeah.
Oh, Abed, you're like the best.
At greendale, they were always
out of chicken fingers,
So whoever could get
them had power.
Oh.
And I was the guy in the apron,
So I came up with a system
and pretty soon
Half the chicken at greendale
Was going out the side door.
Everybody in our crew
had a job.
T-bone was the bag man.
He'd move the fingers
to a storeroom
Where two of the girls
did the packaging.
We could trust them not
to eat the supply
Because britta was a vegetarian
And Shirley figured
that if she stole,
She'd go to hell.
They'd hand the stuff
out the window to Annie.
She was the leg man
and distributor.
The crazy thing
was it was their food
And we were stealing it and
giving it back to them
Like it was a big favor.
Nobody asked any questions
because Pierce's experience
As a ceo had taught him how
To keep the wheels
from squeaking.
I had it all worked out
on a schedule.
You know, I've never been
fired from a job
And this is, like,
my perfect job.
I'm Mr. Chicken fingers.
The minute before
you thought about busting us,
That was the minute you
had a chicken in your hand.
Everyone had their hand out.
Everyone wanted what we had.
Oh! Oh, well.
So we had anything we wanted.
And Jeff had the most
important job of all.
He was at the top.
He was the boss.
He was our leader.
What the hell is going on?
A-v kids hooked it up.
Abed supplied
the whole department
With chicken fingers.
You think that's good,
Check out my posse
and Troy's monkey.
Troy, why do you have a monkey?
Uh, it's an animal
that looks like a dude.
Why don't I have ten of them?
Guys, look what Abed
scored for me.
Ooh.
It has a million zippers
And it was free.
- Oh.
- Ooh, robot.
I am a robot.
I am programmed
to love this backpack.
This is insane.
More insane
than programming them
To replace auto workers?
What?
Okay, okay, if you're not
in this study group, please.
No, no.
That means you,
sexy dreadlocks,
Britta's hairdresser...
What?
Pierce's hackneyed entourage.
Hackneyed?
You see the turban guy?
Yes, in a '90s ski movie
That featured an entourage.
Don't you guys think this
is getting out of hand?
Oh, we're not gonna get caught.
We have campus security
on the take.
Abed's got it all figured out.
- Mm-hmm.
- Well, that's a relief.
Yeah, it's pretty cool
being friends
With the biggest man on campus.
Isn't that right,
Annie's boobs?
Please rename that thing!
And this time, not with
a contest on Twitter.
It's his Twitter account.
He can do what he wants.
They are my body parts!
I do not consent to this!
You know what
I don't appreciate?
You wouldn't threaten a monkey.
They have more
lactic acid than us.
Shared my chicken with him.
- Talk to the backpack.
- I told you!
You're the worst, Annie.
Streets ahead!
Line starts behind you.
Oh, he's cool.
Six fingers every Wednesday.
Cool.
And what can you offer?
I have a bicycle
and I teach beginner's tennis.
Cool.
Okay.
Six fingers wednesdays.
All right.
We'll be in touch, janel.
- Thank you, Abed.
- You're welcome.
Hey, Jeff.
Hey, buddy.
It's quite a setup
you got here.
I'm pretty excited about it.
It turns out everyone has needs
And everyone has functions.
Look, um, I've been thinking
Maybe I need to hit
the big red button
And bring an end
to this operation.
I mean, it's been fun,
but it's out of control now.
Am I right?
I don't know.
The entire campus
is controlled by our group,
Our group is controlled
by chicken,
And the chicken
is controlled by me.
Float?
I'm good.
Abed, the mafia movie is over.
I'm not doing a mafia movie.
In fact, I don't need
to use movies
Or tv shows to talk
to people anymore.
Before, I only needed them
because the day-to-day world
Made no sense to me, but now,
Everyone's speaking
the same language.
Chicken.
I understand people
and they finally understand me.
Abed, eventually people are
gonna get tired of chicken.
I'm tired of chicken.
You're not tired of chicken.
You miss the taste of control.
Well, that's crazy.
Is it?
Unfortunately, the very thing
that drove you
To this dorm room
is what would prevent you
From properly running
this machine
Or even being a cog in it.
Your ego.
Well...
I see.
This has been about me
the whole time.
You want a shot
at the Jeff winger throne?
You better bring
a powerful ass.
Oh, and for your information,
I don't have an ego.
My facebook photo
is a landscape.
You're the best, Eduardo.
Thank you all for coming.
Can we make this quick?
I need to give a banana
to Annie's boobs.
Abed is drunk
with chicken power.
He's gone from lovable
Johnny five to evil hal.
- Hal holb--
- not hal holbrook.
What are you saying?
You all have
to stop working for him.
Let this operation dry up
And let his wheels spin down.
At which point you would
be in charge again, right?
- What?
- This is so sad.
You're jealous of Abed because
he's providing for us.
Mm-hmm.
No, I'm concerned about Abed
Because he won't listen
to reason.
Won't listen to your reason.
Mm-hmm.
Why should he?
Jeff's so not...
Say "streets ahead" and die.
Streets ahead.
You want to boss me around?
Get me an entourage.
Get Troy a monkey.
That's what a real boss does.
Yes.
We probably shouldn't
even be talking to him
Without checking with Abed.
I'm already trying him.
He's not picking up.
What did you do with him?
I don't believe
what greedy sellouts
You people turned out to be.
I'm not gonna stand here
and be ignored.
Shh!
Voicemail.
Hey, Abed.
Jeff says you're
not listening to him.
Does that mean we shouldn't
listen to him either?
Oh, also, should
we make special jackets
For our crime family?
Like, blazers with
chicken finger patches.
I don't know.
Long message. I'm sorry.
That's it!
- Ooh!
- Abed!
Look, I'm walking out
this door right now.
- Okay.
- For real.
- Good.
- I'm not gonna look back.
- Mm-hmm.
- Good-bye.
- Good-bye!
Abed!
- Hi!
- Yes!
Anybody need anything?
Oh, everything.
You look handsome.
I like everything
about you now, Abed.
I want a new hairdresser
though.
Yeah, I got you fired.
You deserved it.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
The question is:
What do they deserve?
Key to the kitchen.
There's a valve on the back
of the chicken fryer
That's not made anymore.
Now, say someone were
to remove it.
The fryer wouldn't work...
Forever.
How petty do you think I am?
Jeff leaving the family didn't
turn out to be a problem.
Okay, I think we're set
for the quiz.
- Yep.
- See you guys in class.
Oh, wait.
Before you go.
- Oh, free notebooks.
- Here.
But the family's success started
to go to their heads.
They didn't have college ruled?
No, sorry.
It's okay.
- Abed?
- Yeah?
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Sure.
We have a situation.
- Hey.
- Who is this?
It's Travis.
You said you wanted someone
in your entourage named Travis.
Show him your license.
Travis is his middle name.
I go by Travis.
No, you go by the door.
See you, Travis.
Get it right next time.
- Abed?
- Yep?
No, no, no, no.
My monkey hates this caviar.
Troy, isn't that--
They were spoiled, fat, lazy.
I'd given them everything
and somehow
I'd lost their respect.
So I did the only thing
I could think of.
I did what I thought Jeff
would do.
I sent them a message.
What is that?
I think it might be a backpack
That's been mutilated.
These were the bad times.
- There he is.
- Jeff.
- Jeff!
Abed killed my backpack.
And I caught him
stuffing my man
Full of chicken and Tyler Perry
has a whole series of movies
About why that's wrong.
That little arab
is off his rocker.
He released Annie's boobs.
Annie's boobs could
be anywhere.
Annie's boobs could be
on the side of the road.
We got it.
The monkey's name
is "annie's boobs."
Look what Abed did to my hair.
I feel terrible for all of you.
Wait, no, I don't,
because I warned you
About all this,
but you were so high
On your backpacks
and hairstyles
You accused me
of being jealous.
You were right.
But what can we do?
I'm sorry, you brushed over
that first part.
Together.
You were right.
Now what you can do is go home
And write that
on your bathroom mirror.
Wouldn't that make it seem
like I was right?
Yeah, because it would be
my mirror.
It's not gonna be reversed
because you're the one who--
As for Abed, for his sake
I guess I'll have
to take him out.
Poor little guy.
Oh, good.
That's nice.
Abed.
What are you doing?
Making tater tots.
You were right,
people got sick of chicken.
But I was close.
I just need a new food,
a new system.
I'm gonna experiment
with jalapeno poppers next
And then zucchini zircles.
I don't get it.
It's not that complicated,
Jeff.
They replaced the "c" in circle
with a "z" for zucchini.
No, no, I mean,
why are you here?
You said you were close?
What were you close to?
To the group?
To people?
Please don't do
a special episode about me.
Oh, I wouldn't dream of it.
Everyone else needs my help.
That's what people don't get,
Is that they need to get me.
I just need to be able to
connect to people like you can,
And then I can
make everyone happy
Like you do.
Do you know why I'm here?
You got caught
with a fake bachelor's degree.
By the way,
they started using that
As a seasonal arc on
law & order.
Total rip off.
I'm here to dismantle
the fryer,
To cut your power off
at its source.
Don't you see what happened?
I manipulated the group
Into getting you
the fry cook job
So I could have some chicken.
And you turned it all into
a way to make everyone like you.
Mm-hmm.
Made me ashamed of myself.
Made me jealous.
Maybe this is
a special episode.
It's pretty alarming behavior,
Jeff.
Yeah.
You know, there's specialists
you could talk to.
Yeah, maybe I should do that.
Mm-hmm.
- In the meantime...
- Mm-hmm?
Let's make a deal.
I'll help you
connect with people,
And you help me
do a better job with them.
Like knight rider.
Exactly.
Deal.
I'll put on a leather jacket
And make out
with an aerobics instructor.
You pull around front
and comedically
Startle passersby
with your ability to talk.
Maybe we should just stay here
And have a plate
of chicken fingers.
Cool.
Can we eat them
while sitting on a table
Like in sixteen candles?
Pick one reference, Abed.
Sixteen candles.
And just like that,
the mafia movie was over.
I quit the fry cook job,
Somewhat for the sake
of the family,
But mostly for the sake
of Jeff's ego.
Poor guy.
Things went back to normal.
Now everyone's back to being
a bunch of regular schnooks,
And I'm back to being a weirdo,
Back to watching
from the outside...
For now.
There's still
not enough chicken fingers.
- No way.
- What?
'cause as soon
as our family moved out,
A new syndicate moved in
to take its place.
But you know what they'll
never make a replacement for?
Friends.
Okay, thank you.
That's great, Abed.
But could you just
answer the question?
What was it?
Do you know
who might have stolen
A box of hairnets
from the kitchen?
Someone with hair.
I'm gonna write that down.
Sync by YesCool www.addic7ed.
Resync for 720p by Baqinardo
com www.iSubs.coil.us.to