[§§§]
Good morning, everybody.
SHlRLEY: Hi, Jeff.
I brought bagels.
Oh, I'd love a bagel.
The perfect beginning
for my first day of billiards class.
Oh. Did you pick a special outfit
so you could look sexy
shooting pool?
Shirley, I have no idea
what you are talking about.
Oh. Oh.
Thirteen.
Oh, great, so much for "baggles."
So much for what?
The "baggles."
You dropped them on the floor.
Uh, they're called "bay-gels."
Uh, I lived in New York, Troy.
I know what a "baggle" is.
[GROUP LAUGHlNG]
What the hell is wrong with you?
What?
You say "bagel" wrong.
I say it the same as you.
Say it again.
"Baggle."
[ALL LAUGHlNG
EXCEPT BRlTTA & ABED]
Can we just keep studying?
We're on page 258.
What "padge" was that?
SHlRLEY: Two-five-tee-eight. Heh.
Whoa. Check this out.
Uh-oh.
Oh, it's a drawing of Abed
with hearts all around it.
Strictly speaking, Troy, the Bible
condemns this level of friendship.
I didn't draw that.
I bought that used.
Must have been whoever had it last.
Obviously, it's a girl
who has a crush on Abed.
This is so romantic.
It's just like The Notebook, except
instead of Alzheimer's, Abed has--
Ahem. Mm-hm.
Someone who likes him.
Well, whoever she is, she's fat.
These thick pencil lines
were drawn with a heavy hand.
We gotta find this person for Abed.
Unless it's a boy,
then we find him for Jesus.
But either way,
this is going to be fun.
[SHlRLEY & ANNlE GlGGLlNG]
SHlRLEY:
Cute little face.
[GlGGLES]
[THE 88'S "AT LEAST
lT WAS HERE" PLAYlNG]
[CHANG SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH]
THEN CLASS REPEATlNG]
[CHUCKLES]
[CHANG SPEAKlNG lN SPANlSH]
THEN CLASS REPEATlNG]
Guys, class is over.
I'm trying to get you to leave.
SHlRLEY AND ABED:
Oh.
STUDENT:
Let's go.
Pick that up.
Señor Chang?
We're trying to figure out whose
Spanish book this was before Troy's.
[MOANS THEN CHANTS]
Jenny Adams.
Oh.
Oh, come on.
If all Chinese were psychic
you would have started using
birth control centuries ago.
Her name's in the front
of the book, morons.
Yay. He's right.
Them I understand.
But how did you not think of that?
I may have been thrown off
by Britta's pronunciation
of the word "bagel."
How do you pronounce bagel?
I don't.
Come on. Ugh.
"Baggle."
You're the worst.
So we have a name.
Jenny Adams.
Cool.
See, it's a fat girl's name.
Might as well be Gravy Jones.
Pierce, it doesn't matter
what she looks like.
This will be great for Abed.
It will?
Aren't you excited
about talking to her?
I wasn't planning on it.
What?
Guys, come on, you heard Abed.
He's not interested. Drop it.
Jeff, you need to mind
your own business.
Abed, you need to get with this girl,
immediately, if not sooner.
Yeah?
Abed, for guys like you,
this kind of opportunity
only comes around once in a life--
While.
It's important to date
in college, Abed.
It's a time of freedom
and exploration.
A time when a simple pillow fight
between two innocent girls
could turn to a steamy night
of unbridled lust.
Britta knows all about it.
Okay. Cool.
So you guys are gonna
Can't Buy Me Love me, right?
We're gonna what you?
You're gonna Can't Buy Me Love me.
You know, transform me
from zero to hero, geek to chic.
Oh, he wants us to
Love Don't Cost a Thing him.
Oh.
Can't Buy Me Love
was the remake
for white audiences.
That's so uncomfortable
when they do that.
I can't believe it doesn't
insult them.
All right, nobody here
is Can't Buy Me Love-ing
or Love Don't Cost a Thing-ing
anyone.
Because we've all seen enough
after-school specials
and Fat Albert to know
Oh.
that Abed only needs
to be himself.
Sure glad
there are no old people here.
This conversation
would probably be
total gibberish to them.
Jeff's unprecedentedly right
about this.
Abed, when we find this girl,
you're gonna approach her
just the way you are.
Because that's good enough.
Yeah. Then you can
take her to a nice deli
and treat her to a "baggle."
[ALL LAUGH]
[§§§]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
MAN 1 :
Oh, yeah.
MAN 2:
Hey, nice shooting.
Good clean strokes.
Thanks.
Form a line, please.
My name is Coach Bogner.
Welcome to the Art of Pool,
which is a phys ed class.
Which means that you
all have to wear
the proper equipment at all times.
So suit up.
See you back on the felt in 5.
Heh. You're gonna look
like an ass in those.
Shut up, Leonard.
I talked to your son on Family Day.
I know all about your gambling.
Touché.
All right, everybody just hang out
and be casual.
My sources tell me
that Jenny Adams is the blonde
who's reading right over there.
Whoa! That's her? She's pretty.
Which is not a surprise at all, Abed.
Okay, Abed, we're gonna be here
for moral support.
Just go over there, do your thing.
Okay.
BRlTTA: Remember, be yourself.
Got it. Cool.
BRlTTA: Great.
[CLlCKlNG TONGUE]
TROY: Abed.
Yeah?
What are you doing?
I'm being myself.
Go be yourself by Jenny.
But I wouldn't go over there.
How do you know that?
A lifetime of observation mostly.
Well, do you think there's a version
of yourself that might go over there?
Absolutely.
ANNlE: Could you be him?
Okay.
[HlSSlNG]
Oh.
What the hell was that?
A different version of me.
I think he was a vampire.
All right. If this is gonna turn ugly,
I can't be here. I'm a two-striker.
No, Pierce, please, hang on.
Abed, will you excuse us, please?
Yeah.
[§§§]
Look, I know that
we're all good people.
And good people believe
that people should be themselves.
But if Abed is himself,
he's gonna die alone.
And if we let him be someone else--
Be right back.
[HlSSlNG]
[GRUNTS]
I'm out of here.
[§§§]
MAN:
Oh, my God,
there's a midget on stilts.
[GROUP CHUCKLlNG]
[LAUGHS]
[MAN WHlSTLES]
You're not in uniform.
Yeah, about that.
We seriously have to wear shorts
to play pool?
If you play in this class.
It's regulation.
Regulation pool or regulation you?
Do you have something
against playing pool
with a full range of motion
and optimal comfort?
I'm comfortable in my own clothes.
[QUlETLY] I bet you are.
I'm sorry?
[LOUDLY] I said
I bet you're comfortable dressed
like a model instead of an athlete,
sipping martinis, smoking, instead
of keeping your game on the table.
Hey, listen, man, you're implying
I'm some sort of pool poser
because I don't wanna wear
a bathing suit.
You're the weird one.
That's weird, not me.
Nobody plays pool like that.
Yeah, what do you call this?
I call that
your personal business, okay?
And I call this class the desecration
of America's coolest sport.
Yeah. I-- See, right there. Ha.
"Coolest sport."
Okay, I want everybody to know
what's going on here.
This hipster is dropping this class
because he cares more about what
he looks like than how he's playing.
Oh, please.
You're the one with the rules
about clothes.
And, by the way,
I could kick your ass
all over that table.
Oh, is that a challenge?
Huh? Because if you play me in pool,
you play me in shorts.
And if you can't do that,
well, my point's already made.
[STAMMERlNG]
I don't have anything
to prove to you or...
Look, you're stupid. This is stupid.
Pool in shorts is stupid.
Vanity, thy name is...his name.
WOMAN: Bye.
It's the first day. I didn't catch it.
Okay, Abed, we know that, normally,
you wouldn't approach a girl.
But if you don't learn how,
you won't get Jenny.
Yeah and you got two days.
Then I'm going after her.
Pierce.
What, I'm incentivizing him.
Also, if she's into Abed, let's face it,
anybody could hit that.
I understand,
I need to change who I am
to someone more likeable.
No, no, sweetie, it's not about
changing. It's about learning.
Learning to change?
No, it's--
Good grief, clear the chickens
off the runway. I'll be the bad guy.
Yes, Abed,
you need to be someone else.
Someone who, eventually,
gets a girlfriend.
Because I can't think of anything
more frightening
than a half-Polish, half-Arab virgin
in his 30s.
One way or the other,
that story ends with an explosion.
Let's try a practice run.
All right, Annie, you sit here, okay,
and be a girl.
Abed, you take a run at her.
Let's see what you got.
Okay.
Hmm.
[lN DEEP VOlCE]
What are you reading?
Pride and Prejudice.
[SlGHS]
So you're familiar with two sins.
How about a third?
Oh.
[§§§]
I don't think
we're allowed to smoke in here.
Then you picked the wrong outfit,
didn't you?
Abed, what are you doing?
[lN NORMAL VOlCE]
Don Draper from Mad Men.
What'd you think?
Awesome.
Put your tongue in her ear.
I liked it.
Don't be him. He cheats on his wife.
Be somebody nice like Mike Brady.
He always had that housekeeper
throwing herself at him.
He never made a move on her.
Don't be Mike Brady.
Mike Brady's not sexy.
You should be like Jo
from Facts of Life.
But you know, the dude version.
I knew it.
You should be like Calvin.
His best friend was a tiger,
he always went on dope adventures.
Anything stood in his way,
he just peed on it.
Calvin Coolidge?
No, you guys.
Don Draper
was clearly the sexiest--
TROY:
And the worst thing about it,
is like that Calvin.
What are you guys doing?
They're teaching me
to be someone else.
Oh, for God's sake.
What did I tell you guys?
[lMlTATlNG JEFF]
Oh, for God's sakes, everybody,
do whatever you want.
Leave each other alone.
Whoa, that's a good Jeff.
How'd you do that?
[lN NORMAL VOlCE]
Ten percent Dick Van Dyke,
20 percent Sam Malone,
40 percent Zach Braff in Scrubs,
and 30 percent Hilary Swank
in Boys Don't Cry.
Zach Braff?
Sorry.
Abed, what if you just did Jeff
for Jenny?
[AS JEFF]
Uh-- And your point is?
Look, I don't want any part of this.
And I can't believe
tha-- That you're still doing it
after I already explained the obvious
lesson smacking you in the face.
Hey, why aren't you
in billiards class?
Because I don't look cool in shorts.
Oh!
BRlTTA: Whoa!
Okay.
Because I'm not cool in shorts.
Now that's good.
TROY: That was really good.
[§§§]
I don't wanna spoil the ending
but, uh, pride ends up
with prejudice.
That's funny.
ABED: I know.
Stick with me,
and you get a laugh or two.
That's the Abed guarantee.
I feel like I've seen you before.
It's working.
I know.
I get that a lot from art students.
I'm told I have a face
made for sketching.
I'd rather think
it was made for kissing.
How about for punching, huh?
What are you doing
hitting on my girlfriend, ugly?
[lN NORMAL VOlCE]
This is awkward.
Oh, my God.
It's a white Abed.
I-- I know. It-- It's like Abed
but employable.
Huh, boss? Let's go, Slumdog.
Oh.
PELTON:
And one last Lost and Found
announcement.
Jeff Winger, I've been informed
by Coach Bogner
that you left your panties
in his pool class
so better pick those up.
When is he gonna stop doing that?
Do you know
that he called me a hipster?
Hipster. Do hipsters walk around
wearing $300 jeans from ltaly?
Can we please talk about Abed?
Thanks to us,
his heart's been broken.
Well, I hate to say that I told you so,
so I'll shout it through cupped hands.
I told you so.
We were only trying to help.
Oh, come on, who are we kidding?
Jeff's right.
Abed was happy being Abed
till we had to sully his mind
with thoughts of love and romance
and vaginas.
Those are the big three.
That's what they call them.
Poor Abed. He was probably too sad
to get out of bed this morning.
Hi.
BRlTTA: Abed.
About yesterday--
Oh, yeah.
You guys must be pretty upset.
Why would we be upset?
Well, I know how important
it was for you that I get a girlfriend.
So when Jenny went off with
white Abed, it must have really hurt.
Ah. It did.
White Abed?
Jenny's boyfriend is a white guy
that's almost identical to Abed.
Name is Joey and that's why
the sketch was in Troy's book.
So does that make Abed
brown Joey?
If you wanna get racist about it.
Abed, you know we just want you
to be happy, right?
Yeah, I know.
Everybody wants me to be happy.
Everybody wants to help me.
But usually when they find out
they can't, they get frustrated
and stop talking to me.
Or they trick me into
buying them ice cream and then
shove me into a clothes dryer.
Which I didn't wanna happen
with you guys
so I wanted to make sure you felt
you could help.
The truth is, lots of girls like me
because, let's face it,
I'm pretty adorable.
Mm-hm.
And, uh, my aloofness unconsciously
reminds them of their fathers, so...
I'm more used to them
approaching me.
So we didn't damage
your self-esteem or anything?
Britta, I got self-esteem
falling out of my butt.
[§§§]
That's why I was willing
to change for you,
because when you really
know who you are
and what you like about yourself
changing for other people
isn't such a big deal.
Abed, you're a god.
If you'll all excuse me,
I have a man to beat in pool
while wearing shorts.
Is that code for going number one
or number two?
Abed, you've inspired me too.
People can mock me all they want.
I don't care how
I say the word "baggle."
[GROUP LAUGHlNG]
"Baggle."
She said the word "baggle."
[GROUP CHATTERlNG]
MAN:
Okay, let's play some pool.
Hey, nice cross corner, Leonard.
LEONARD: Totally. Heh-heh.
I'd like to see Jeff Winger
try that shot
without the benefit
of his stylish clothing.
Oh, would you?
Jeff Winger.
Shouldn't you be at
a Urban Outfitters?
I'll go there later if I feel like it.
But first I have to hand someone
their tightly polyester-swaddled ass
in a game of pool.
CROWD:
Ooh.
Oh, burn.
Now, do you wanna talk
about clothes like a girl?
Or use tapered sticks to hit balls
around a cushioned table
like a man?
Balls, like a man.
MAN: Oh!
Rack them.
I'll break.
Why? Because it looks cool?
I don't know.
You tell me.
[WARREN ZEVON'S
"WEREWOLVES OF LONDON"
PLAYlNG]
MAN:
Yeah.
[MAN WHlSTLES]
[CROWD CHATTERlNG]
Get out of the way.
[CROWD CHEERlNG]
Shh-shh, boom.
Yeah. Let me just clean this side
of the table off here, all right?
Oh, okay.
There you go. See that?
There you go. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. What do you think of that?
See, you haven't learned anything.
Except how to look cool
playing pool in shorts.
You're wrong, man.
I'm just having a good time
because I love playing pool.
BOGNER:
Liar.
You think you look cool.
Yeah?
Well, how cool is this?
[CROWD GASPS]
Stop projecting your obsession
with clothes onto me as an excuse
for when I beat you
in a game of real pool.
Oh, you wanna play real pool, huh?
CROWD:
Oh!
I'll play real pool.
Now who doesn't care
how they look?
Me.
Shouldn't you be stopping this?
Soon. Soon.
Just gathering evidence.
[WARREN ZEVON'S
"WEREWOLVES OF LONDON"
PLAYlNG]
Three-to-one against Winger.
Who's on?
[CROWD CHEERS]
[MUTTERS]
Oh!
Ah!
Oh.
CROWD:
Oh...
You know what, Jeff?
One of us is about to win this game.
But years from now,
when the story is retold,
all they're gonna remember
is one of us loved clothes
and the other loved...the game.
CROWD:
Ooh.
[§§§]
Aah!
[CROWD CHATTERlNG]
BOTH:
Aah!
[ALL SHOUTlNG]
[CROWD CHATTERlNG]
MAN: Oh...
WOMAN: Ooh.
CROWD:
Oh!
Ooh!
[ALL CHATTERlNG]
[§§§]
Yeah!
[CROWD CHEERlNG]
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah.
You look at me. Look at me.
You beat me.
From now on, you play pool
dressed however you choose.
I choose shorts.
Shorts.
You son of a bitch.
You magnificent son of a bitch.
[§§§]
Jeff.
That was awesome.
Let me get in here. Oh!
Okay, you're sweaty.
All right, all right.
[ALL LAUGHlNG]
Nice game.
Thanks.
Look, l-- I hope this doesn't sound
too forward.
But, um, could you introduce me
to your friend?
[§§§]
You know what? I--
I know that guy's m.o.,
and I think it's better
if you introduce yourself.
Okay.
Hi.
Courtney.
Abed.
Man, why couldn't I be Brown Joey?
Tsk.
[HUMMlNG]
Hey, Abed.
Hey Troy.
Here's the book I borrowed.
Thank you.
Did you finally get your own book?
Something like that.
Wait a second.
[CHUCKLlNG]
[MOANS]
It's okay. Let's have cookies.
Okay.
Mm. Mm.
[LAUGHS]
My cousin's funeral was today.
Oh, was that-- That was today?
I knew there was some reason
I couldn't do this today.
Poor Demitri.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org