Why is everyone
wearing those hats?
Is the dean planning
another ridiculous event,
or is the Greendale hat club
still struggling to be noteworthy?
- You're talking about it.
- I talk about lots of stuff
that annoys me.
Speaking of the dean...
Guten tag, homies.
I hope you'll all be
attending Oktoberfest.
It's not often we get to
celebrate German culture.
It's not often we want to.
Yeah... a little
goes a long way.
True.
Greendale's Oktoberfest has
never drawn huge crowds,
probably due to our diversity.
So this year,
we are adding some color!
Kick it!
I'm gonna give this to you, Troy.
"Pop and locktoberfest."
The central event will
be a pop-and-lock-a-thon.
Winner gets to annex Poland.
Kidding!
The winner gets an
iTunes gift card.
Okay.
- Oh! A break-dance contest.
What should we name our team?
Okay. I'm gonna go
hang myself in my closet.
I'm comin' with.
Is it me, or is this campus
getting more cartoonish every day?
Yep. It's exciting.
I painted a tunnel on
the side of the library.
When it dries, I'm going for it.
Okay. You see
that guy over there?
The one wearing the Gucci suit
and the lightweight
woven wool-mohair blend?
We used to work together.
Cool. So he's from your origins.
This is all I need.
Excuse me, sir.
You're all my friend needs.
Your mouth isn't curved upwards.
Did I misread something?
Ah...Tango?
Sundance. We worked with
different partners. - Got it.
- Ha ha!
- Hey...
What brings you to Greendale?
I'm a teacher.
Wait. That's worse than the truth.
I'm a student.
Hey, I'm in no
position to judge.
I'm here for an
N.A. Meeting, so...
- Narcotics anonymous?
- Remember when you asked
for my secret, I said yoga?
I lied.
I'm Abed. - Hey.
Abed, this is Alan Connor.
This guy and I
used to wipe the courtroom
floor with prosecutors.
D.A. called us the litterbugs,
we put so much trash back
out on those streets.
Come here, come here!
You still ticklish? - Stop that!
Hey, hey, hey.
Let's get a drink, huh?
- Are you allowed?
- Yeah. I quit doing blow,
not being rad.
All right, let's do it.
Wait. Jeff can't go.
He has class.
Well, those cargo pants
would suggest otherwise.
What has this place done to you?
Ah. You have no idea.
Hat club!
Now you have some idea.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
So...
So?
Anyone that's ever been in
a team pop-and-lock-a-thon
knows you need at least seven
people to stand a chance.
- We have seven.
- Oh, do you?
Word has it on campus
that Winger's too busy
hanging out with his
cool new lawyer friend.
Ha. Slow news day.
That's your Carson?
Jon Stewart.
- You depress me.
- Look, we'll get back to you.
All right, well,
don't take too long.
And don't rip off this exit.
Shoom, shoom.
- Where is Jeff?
- Obviously hanging with Alan.
Those two are like siamese twins
attached at the
cell phone holster.
I haven't met him yet.
Shouldn't we be happy that
Jeff found an old friend?
Our concern is
that Alan is to Jeff
what Rob Lowe was to James Spader
in the 1990 film bad influence.
He's a bad influence.
You saw it?
Hey, uh, guys.
Uh, I'm gonna be a
little bit late today.
Alan and I are gonna
take a quick sidebar.
Mmm, or any bar.
Oh, he's got Britta down!
- You look familiar.
- That's possible.
Have you or someone you
know been injured at work?
Oh!
Yes! A shrimp boat
ran over my cousin.
That's serious. Call me.
And, Jeff, you need to be
more respectful of our time.
Shirley, if killed a man,
as a Christian,
would you forgive me?
I would.
Then either that man's life
is worth less than your time,
or it's okay for me to be late.
Ha ha! No!
You still got the moves, man.
If they gave away
awards for mind games,
the statue'd be Jeff
Winger doing it to a brain.
Come on, Jeff's bush league.
I gave seminars on manipulation.
I could reach into a man's soul
and unravel it with one tug.
Cool. Hit me.
You're bald.
- So are you.
I'll kill you, you...
Come here!
- Mistrial.
Ha ha ha! Come on.
I have hair.
Father, I have hair.
On a tax evasion case.
Yeah.
God, I miss talking
about this stuff!
Well, you should
visit the office.
Right. I can't
show my face there
after getting busted like that.
Jeff, you know what
lawyers call someone
who defrauds the state bar,
cheats on his SATs,
and cons his way into a firm?
Best...Lawyer...Ever.
Seriously?
Hey, tomorrow night.
Office party.
You're my guest.
Oh. Naw.
Come on, you just
said you missed it.
I do.
I really, really do.
What does Alan
have that we don't?
A butt for Jeff's Weiner.
I mean, we all have butts too.
We have butts.
Just not for the same thi...
I'm trying to say they're gay.
Well, I don't like how much
drinking and carousing they do.
It's a gateway to narcotics.
Narcotics! I know how I know Alan!
But I'm not allowed to say.
Which means that you met
him in narcotics anonymous.
Why bring it up if
you're not allowed?
Because...He said
something at a meeting
about something bad he did. - Oh.
And he might have
done it to Jeff,
but I can't say what it is.
Okay. You've gone from
precious to annoying.
What if you don't say
it out loud but we guess?
- Like charades?
- With this group?
I'm watching.
Four words.
- "Alan got Jeff disbarred."
- Uh...
Oh, please, those junkies
weren't thinking about rules
when they were shooting up scag.
- Jeff, Alan narced on you!
- Narced?
Hmm. But he's like way
too primo for that,
Frank Zappa.
I think he turned you
in to the state bar.
I was in an N.A.
meeting, and he bragged about it.
He doesn't recognize me,
because my hair's longer,
my skin's clearer, I...
I've lost a lot of weight.
Annie.
He said he turned me in?
He said he sent an email
that got a rival coworker fired.
It was around the
time you got caught.
I know they never covered
this on yo, gabba gabba,
but that's called circumstantial.
Any other meaningless
conspiracy theories?
Yes. Did you know that
go-gurt is just yogurt?
You know what a therapist
calls this kind of a
relationship, right?
A gold mine.
Codependent.
You guys don't want
me to be happy.
You want me to need you.
It's getting a little
claustrophobic.
I used to run full-speed
through the boundless wilderness,
and now I'm in the zoo
where the horizon is wallpaper
and the air is stale
and nothing is ever at stake.
In other words, we're not cool.
I never said that.
You may have heard it.
I may have thought it,
and it may be true.
But I never said it.
Jeff, will we see you
tomorrow night at the
pop-and-lock-a-thon?
No, Abed,
I'm going to a cool party
at my cool former law firm
from when my life was cool.
Fine. You can be on the team.
New deal.
If we win, I get to
be in the study group.
The stakes have
never been higher.
I just wanna thank
everybody for coming.
You know, when I became a lawyer,
I had a dream.
I had a dream that one
day I'd be head of a firm
so nobody would be able to talk
about the big,
weird hole in my hand.
I know everybody talks
about it behind my back,
and that's okay.
You know, I would.
What's great, though,
is that you don't stare
or ask any questions.
And as a reward for
your restraint,
got a little something for ya.
There.
That oughta keep you
goin' to Christmas.
Everybody have fun tonight!
Anyone else with that
hand would wear a glove.
He controls a room with it.
He's the master.
Well, he sure is a fan of yours.
Oh, um...
Hey, when you talk to him,
will you mention me?
He keeps passing me
over for partner.
Alan, did you invite me
here with an ulterior motive?
God, I miss this place!
God, it's a sea of Wingers.
This whole place reeks
of moral ambiguity.
Actually, that was me.
I apologize.
Now, you guys are
new to high society,
so just... follow my lead,
everything will be fine.
First, why are you here?
Second, I don't care. Leave.
As a matter of fact,
Jeff, we were invited.
Why would anyone do that?
Hey, you guys made it!
Come on in.
Okay, before this
gets more embarrassing,
what is your misguided plan?
To apologize to you
for casting aspersions
on your friend.
And to show you we can be cool.
Hey! Is that Jeff Winger?
Find Annie and leave.
Ted! Hey, man!
- What's goin' on?
- Wow!
Once Annie gets
Alan's office number,
you guys break into his office,
hack into his emails,
and find proof that
he screwed Jeff over.
Fourth floor. 470.
First he said it was 69.
I wanna rub purell on my brain.
You are so missed here, Jeff.
If we had five guys around
here with your balls,
we wouldn't need 30 lawyers.
True. But we'd
need a good doctor.
Ted, stop hittin' on my date.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
I'm kidding. We can share.
I get the head!
I love the brain in there! Arr,
arr, arr, arr!
I'll eat it.
Hey, everybody,
Jeff Winger's here!
Hey!
Shouldn't we notify someone
that our team's not gonna make
it to the pop-and-lock-a-thon?
You actually think
anybody cares?
Um, checking in for the
Heather pop and locklears.
Okay. And, um...
Where's the rest of your team?
Oh, they'll be here.
I suppose you're allowed
to start by yourself,
but you won't stand a chance
if you don't have someone...
they'll be here!
I brought stuff
people use for capers.
Suction cup.
Credit card.
Chloroform.
The credit card doesn't work,
the chloroform does.
Annie, go back and keep lookout.
Why me lookout?
Why not you guys?
'Cause if someone comes up here,
Kanye and Kumar get taken to jail.
You get taken to dinner.
You guys!
I am the smartest one
in this whole group,
and all I've been used for
is bait and distraction.
Ohh!
Go on your stupid mission.
I hope it sucks.
- What did she say?
- I don't know.
All I heard was suck.
I'm surprised that Alan
hasn't made partner yet.
I'm surprised I
haven't fired him.
Why? I mean, he's got a
better win record than I do.
He's a spineless
trust fund jagoff.
I'll tell you what, Jeff.
You're the best liar
I ever employed.
If you can look me in the eye
and tell me you
actually like Alan,
I'll make him a full partner.
Well, I only ever
really liked one person.
My mom.
And she liked my dad.
And after all the dust
and custody was settled,
the guy I really admired-
not liked, admired...
was the lawyer leaving
the courthouse
in the great-looking suit
and a sky blue Mercedes SLK.
- Sweet ride.
- Sweet job.
Sweet life. He didn't care.
He couldn't care.
And the less he cared,
the better he was.
We are a special breed
because we rise above
the sloppy stuff
and look at the bottom line.
You wanna like your employees?
Open a hair salon.
You wanna win? Make Alan partner.
The student has
become the master.
Thank you, Jeff.
You make me wanna be a worse man.
By the way, just 'cause
you can't work cases here
doesn't mean you can't work.
You can always be a consultant.
Ted...That would be amazing.
Oh. I'll be right back.
I didn't know they had rules.
Hey, Jeff.
I'm sure you know Phillip.
Did you know that if I sleep
with Philip once a month,
I can use his beach house
in Rio whenever I want?
Wow.
You guys are really
on to something.
I think you found the
world's newest profession.
Guys, guys, did you know I
actually have a civil case
against that bitch
that stole my husband?
Shirley, don't sue a stripper.
- Why not?
- She's a stripper.
Life sued her, and she lost.
Where's Pierce?
Jeez, why am I even
worried about him?
Hey.
Did you know there's
an island in Indonesia
where you can hunt people?
We need to talk.
I think this is it.
Abed: Print it.
'Scuse me.
Who are you guys?
This is not your office.
I can explain.
Let me explain.
Oh, my God!
- I didn't know what to do.
- Oh, my God!
I usually have one
foot out of reality,
and even I'm freaking
out right now.
You chloroformed the janitor?
Stop yelling at me!
You're the ones that got caught!
You're the one who's yelling!
We're in big trouble!
We have to do something!
Oh, I don't know what to do.
My whole brain is crying!
Oh! Oh oh oh!
Guys, guys, guys!
Hey, hey, I have an idea.
Okay, it may sound a
little weird, but trust me.
What's...Happening?
Oh! We all got chloroformed!
Somebody chloroformed all of us.
And now we're
regaining consciousness
together.
I don't understand. Who's she?
Why is she holding a rag?
Okay, that was the
worst idea ever.
Can we please just run away now?
- Yeah.
It is the fourth straight hour,
and Ben Chang is still on his own.
One can only imagine
what is driving him to...
Push himself to such limits!
My body hurts.
You jealous because
we're fitting in
with your cool friends?
No. I'm distracted,
watching you mutate.
Britta, you're not a whore.
Shirley, Jesus turned
the other cheek.
He didn't garnish wages.
Pierce, do I even
need to say this?
It is bad to hunt man for sport.
Bad ass.
This is the email that Alan
sent the bar association.
He stabbed you in the back, Jeff.
He's a bad friend.
You're right.
He is a bad friend.
But he is a good lawyer.
Now, I appreciate
you guys caring,
but you have to
understand that I don't.
Caring is lethal around here.
It's... it's a disease.
You guys have it. I don't.
So if you do care about me,
don't infect me.
Now,
go win that pop-and-lock-a-thon.
I'll see you Monday.
It's like watching a soul
slip through our fingers.
But what more can we do?
Would you stop?
Tango!
I don't know how
you did it, man...
But you're looking at
the firm's next partner.
If I wasn't actively
repressing my bi-curiosity,
I would kiss you full
on your beautiful mouth.
Well, maybe you can
return the favor one day.
Maybe...I can
return it right now.
You probably know
that it was someone here at
the firm who turned you in.
God, this is really hard.
Alan... it's okay.
You can tell me.
It was Thompson.
- Thompson.
- Yeah.
Thompson that adopted
three at-risk teens
and donated his kidney to a temp.
- All an act.
- Mm.
Yeah. Why do you think he
quit right after you left?
Well, his... his wife died.
Did she...Jeff?
Did...She?
Anyway...Congrats.
Hey, let's go do some
shots with Phil, huh?
No, you go ahead. I, uh...
I think I caught something...
At... at Greendale.
College chicks. I get ya!
You're bad!
It hurts!
Shamone...It hurts!
Ben, you need to
switch up your moves.
Ohh...
***
- oh!
- Oh, my God!
Only two teams left.
The poppy lockstockings,
and the Heather pop and locklears!
- Troy, what's wrong?
- I don't know.
My heart's just not in it.
Maybe we should quit.
I mean, who even cares
about this anyway?
***
- oh, Jeffrey, you're back!
- Oh!
- Did you miss me?
- Took you long enough.
Oh!
Now we got it.
Hey! - Yes!
Jeffrey, did you punch
Alan in his rotten face
and then storm out? - Hell, no.
That guy's useful to me.
Thanks to you,
I've now got leverage
over a spineless jag
that just made partner.
That is the place I want to work.
But I prefer to hang
out with cool people,
people so cool... they care.
Oh!
And now...The puppet.
Jeffrey!
Ah, no parking on the
dance floor, Winger.
No, I'm serious.
You're disqualified.
The winners are the
poppy lockstockings!
Noooooo!
I been popping and locking
for five hours,
and you threw it all away!
The contest doesn't matter.
What's important is
we have each other.
Then...Can I be
in your study group?
Well, that wasn't the deal.
We lost, so...
That was dope, what we did.
That was so good!
The puppet too!
The puppet was so...
I rolled my ankle during that.
- Aw!
- Twisted it?
It was worth it, though.
You know what,
he's bringing us down.
Let's move him. Can we move him?
Psst! Troy!
It's me.
Abed?
I made it through!
I'm a cartoon now.
That's impossible.
Nothing's impossible in here.
Animals can talk.
Your heart is shaped like a heart.
And the smell of pie
can make you float.
You have to believe, Troy.
Wait! You don't have to believe.
I didn't.
I may have done
some damage there.
Sync by YYeTs.net
www.addic7ed.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org