All: ♪ to you ♪
[horns tooting]
- That was weird--how come
we only sang the last two words?
What happened
to the happy birthday part?
- Well, you know troy's
a jehovah's witness.
- He doesn't celebrate
birthdays.
- Annie and I did our best
To keep the language
on the cake compliant.
- "hello during
a random dessert,
"the month and day of which
cocide numerically
With your expulsion
from a uterus."
Yoguys,
I never cry, but...
- All right.
Happy expulsion, troy,
But after cake,
we cram for realsies.
Guys, finals are coming up.
- Yeah. This group is starting
to use special occasions
To avoid studying.
Last week we had fondue
and played boggle
Because shirley's niece
took her first bath.
- With bubbles.
- Thank you. It's a milestone.
- Funny, because last week
was my birthday,
And nobody noticed
and nobody cared.
- Pierce...
You don't remember
the huge party we threw?
We need to talk about
those pain killers you're taking
Because don't think
you're remembering anything.
- That was a huge party.
[overlapping chatter]
- It was the best party
of my life!
- Gotcha!
[chattering stops]
[chuckles] of course
I remember my birthday.
What a party.
[clicks tongue]
- Yeah, you still owe me
for the cake deposit.
- Oh, you think
I don't know that?
- Troy...
- Troy.
- ♪ give me some rope,
time in a tree ♪
♪ give me the hope
to run out of steam ♪
♪ somebody said
we could be here ♪
♪ we could be roped up,
tied up, dead in a year ♪
♪ I can't count the reasons
I should stay ♪
♪ one by one they all
just fade away ♪
Synced By YesCool
www.addic7ed.com
- Kick puncher: Detroit!
No way!
This is sold out everywhere!
- Not everywhere.
I got a cousin in detroit.
They're not crazy about it
up there.
- This is how you turn 20.
Thanks!
- Ooh, there's strawberries
under there.
- Here, let me, uh,
help you with that.
- I broke my legs,
not my gender.
- Okay.
- Whilwe're...
Watching this unfold,
Some birthday facts
to enjoy.
Troy's birthday is tomorrow,
December 4th.
Also born that day,
tyra banks...
- Ugh.
- Marisa tomei...
And french cinematographer
claude renoir.
- [whispers]
yes! Jackpot!
- On the chinese calendar,
troy is a horse.
Like me.
"purposeful, self-possessed,
and gregarious."
- No. I'm pretty sure
I'm a snake.
I remember because
I'm determined, self-possessed,
And mendacious.
- Pierce, what is this?
What are you doing?
Explain yourself.
- Who made this
crappy cake anyway?
- A cake maker.
At a cake store.
- They did it wrong.
- Troy, we're 1990.
We're horses.
- I was born in '89.
- Then...
You were born 21 years ago.
- Which would make me 20,
Because everyone
is 10 for two years.
Because fifth grade
is really hard for every...One.
[yelling] mom, how many lies
have I been living!
- Troy, do you realize
at midnight you are turning 21
As in
"the legal drinking age"?
- Whoa!
- This party just became
unacceptable--we're going out.
- Yep!
- But you guys were just
Complaining about us having
too many parties.
- Too many lame ones.
This is real.
- Well, what makes it real?
- Well, shirley, think of it
As troy
taking his first bath,
Only the bubbles
are his manhood.
- Yes. I wanna bathe
in manhood.
Together: Oh!
- I'm taking you to l street.
- [scoffs]
douche street.
- Oh, of course
you hate cool bars.
I don't suppose you've
ever even been to l street.
- No. But I also haven't been
to beirut.
But I'm sure
I will go one day,
Because I hear they have
lots of important cultural--
[groaning,
overlapping comments]
Unlike l street,
which is douchey.
- All right, let's hear
your great suggestions.
- The red door.
- Oh, yeah, the red door!
The red hipster.
- Not hipster.
Hipsters haven't
discovered it yet.
It's underound.
- Why don't we go someplace
fun like peg leg pablo's?
They serve virgin mudslides.
- Those are milk shakes,
shirley.
- You guys! All you
think about is yourselves.
Think about me. I'm 19.
I can't get into bars.
- Well...
- [fakes crying]
- Yeah, sorry.
- Okay, well...
Have fun.
- [sighs]
Fine.
I'll get annie an I.D.
- A fake I.D.?
- It will be real.
It just won't be yours.
I will see you
at the red door.
- Nice try. We're not going
to red poet's society.
- Well, we're not going
to douche street either.
- Fine. Count of three,
name the least offensive bar
You've ever been to.
One, two, three.
Together:
Flannahan's hole.
Done.
Troy, you ride with me?
- Do you even have to ask?
- Pierce, do you wanna
ride in my van?
- I'm not a disabled.
I don't need people
helping me
Do normal things
and doting over me...
Why don't you just leave--
Okay!
I'll beat you there.
- I don't think this girl
looks very much like me.
- Come on.
She's a white brunette.
- So is anne hathaway.
- Go on?
- What's your friend doing
With a stack
of other people's I.D.S?
- I don't know--
sometimes people sell their I.D.
When they're leaving the state
and need cash.
- So she's a drifter.
A floater.
An urchin.
Caroline decker
from corpus christi, texas.
Texas?
Do I need an accent?
- You don't need an accent.
- Howdy, y'all.
I'm caroline decker.
- Please don't do that.
- I guar-un-tee!
- That's cajun.
- [giggles] cajun.
- I should research
corpus christi.
- Annie, relax.
I'm not a relaxed person,
britta.
I think ahead.
I prepare.
I don't improvise my life
like...Caroline decker,
Who probably has
really bad credit
And an unfinished
mermaid tattoo.
[cell phone rings]
- What?
- Flannahan's hole is closed.
That's not a--
I-I'm not being clever.
I mean it's out of business.
- Well, that's what they get
for trying to please everyone.
So now what?
- Well, there's a place
At third and water.
It's fun, divey,
but not staph infection divey.
It's either got a gross name
or an ironically fancy one.
Possibly both.
- Oh. The ballroom. Good.
- Go to third and water.
- Wait--what?
That wasn't the deal!
- Shirley's pushing back.
- Why, because they don't have
plastic menus and milk shakes?
- Why, because they don't--
- don't repeat that, you goon!
Jeez. Look, just--
the women are your problem,
And the men
are going to the ballroom.
And now I guess I am
being clever.
[muzak playing]
- So...Plastic menus
are bad?
See, this is the kinda stuff
I need to learn.
Plastic menus seems like
a great idea to me
For when you spill
something on them,
And then your mom says,
"hey, troy,
You're ruining fuddruckers
for everyone."
- Troy...You're entering
the next chapter of your life.
Sadly, it's the final chapter,
But it's also the longest.
And if you play it right,
the best.
You and I...
We're just two guys now.
Peers. Equals.
- So awesome.
Maybe later
you'll let me drive your car.
- [chuckles]
[both laughing]
[laughter]
- Hello, former enemy.
- He's 21 at midnight.
Cool?
- Yeah. Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
- Uh, I-I don't like
this place.
- Ugh. You made that clear,
shirley. Oy vey.
- Caroline decker
from corpus christi.
- Annie,
you don't need an accent.
- If my I.D. Says texas,
they'll be suspicious.
- They're not gonna question
your I.D.
Because you're a hot girl.
We're good for business.
The hotter you are,
The more they'll risk the fine.
- Howdy?
- Go ahead.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Can't be too careful.
- I understand.
Hey, hey, shirley!
Welcome back!
- You don't know me.
Hmm?
Okay?
- [quietly]
yeah.
- You don't...Know me.
- This place is all right!
- Yeah. It's okay.
- These pictures must be
of all the regulars.
You think someday I can
make it up to this wall?
- I don't say this often,
troy, but...
Dream a little smaller.
- Can I get you guys anything?
- Oh!
I-I'm okay!
- Another macallan. Neat.
- Vodka. Neat. Four olives.
- I'm waiting till midnight.
All: Aw!
- Sweetie?
- Water!
- Oh, where's that
accent from?
- Corpus christi.
Texas.
78418.
- What are you doin'
here in town?
- Not much, I reckon...
Just driftin', floatin',
Spittin' in the wind.
General waywardness.
- All righty.
- Annie, you're in the bar.
You don't have to be
from texas anymore.
- I don't know how it works.
I'm not a barfly, britta.
- They have asteroids.
Slide out.
- O-okay.
Oh! Oh! Okay.
I-I'm gonna go take
a little look around.
- Me too.
- Annie.
Don't accept any drinks.
- Or invitations
to the bathroom.
- So what are you gonna order
for your first legal drink?
- What should I get?
- Whatever you want.
- No wrong answers.
- I like beer.
- Don't order beer.
- You've had beer.
- W-what should I get?
- Well, what do you think
you might like?
I mean,
it's your world now.
- Follow your heart.
- My uncle carl
Played a big role in my life.
He taught me
how to throw a football.
He...He passed away
this year.
His favorite drink
was a seven and seven.
- Don't order that.
- That's an awful drink.
- You're better than that.
- That's a high school drink
for girls.
- Actually,
I'll have a root beer
Instead of that water.
- Sure thing.
- Thank you kindly.
Y'all are so nice
in this town.
I'm caroline.
From corpus christi.
Grew up on a trout farm.
Deedly-do.
♪ doo doo doo doo ♪
- Oh, careful.
You score any higher
on this thing,
The rylans
are gonna recruit you
To fight against
the ko-dan empire.
- The last starfighter.
Did you get
the 25th anniversary blu-ray?
- Was scorpius half-scarran,
half-peacekeeper?
Frell, yes, I got starfighter
on blu-ray.
- You're a fan of the sci-fi
original series farscape.
- Can I buy you a drink?
- You got some id?
- Very funny, punk.
Get outta my way!
[muttering]
people trying to--
I don't know how people like you
even get jobs today.
- Hey, do you need help, man?
- Oh...
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Ha ha!
A little turning
of the tables.
Ha.
- The turning
of what tables?
- I don't know!
Leave me alone!
[blows into tube]
pffttt!
[bang]
[crash, bang]
- [exaggerated accent
so I punched her
Right in the face.
- Your probation officer?
Didn't you get in trouble?
- Hell, yes,
I got in trouble!
Wasn't the first time.
Won't be the last.
I'm not exactly known for
my sound judgment.
Back in corpus christi, they
call me capricious caroline.
- What's capricious mean?
- Probably means I'm...
Too busy livin' life
to be learnin' $5-words.
Ha ha!
Hot damn!
- With an aged scotch,
never use ice.
- Never use ice.
Got it.
Why?
- Destroys it.
At most, what you want--
two drops of spring water.
Activates the flavor.
- Good lord.
Do they have the rules to
high-maintenance poser drinker
On the wall at l street?
- Do they?
- Poser drinking?
Hey, miss vodka,
need four olives.
What's that called,
the too-cool-to-care-tini?
- Is it?
- I bet the forced
starkness of that drink order
Turns a lotta horn-rimmed heads
at the red door.
- I can't wait to understand
these arguments!
- Hey, y'all,
'nother round for ya.
Everybody holdin' up?
I'll be back in two shakes
of a rabbit's ass.
- Who the hell was that?
- I gotta go see a woman
About the female equivalent
of a horse.
- Classy.
Way to show troy the ropes.
- Shut up, l street.
- That woman is a hurricane.
- Yeah.
- Hurricanes are bad, troy.
- I know.
- I always thought it's possible
That the wormhole
crichton fell through
Moved him across not only space
but also time,
Which would suggest that the
sebaceans are our future selves
And crichton is longing for
a planet that no longer exists.
- Ha. Hey, you're really
nursing that beer.
- Ahh. Which would make sense,
Because what kind of
wormhole would it be
If it could only move
from one place to another
Within the same galaxy
on the same day?
- You know,
speaking of wormholes,
Uh, whaddaya say
we use one to...
Teleport this conversation
someplace a little more private?
- That doesn't make any sense.
Wormholes and teleportation
are two different things.
That's what I've been talking
about this whole time.
- I noticed.
- Cheers.
- I followed that band phish--
spells it with "ph".
I just lived in parking lots
wherever they played.
I don't even like their music.
Just did it to see
if I could do it.
And guess what.
I could!
- So what now?
- I dunno!
Even if I planned it,
plans just fall off me
Like chicken crap
off an armadilla.
[chuckles] annie's the one
that plans things, not me.
Annie's my friend.
She goes to school here.
Thinks she's got it
all figured out.
She wants to major
in healthcare management.
What does that even mean?
- No idea.
- I'll tell you what it means.
It means a master's degree
followed by an internship.
She's got the next
15 years of her life
All mapped out,
and all she gotta do now
Is just follow it
or screw it up.
- Another soda?
- Actually,
gimme a screwdriver.
I got no place to be.
What am I...Annie?
- The first season, when you
watch it the second time,
Is better than the third season,
and the fourth season,
When you watch it
the fifth time--
- Okay. Um...
What's your name?
- Abed.
- Abed, I'm robert.
- Hey, robert.
- Abed, would you
like to have...
Gay sex...With me?
- No, thank you.
- Wow.
Okay, so...
What is wrong with you
That you can sit here
this whole time
And never pick up on the fact
that a man is hitting on you?
- Oh, I actually did pick up
on it after a while.
- You actually--
And?
- I really, really like
talking about farscape.
It's a really good show.
- Stargate's better.
[blowing]
Electronic voice:
Battery depleted.
- Oh, man.
Aw...
[laughter]
- that is wrong!
Wait.
- Oh!
- Hey, there!
What you been up to?
- I was just, uh,
Praying for these poor souls
in these photographs.
- Oh, that's nice, but, uh...
You missed one.
I found it
in the ladies room.
- Uh...Give that to me?
- No, no, come on!
Don't feel bad.
This makes us like you
way more.
- You think
this is really funny.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, a little.
- I had some bad years.
With a chaser.
- Come on.
It's a funny picture,
Because you act so perfect
all the time.
And because
you look like a zombie,
But it's not funny
when you're sad.
We're on your team.
Relax.
Sit down.
It's my birthday.
- Give it to me.
Give it to me.
See you all on Monday.
- Sheesh.
- Oh...
Britta: Blue town.
Jeff: Shirley. Wait.
- What?
- Nothing.
Get out of my way!
- I can't get out
of your way.
I'm stuck in this pl--
the chair broke--
I mean, I can't get--
Could you p-please help me?
Pretty please?
Thank you, shirley.
- You're welcome, jackass.
- Hey, um, it's my birthday,
And technically,
I'm not allowed to drink
For another 45 seconds.
Well, actually,
it'll be 30 seconds
By the time I'm done
saying this.
But can I have
a seven and seven?
- It's on the house.
Happy birthday, kid.
Britta:
I prefer that to avatar.
I'd rather have my eyes
gouged out.
Jeff: Imagine the hurt locker
as radio play.
Britta: It would be fascinating
and thrilling!
Jeff: Go see the other play!
- Big boy.
Big, big boy.
You're my big boy.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
- Troy.
I think I owe you
a birthday.
- I'm cool.
I actually always wanted
to drive this thing.
- What?
Oh.
This is my car?
Don't crash it.
- I'm not gonna crash it!
- [slurring]
crash it, troy.
- Go to sleep, britta.
Go to sleep.
- Crash his car, troy!
- Seems like a really dark
chapter in our group story.
- Go to sleep, abed.
- Cool.
- [gasps]
hey, that's the place
That we shoulda
gone to tonight!
- Yeah, l street.
Exactly.
- It's the red door, stupid!
You see a sign
that says l street?
- L street is too cool
to have a sign.
It's called l street
after the street it's on.
- [laughs]
The red door's on l street.
- L street has a red door.
[both laughing]
[brakes screech]
- Aah!
- Hey!
- It's the same bar?
You two have been saying
one bar is lame
And the other one is awesome
all night...
And it's the same bar?
- Well, he probably was
around Friday nights,
Which was lame.
- You wish!
- Stop. Just stop.
I just spent the last two years
Thinking that you guys
knew more than me about life,
And I just found out that you
guys are just as dumb as me.
- Duh-doy.
- Yeah. Duh-doy.
- Got it.
Duh-doy.
- You can take me home first.
I only live
a few blocks from here.
- You do?
- Hey, this is a really
terrible neighborhood.
- Yeah.
- This is my apartment.
Weird night, huh?
- Yeah. Alcohol
makes people sad.
It's like the lifetime movies
of beverages.
- I pretended to be
a different person tonight.
- Abed does that
like three times a week.
- But I did it because
I didn't wanna be me.
I-I did it because
I'm not sure who I am.
Admit it--we went to school
together for four years,
And you didn't even
know me.
- Yeah, but...
I know you now.
You're annie.
You like puzzles and...
Little monsters
on your pencil
And some guy
named mark ruffalo.
You're a fierce competitor
and a sore loser.
And you expect everybody
to be better than who they are
And you expect yourself
to be better than everyone.
Which is cool.
[laughs]
Good night.
- Guess everyone's gonna be
pretty embarrassed
On Monday, huh?
- Naw. Everybody
just got a little bit drunk.
Nobody did anything
that bad, right?
- [slurring]
no, wait, wait, wait.
What are we doing?
- Yeah. What are we doing?
- This is a bad idea,
right?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I flew off the handle
earlier.
I apologize.
- They were making out.
- Abed!
- Abed, why would you say that?
- Why would you do it
in front of me?
I'm not a coat rack.
- Abed.
- Mm-hmm.
- No one likes a tattle tail.
- Happy birthday, troy.
- Thanks.
- You're a man now.
- I don't think
this is gonna be big enough.
- Just try it--we're so close!
- All right. Breathe in.
- [inhales]
- All right.
- [gasps]
- Arms.
There we go.
There we go, yeah.
- Ah!
[panting]
- 157!
- We did it!
- Yes.
[cell phone rings]
That you?
- Yeah.
[ringing]
little help?
Hurry.
I think it's a girl!
- Left side or right side?
- Left side.
- Got it.
Tell me when I'm clo.
- Okay.
Synced by YesCool
www.addic7ed.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org