By the end of WWII President Roosevelt
had finally succumbed
to the polio
that afflicted him
his entire life.
Which brings me to
the Yalta Conference.
Who can tell me three
key points brought up there?
Annie.
The demilitarization
of Germany--
I'm sorry.
Annie Kim.
The demilitarization
of Germany,
the establishment
of Poland's borders
and the formation of
the United Nations.
Side note: The results
of Yalta would later
set the stage for the Cold War.
Oh, boy, spoiler alert.
Somebody just won
a ride in the wheelchair.
I'm proud of you
for deciding on a major, Britta.
I'd like to thank the lord
in my prayers about you,
but you're still dressing
like a streetwalker.
Yep, I'm getting serious.
I got a backpack,
I got a new notebook.
Oh, I got one of
those see-through yellow pens
so I can do that thing
where you color in the words.
Highlight?
Probably the backpack.
Free the damascus three.
Oh, thanks.
Oh, whoa.
I know this girl.
We used to protest together
all the time
and now she's locked up
in Syria.
Oh, that's terrible.
Yes, it's terrible.
She's imprisoned
by an oppressive regime
halfway around the world
and I'm, what?
In college?
Where are my values?
Man, she's got
a Facebook group?
My first cop flashlight.
Can't wait to get some brains
on this bad boy.
Are you safe, ma'am?
Everything okay?
Is this guy bothering you?
- Huh? Huh?
- Hey!
Who the hell
do you think you are?
The badge says
to serve and protect!
No, it doesn't.
"How's my smile?"
Oh, man.
What the hell am I
in charge of?
See this garbage can?
Students coming out
of the library bump into it.
You can serve and protect them
from a nasty boo-boo.
What do I do if I see a crime?
What a security guard does--
Call a cop.
Where'd you even get these?
- Come on, let me keep them.
- No.
Please?
I swear they're just for sex!
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
♪ We could be roped up,
tied up, dead in a year ♪
♪ I can't count the reasons
I should stay ♪
♪ one by one they all
just fade away ♪
And this ragtag group
of cut-ups is my study group.
Gang, this is Annie Kim
from my Poli-Sci class.
We just figured out we had
the same G.P.A. in high school.
Well, mine was higher if you
consider my school's ranking.
Well, it sounds like you had
a lighter course load, so.
Well, I was in a lot of clubs.
I founded 17 of them.
Well, I was actually thinking
about founding a model U.N.
here at Greendale.
Any interest?
I'll probably be busy,
and you probably need to study,
so see you in class.
Okay, goodbye.
Wow, Annie.
How progressive of you to have
a multicultural evil twin.
An Asian Annie.
Obama's America.
Her name is Annie Kim,
and she's not evil.
She's my friend.
Didn't look like it.
Yeah, you seemed pretty
competitive with her.
You be careful, Annie.
They are ruthless.
What?
What? Not Asians.
Women.
I'm not competing with her.
I find her adorable.
She's like a younger me.
You mean the younger you
that took so much Adderall
she tried to straighten
the lines on our high school
football field during a game?
Ooh, be careful, Annie.
You don't want this little girl
to suck you back
to the dark side.
Hey, guys,
what're you trying to do here?
This is our Annie.
That little twerp
is a can of Annie lite.
She couldn't hold a candle
to the real thing
in any category of anything.
Aw, well, I wasn't
fishing for that.
You're the best, kiddo.
You know what else
was the best?
The rainforests.
Too bad the fascist oligarchies
are raping them
to make hamburgers.
Look it up.
Looks like someone woke up
on the regular side of the bed.
Britta's just having
a rough time
because her friend's in prison.
I went to her Facebook page.
It says she was tear-gassed
and possibly beaten.
I haven't been tear-gassed
in so long.
Well, you're on a new path now.
Oh, goody, a new path.
Is it lined with credit cards
and flat screen TVs?
Does it go by an Ikea?
Maybe I don't want a new path!
Or any path.
Maybe my path is a war path
that leads
to the terrordome, n-words!
Okay, maybe I went too far.
Maybe I don't want to offend
my African-American friends,
but the larger point is,
maybe I'm not done
raging against the machine.
Raging against the what?
That sounds dangerous.
Don't worry.
She'll be bad at it.
Keep clear of the can.
Sir, step around the can.
Mind the can, student.
♪ Hello ♪
♪ is it me you're looking for ♪
♪ I can see it in your eyes ♪
You just got yourself
a warning.
I piss warnings, pig.
♪ You're all
I ever wanted... ♪
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
And that's how we do that.
Hey!
I got my eye on you, missy.
Hi.
You okay, kiddo?
Yeah, yeah.
You know what's funny?
This is so silly.
Remember little Annie Kim
from Poli-Sci?
Boy, she just...
took my model U.N. idea
and just...
She is quite
the little go-getter.
Wait, what?
She stole your idea?
Sneak attack.
That's just like--
Not women, Asians.
Well, the real important thing
is that there is a model U.N.
It doesn't really matter
who starts it.
It just means her name
goes on some charter
and she gets to put it
on her résumé.
And lead the Greendale team
to the national model U.N.,
and meet Kofi Annan, Boutros
Boutros Ghali, and Will.I.Am.
Boutros Boutros Ghali?
I'm gonna find
this little brat's off-switch.
Jeff!
He's just being protective.
I'll stop him.
I am so excited that
we finally have a model U.N.
here at Greendale.
I am really, really, really,
really, really, really
into model U.N.s.
They used to call me model U.N.
guy back in college.
Well, that's not--
don't research that.
The important thing here
is that I am really--
Pardon me, Professor Cligoris.
Cligoris?
Either pronunciation is fine?
Are you here for the model U.N.?
I'm here to tell you
that the entire idea
to have a model U.N.
was hers.
Really? So you're
Clark M. Eichelburger.
So I've had your photo around my
neck since I was in high school.
I'm talking about
the Greendale model U.N.
My Annie gave
this other Annie the idea
and the diabolical
little b--usybody
stabbed her in the back.
It's childish.
Honestly I'm just happy
there is a model U.N.
Annie, is this true?
I recall other Annie
mentioned the concept,
but she certainly
didn't take the initiative
to find a faculty advisor.
I didn't know that all you had
to do was call dibs.
I'm not calling dibs.
Because I'm not a petty
competitive child
that steals ideas.
I simply refuse to acknowledge
the authority
of your criminal model U.N.
So don't recognize it.
It still exists.
Oh, then Annie'll just
start her own model U.N.
Yeah, for grown-ups.
Well, I still don't
recognize it.
Well, it exists, baby!
I'm sorry, I don't understand
your relationship here.
Is he your father
or your lover?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
There can only be one
model U.N.
that officially represents
this school
so let's take our foot
off the crazy pedal
for just a moment here.
There's only one rational way
to settle this.
A head-to-head model U.N.
Battle Royale,
the rules to which I would have
to spend the evening devising.
We'll have the competition
tomorrow
in the cafeteria
at 7:00 P.M.
May the most United Nations win.
- Fair enough.
- Totally fair.
I'll see you in the fair papers,
other Annie.
Oh, and you were asking
what our relationship is?
- We're friends.
- Yeah.
- Good friends.
- Grown-up friends.
- Yeah.
- So.
We're friendly.
So, the key to winning this thing is
when in doubt,
agree with Annie.
That's sweet, Jeff.
But everyone should
just have fun.
Then again, what's more fun
than winning?
Pierce.
I'm offended you would
single me out.
Did you read up on
your country's info-packet?
Yes.
Somalia has 1,900 miles
of coastline,
a government that
knows its place,
and all the guns and wives
you can afford to buy.
Why have I never heard
of this paradise before?
I studied up on my country.
Is it okay if
we do accents, sugar?
Troy, Georgia the country,
not the state.
That's right.
Capital city Tbilisi,
and former member
of the Soviet Union.
And we kindly request y'all
mind your Ps and Qs.
Welcome to the world's
first ever model U.N.-off.
You will each be scored
on your U.N.'s ability
to pass resolutions, follow
procedure, and maintain order.
The end goal, of course,
total world peace.
Any questions?
Does two U.N.s mean
there are two earths?
Uh, yeah.
Sure, two earths.
Parallel earths
in different galaxies
or identical earths
in parallel dimensions?
The latter one.
Well, what does that say
about free will?
Abed! Professor--
Right, yeah, let's begin.
Ready, set,
peace.
Crisis alert.
A civil war has broken out
in Ethiopia.
Rebel forces have seized
the grain supply,
creating
a humanitarian disaster.
Okay, cool heads, everyone.
America proposes a U.N.
peacekeeping force of
10,000 troops.
Uruguay agrees.
Ooh, uh, China, too.
Georgia--the country--
is much obliged.
There's gonna be refugees.
Who can take refugees?
The great country of Somalia.
This gem,
this Shangri-La
graciously invites
the Ethiopian refugees
to enjoy safe lodging
and cool ocean breezes
on its sand-swept beaches.
Okay, we're rolling.
Switzerland proposes
a peace summit.
Good idea, Switzerland.
And maybe at the peace summit
we can discuss the possibility
of opening a portal
to Earth II.
Can we put a pin
in that, Switzerland?
Earth II is out there,
can't ignore it forever.
Well, China has money.
Does anybody want some?
Yes! The United States
proposes using China's money
to fund agricultural programs
to support Ethiopia's
sustainable farms.
Which should promote economic
development and security.
All in favor?
It's unanimous.
Good resolving,
blue U.N.
You really covered
all the bases.
We have a unanimous decision
as well.
Then after one round,
we are tied.
Looks like both U.N.s
are experts at fostering unity.
- Crap.
- Damn it.
Crisis alert. Russia...
This is what the United Nations
is doing to your freedom.
I'm your freedom!
And I'm in a cage.
With the world!
Because of them!
I thought I'd find you here.
What are you gonna do,
lock me up?
Just give me a reason.
I'll give you a reason!
Whoa!
That's it,
you're coming with me.
♪ Hello ♪
♪ is it me you're looking for ♪
He's pulling my cage.
I'm being pulled in my cage
for no reason!
Is anybody seeing this?
Is the world seeing this?
Are we facebooking this?
Crisis alert!
A tsunami has hit Vietnam.
Massive--crisis alert,
famine in Ghana--
crisis alert--tuberculosis
outbreak--crisis alert!
Humanitarian aid.
We further resolve--
- Disarmament treaty.
- Crisis alert!
To help women and children
get through famines.
Save the orphans.
Loose nukes--
sinkhole--
North Korea--
the prime minister in exile!
Military coup!
The tropical paradise
of Somalia graciously yields.
- China will pay.
- Gooder than grits.
Switzerland is very concerned
about Earth II.
Uruguay agrees.
Uruguay sounds
like "you're a gay."
Backyard barbecue!
Uruguay kindly requests that
Somalia stop pronouncing it
"you're a gay."
- Hereditary monarchy!
- Resolved.
- Graft and corruption.
Crisis alert!
Resolved.
Looking good, blue U.N.
Getting very close
to world peace.
That's my girl.
You are kicking ass.
All right, guys,
this is the home stretch.
All we gotta do is focus.
Oh! Damn, Pierce.
Ooh, that wasn't me.
I don't smell anything--
whup, I just got it.
Oh, it's in my mouth.
Guys, come on, focus.
Like adults.
We're gonna lose a point
if we don't get through this.
Get through it?
It's almost a solid.
Crisis alert.
A genocidal dictator
in Laos--
Yeah, yeah, we'll get to that.
Okay, so, looking at Turkey,
what can you do?
So let me get this straight.
You're bringing her in here
for "making a mess."
I did more than make a mess.
I turned your whole system
inside out.
And I shut her down.
Young lady, you spilled paint
on a globe.
You're as much a criminal
as this idiot is a cop.
None whatsoever.
Okay, but, um, she's going
to do something illegal.
Aren't you?
Is that true?
Do you, Britta Perry,
have any intentions
of breaking any laws ever?
I-I-
Oh, my God.
No, it's not that simple.
I have a life now.
I have a major and--
Get out please.
I have highlighters.
Get out!
Okay, I know you've got a lot
on your mind right now.
But somebody broke that thing
that comes down
from the parking booth.
You know the thing
that comes down,
keeps the...cars
from coming in.
The thing. It's like a gate,
but it's just a stick.
Comes down, from a hinge.
Keeps the cars out.
Goes up and down 90 degrees.
The arm?
Ooh, point goes to red team.
How is this still happening?
I can't remember what
regular air smells like.
Do something or
we're gonna lose.
Guys, this is important
to Annie.
So whoever actually died
a few months ago, 'fess up
so we can put a stake
through your heart.
Jeff!
Annie, I think
the real lesson here is
that a model U.N.,
much like the real U.N.,
quickly falls apart
when faced with actual--
Noooooo!
I think the lesson here
is that I need to win this!
I want to win!
And you!
You suck!
You're a stupid, ugly poopface!
I'm better than you!
Annie, stop.
You're acting
like a little schoolgirl
and not in a hot way.
Okay.
Uh, that made me sound creepy.
But--but here's the thing.
Don't look at me.
If embarrassment were
bountiful zinc deposits,
I'd be Zambia.
There's nothing
to be Zambia about, Annie.
This is all my fault.
I pushed you into competing
with other Annie.
Are you kidding me?
I practically ran to you
with that flier.
I wanted to destroy her.
All because I can't handle
the thought
of anyone getting
more gold stars than me.
I'm such a child.
You're not.
Listen, when you really
hate someone
the way you hate Annie Kim,
or when you feel
the way I feel about you,
the easy loophole through
the creepiness and danger
is to treat them like a child.
"A chip off the old block,
you're the best, kiddo."
It's a crutch.
It's a way for me to tell you
how important you are
from a distance.
But now you're becoming this...
mature, self-possessed,
intelligent young woman,
and I can't keep
patting you on the head
or talking down to you.
But I like how close we are.
I don't want to grow up if
it means losing what we have.
Well, tough, Annie.
You have to grow up because the
world needs more women like you.
Can't keep doing
this forever, kiddo.
Can't we?
- Nope. I can't, no.
- Nope, that's gross.
That feels gross.
Well, I better go
check on the group.
If they haven't left already.
I'll follow you.
From a respectable distance.
Guys?
I'm sorry I put you
through that.
And I know it doesn't make up
for what happened,
but would it help if I said
I farted?
Annie, no.
I can't let you fall
on that sword because...
I farted.
No, I farted.
Guys, I wasn't doing
the Spartacus thing.
I farted.
No, seriously, I--
We all farted.
Oh, you guys!
- Annie...
- I'm farting now.
Wait, why are you still here?
Abed may have figured out
a way we can still win.
Really? How?
It's simple, really.
First we...
Abed, what did I tell you?
You can't just mumble nonsense.
No one's cutting away.
Okay, fine,
here's my actual plan.
What is that?
It's from Britta.
She's promising to disrupt
the model...U.N.
She says she's gonna cause
a disruption that,
while not completely illegal,
should be a real concern
to campus...Security!
Oh, no.
Maybe we should call
the real cops.
You know, back in the '80s,
I had this real
piece of work protestor,
used to always give me trouble.
You know what happened to her?
She incited a riot
at the W.T.O.
Got choked
until she passed out.
By some real cop
with a real billyclub.
Sometimes I wonder, you know?
Well, what are you waiting for?
Go show that hippie
how the world really works.
Aren't you
forgetting something?
All in favor?
Aye?
Could you morons say aye
any slower? Come on.
- Greetings, people of Earth II.
- What is this?
We represent
the United Nations from Earth I.
Using our Switzerland's
hadron collider
and resources from
every nation,
the people of our planet
have constructed
a trans-dimensional
gateway here.
They can't do this.
The science works out.
Yes.
We come to you with an offer.
We he achieved world peace,
tying our score with yours.
But we are willing
to concede our victory
if you agree conceding yours,
forming one gigantic
United United Nations.
We did it.
You're a fool.
Your ultimatum is itself
a technical act of aggression.
If we simply refuse
to recognize your authority,
we still remain ahead
and you lose.
But you win a simple game.
The larger symbolic victory
will be ours.
Oh la la.
We refuse.
I'll take the real victory.
A logical, effective,
common sense move, Annie Kim.
One which flies in the very face
of the United Nations itself,
a fundamentally symbolic
organization
founded on the principles
of high-minded rhetoric
and empty gestures.
Blue U.N. wins.
What the hell are you doing?
Nothing.
And you can't do anything
to stop me.
Did someone say
"can't do anything"?
♪ Hello ♪
♪ is it me you're looking for ♪
♪ I can see it in your eyes ♪
♪ I can see it in your smile ♪
♪ you're all I've ever wanted ♪
♪ And my arms are open wide ♪
♪ 'cause you know
just what to say ♪
♪ and you know
just what to do ♪
Oh, that's--
that's nice. No?
♪ And I want to tell you
so much ♪
I knew you'd come.
You're so busted.
♪ I love you ♪
Yes.
I told you to stop playing
Operation on me!
I'm not your damn board game!
At least you didn't get
my spare ribs.
Sync & corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org