Why did I come to Greendale?
So I can keep my job
and get busy with my education.
To meet different people.
Because Greendale's
a slam dunk.
- So why should you--
- Why should you--
Why should you go Greendale?
That's easy.
Greendale has
the most advanced typing class
in the southwestern
Greendale area.
And now you can register
by fax.
Go Greendale,
go Greendale, go!
That, as you probably know,
is the currently-running
commercial for our school.
Yeah, I always see it
during late-night marathons
of Fantasy Island.
That's not an accident.
It's the result
of intensive targeting.
But now,
Greendale's School board
has given me a budget of
$2,000 to update our little ad.
Are you sure it should change?
I chose Greendale
over city college
because of the way
that one dude goes...
Ah, okay, okay.
You know I love to be seen
agreeing with you, Troy.
But this is our chance to make
Greendale's most reasonable
dreams come true.
And I need your help--
All of you.
That's okay, Jeffrey.
You can say no.
This school asks
very little of its students.
It mainly gives.
I feel like you guys might know
what I'm talking about.
How can we help?
Oh, thanks for asking.
I've chosen you,
Greendale's brightest,
most coincidentally diverse,
hispanics not withstanding,
study group to star
in our commercial.
- Ooh.
- Pick a character.
We start this weekend.
Oh, we get to be on tv!
But if we're shooting
this weekend,
why are these cameras here?
Abed, true to form, has
decided to do the weird thing
and film a documentary
instead of helping.
As a student of character,
I have a feeling
that trying to make
this commercial
may cost the dean his sanity.
And my camera follows
the fire, not the smoke.
Ever seen Hearts of Darkness?
Way better than Apocalypse Now.
What's the catering sitch
going to be on this picture?
This isn't Hollywood, Pierce.
If it was, these glasses
would be tinted,
and I'd be friends
with Stevie Nicks.
No catering.
This is outrageous.
I'm not leaving my trailer
till there's food.
You don't have a trailer.
Well, then,
I'll rent a trailer.
And I won't leave it till
I have the one I don't have.
I'm an actor,
not a circus freak.
Oh, no.
I needed to go that way.
Eh, I'll loop around.
♪ Give me some rope,
time in a tree ♪
♪ give me the hope
to run out of steam ♪
♪ somebody said
we could be here ♪
♪ we could be roped up,
tied up, dead in a year ♪
♪ I can't count the reasons
I should stay ♪
♪ one by one they all
just fade away ♪
sync by honeybunny
corrected by susanaLC
www.addic7ed.com
All right, let's rehearse
this mamajama.
Does everyone know
who they are?
Where's my script girl?
It's supervisor,
and I'm right behind you.
Thank you, supervisor girl.
Faster than a locomotive.
A script supervisor
is the person
that tells everyone
to stay on script
and keeps careful notes to
prevent logical inconsistencies.
So... basically the star.
We open on
a typical day at Greendale,
only the students
all look happy
and you can't smell that smell.
Troy?
"Why do I go Greendale?"
"With three kids at home,
you better believe
every penny counts."
"To meet different people."
And then, you and Troy hug--
if you're comfortable with that.
- Of course.
- Yeah, Troy and I are buds.
Best buds. Air buds, even.
Feeling stupid.
And then, the camera pans,
and enter Dean Pelton.
I got stuck with
the role of the dean.
So I'm going to show him
how much of a dean I can be.
And I've got a feeling
I won't make the cut.
Welcome to Dean-Dale
community colle-dean.
I'm a silly goose.
Honk, honk.
Dean-a-Lee-doo.
- Look at me.
- Stop.
This is my sister's outfit.
Jeffrey, stop.
You've hit gold.
Save some for the screen.
All right, people,
scene six is up first.
Oh, and I don't think
Pierce is coming back.
Can someone fill in
as the pencil?
Pierce Hawthorne,
screen of stage and star,
will not leave this trailer
until he gets a trailer.
And then I'm not leaving that
trailer until there's catering.
And I'm not eating
the food until--
And action.
Why go Greendale?
Just because, just dean it!
Dean machine.
Got dean, got much,
much got--
And cut.
Oh, a star is born.
I suggested to the dean
that we shoot my scenes
in front of
the Luis Guzman statue
because the dean
has no legal right
to broadcast Guzman's image,
which means every shot
will be unusable.
I even put a call in to
Guzman's lawyers to alert them.
I'm always willing
to go the extra mile
to avoid doing something.
Like sex with women.
Shut up, Leonard,
you smell like mentholyptus.
What are you even doing here?
I'm thinking about
breaking into the tv game.
Since it's apparently
sticking around.
I don't want to wake up
in 30 years
and wonder "what if?"
"Because this full-time mama
ain't breaking the bank
with your expensive tuition."
Okay, cut.
Shirley, the voice.
Can you make it, um--
I thought it would be more s--
What's another word that means
happy/threatening?
The worde's looking for
is "sassy."
He better pray
he don't find it.
As soon as we get this shot,
we are done.
- Your phone is ringing.
- Oh.
- Dean deaning.
- Dean Pelton?
Hey, man, how you doing?
It's Luis Guzman.
I hear you're making
a commercial for Greendale,
and you need permission
to use my face or something?
Well, I, um...
Uh...
Well, why not
use the real thing?
I'm sorry?
I'm saying, I'd love
to be in your commercial.
Wowee!
A real big-time celebrity
wants to be in my commercial.
Wowee.
A real big time celebrity
wants to be in my commercial.
- Come on down.
- Yeah, that's cool.
But listen, I've got
to finish this movie,
so, you know, I can't come for
a couple of weeks, all right?
Mr. Guzman, Luis,
thank you.
And can I just say,
I loved you in--
Innnnnnnn...
IMDb.
See you soon, man.
That was tragic.
The students here mean well,
they really do.
But what Greendale has
always needed is a miracle.
This is it.
This is how I get
to put Greendale on the map.
You know, I thought this
commercial was going to be okay.
Well, guess what?
It just officially
became great.
Let me give you
a little rundown
of this commercial's
great elements.
Luis Guzman is in it.
I'm sorry, will you excuse me?
Everyone gather 'round,
quick announcement.
Come on around.
Everything that we shot so far
is worthless.
I've thrown it out,
and we're starting over
tomorrow morning.
- Why?
- Because...
Luis Guzman
is in the commercial now, so...
Yeah. For realsies.
Everyone, go home.
I'm rewriting all of your parts.
Except for you, Jeffrey.
You have locked
into something here.
And the only thing
your character needs
is more screen time.
It's great that
he got a celebrity,
- but why reshoot everything?
- Perfectionism.
The dean's first step
down a road
that ends
in self-destruction.
That sounds...
Horrible.
Actually, I might end up
taking this to some festivals.
The dean's production has
taken over the entire school.
Classes are shut down.
The quilting club is being
forced to sew costumes.
Two females, both 5'10",
one brunette, one with asthma.
He's also using the P.A.
system for casting calls.
Okay, everyone--
Does everyone have
their new script?
Uh, it says I'm supposed to be
a book reading a book.
That--that doesn't
make sense.
What's this?
Scene four.
Last night, I had an epiphany.
I'm ready to step
this mother up a notch.
This commercial is going
to push every button,
starting with the one
that is so hot,
it will sizzle
your finger--
racccccce.
And action.
"To meet
different people."
Cut!
I'm coming in.
I am trying to pull
a 400-year-old dagger
out of this nation's heart,
and you two are hugging.
Her, I understand, but you?
What did I do?
You didn't.
Let's take it again!
"To meet
different people."
Again.
"To meet
different people."
I need more!
More!
Wrong!
Fight the power!
Fight it with your hugs.
Tear down those walls.
Okay, you get this wrong
one more time,
I'm segregating the school.
"To meet different people."
You can't even do it
when we're helping you!
Somebody help her!
To meet different people!
Stop saying I'm different!
Dean, we've spent
12 hours on this scene.
Maybe it's time
to move on to something else.
I'm in Psych 101, and even I
don't know what's happening.
The dean is going insane
and taking all of you with him.
If you know that,
then do something!
I'm doing everything I can.
I only have so many cameras.
- Oh!
- Aah!
I've spent an entire day
in this thing for no reason.
What if the shoot drags on
for another day?
Or, God forbid, two.
And action, and move.
"This full-time mama
ain't breaking the bank--"
Cut, cut, cut,
cut, cut, cut--Garrett,
you're not taking advantage of
the motion capture technology.
You have to move.
I forgot what I am again.
Oh, for crying out--
you are a microscope!
No, that's a toilet.
No, that's clearly a frog
who can't get out of a box.
Jeff thinks he has it bad?
As Jeff's understudy,
I have to wear my Jeff wig
on top of my Chang hair and
then my bald cap on top of that.
There's no air
getting through here.
I'm literally dying.
But you'll never hear my story.
I mean, now you heard it,
but... That was close.
Are you sure you can't
work a little faster?
Nobody asked for perfection.
Well, perfection
is what you're getting.
And if you don't like it,
you can fire me.
Yeah, if we don't like it,
at this point,
we definitely will fire you.
Good.
That's how I like it. Ha!
I'm surrounded by assassins.
By own school's paper
has turned on me.
But when this is all over,
I'll have a commercial
with Luis Guzman in it,
and all they'll have are
their words and their fears
and whatever
embarrassing photos
they can get from
my two-faced mother.
Garrett, I've got
two men in diapers here.
I know one of them is playing
the dawn of a new era
in education,
but I've got nothing
on the other one.
Oh, um,
just a guest of the dean's.
Well, both of you
go that way, then.
The dean had
his seventh epiphany today,
which has given me
an epiphany of my own.
The dean is a genius.
He has to be.
If he isn't, I've given
almost two weeks of my life
to an idiot.
That is unacceptable.
Therefore the dean is a genius.
And I will die
protecting his vision.
Are you by any chance familiar
with Stockholm Syndrome?
Is it something
that the dean created?
Because if not, I don't care.
We all wanna go,
but the dean won't let us.
I think Pierce played this
the smartest from the beginning.
He's probably at home
watching Forensic Files
and eating cheesy popcorn.
Well, about time.
Hey, that's for Luis Guzman.
Well, when you get me
my trailer, he can have it back.
And make it
as nice as this one.
Hey, Dean.
Dean? Hey, Dean!
Pierce mistook me
for the dean today.
- I want windows.
- How did that make you feel?
I've become
a stranger to myself.
I'm bald now.
I've always been bald.
I merely dreamt of having hair.
And now the bald man is awake.
Jeff?
It's time.
Lights, camera, Dean.
Action.
Why go Greendale?
Just because!
Cut.
Lose the bald cap.
- What?
- I don't like it.
It's hokey, it's fake.
Take it off.
No.
I beg your pardon, actor?
I have worn this stupid thing
for 12 days.
I have made bald friends.
Well, that's your mistake.
Because it's a lie.
It's Hollywood crap.
And I won't allow it
in my commercial.
You're not bald.
Yes, I am.
Well, then, you're wrong
for the part!
Understudy!
That's it.
That's reality.
Winger, you're done.
Go home.
Okay, I don't know why,
but this is the last straw.
As a licensed psychology major,
I am declaring this production
a violation of human rights.
You have made us prisoners
of your insanity.
Shut your face, Britta.
If the dean wants his role
to be played by a Chinese man
in a blond wig--
Oh, my God, you are insane.
All right, I'm sick and tired
of hearing complaints
that I'm forcing people
to be here.
Anyone who doesn't want
to help me can leave!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
- Abed, stop!
- Okay.
Keep rolling.
Hello?
Hello.
Hello, it's me.
Luis Guzman.
- Hello!
- Hi.
Hi, Mr. Guzman,
Dean/Director Craig Pelton.
Sorry, I've been editing.
It's a ltle bit of a mess.
What the --  is that?
Oh, that's a possum.
Once you spend
some time with them,
you see they're just like
big, gentle rats.
- Who's the guy?
- I'm no one.
That's Abed.
He's a little bit odd.
Now, without further ado,
here is the commercial
you will be staring in.
Why do I go Greendale?
- Aah!
- What's in the box?
Ohh...Oh...
I've got to make a phone call.
I had to tell this dean
I couldn't do his commercial.
He didn't take that
too well either.
Y'all gotta help this dude.
I mean, aren't you his friends?
I'm more of a fly on the wall.
What is go--
what?
You won't be in my commercial,
but you'll be in
his stupid documentary?
All he does
is follow people around.
Yeah, but haven't you seen
Hearts of Darkness?
- Way better than--
- I want you
the hell off of my campus,
you ungrateful backstabber.
I already got rid
of your trailer.
I had a trailer?
Can anyone hear me?
I will walk off
this production.
I will quit!
Hello?
I come here to shoot
this commercial for Greendale.
That's what you had
written on the script.
Ugh, that script was terrible.
I thought it was pretty good.
Of course you'd think that.
You went here.
Oh, I get it.
You're worse than crazy.
You're ashamed of your school.
And that--that statue
of me out there,
that's just wrong, man.
Well, the bronze
adds ten pounds.
- Nah, man--
- It's not going to be perfect.
Screw you.
I'm just saying, don't worship
the people leaving Greendale.
Worship the people
that are here.
Worship this place.
It changes people's life.
Look, I loved my time here.
I got laid like crazy.
That's way before
Boogie Nights too.
Look, this is a special school.
You don't deserve to be here.
Are you still filming, Abed?
Yeah, but try not
to address me.
I'm not really here.
Neither am I.
I don't think I can finish
my commercial.
But I think I know
how your documentary ends.
Hi, I'm Craig Pelton,
Dean of Greendale
Community College.
I have failed this school.
I have failed it
because I thought
I was better than Greendale.
See, I went to a university,
so I thought it was my job
to improve this place.
But it turns out that the only
thing wrong with Greendale
is that it's run by
an insecure wreck
who holds five dances
and two talent shows a year
because he's afraid that
the school isn't good enough.
But Greendale is good enough
because it accepts me
for what I'm not.
Greendale is the best school
in the entire world,
and I'm so sorry
what I've done to it.
And I'm sorry what I've done
to the ice cream machine.
Aah!
Please, no one eat out of it
until you clean the nozzles.
The janitor knows how.
I'm horrible.
Gentlemen, what I'm about
to show you
is not the commercial
you paid me to create.
What I am about to show you
is a glimpse into
my mind and soul.
Please hold your questions
until the end.
I know you will have
a lot of them,
but I'll understand
if you'd rather I just leave.
Why do I go Greendale?
The dean is a genius.
To meet different people.
With three kids at home,
you better believe
every penny counts.
I loved my time here.
I got laid like crazy.
So why should you--
Why should you--
Why should you
go to Greendale?
Greendale is the best school
in the entire world.
Go Greendale,
go Greendale, go!
It's good.
Y-you know what,
better than good.
Good enough.
Is there any more
of the crazy Chinese guy?
He pops.
I'm confused.
That's not my commercial.
I-I didn't make that.
Yeah, yeah, okay, Zemeckis,
it moved through you.
Anyway, congratulations.
That should last us
another 16 years.
So, uh, what's next?
- Chump's rusty bucket?
- Quarter taps.
- Did you do this?
- You did mostly.
You got the footage
you needed on the first day.
I added a little bit of
my footage to fill in the gaps.
I thought you were
a fly on the wall.
Some flies are too awesome
for the wall.
Documentarians are supposed
to be objective,
to avoid having
any effect on the story.
And yet we have more effect
than anyone.
Because we decide to tell it.
And we decide how it ends.
Will your story be
yet another sad one
of yet another man
who just wanted to be happy?
Or will your story acknowledge
the very nature of stories
and embrace the fact
that sharing the sad ones
can sometimes make them happy?
Ugh.
Before you say anything...
Nope, I've got nothing.
Can you just forgive me?
Yep.
Why?
Because we've all been there.
Which is why we're all here.
Aww!
I'm a good Dean?
Yeah.
Can someone help me get
a live possum out of my office?
We could do that.
It just keeps jumping
and skittering.
And you think you're prepared,
and then it skitters again.
Okay, scene's over.
Hmm?
sync by honeybunny, corrected by susanaLC
www.addic7ed.com
They'll be ready for you
in 20 minutes, Mr. Garland.
Great.
I'm a star!
Give me that.
I will not be mitigated.
Okay, you know what?
I'm not coming out of
this trailer
until I get a new trailer.
And get me
a granola bar!
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org