Pierce, you made us all drive
to a warehouse
in the middle of nowhere.
You could at least tell us why.
Hey, I know as much as you.
I got a letter
from the executor
of my father's estate.
It said to come out here
with my seven closest friends.
You brought six.
Well, who else
was he gonna bring?
Levar Burton was a maybe.
Mr. Hawthorne.
[All gasp]
I apologize.
Gilbert.
Even from the grave,
my father's got you
by the short and curly
salt and pepperies.
My name is Gilbert Lawson.
I was Cornelius Hawthorne's
assistant for over 30 years,
and before that,
I was just the teenager
who read the Bible to him
in the bath.
- Ew.
- All right, all right.
It's inheritance time.
How 'bout that check,
soul brother?
Your father did leave you
something,
but it's more of an activity.
Thank you for keeping it
as creepy as possible.
This looks like a multi-player
gaming interface.
I've heard enough.
Oh, that diabolical
old fossil face.
I asked him for money
to invest in video games
back in 1979.
Cornelius spent over 30 years
developing a video game for you.
It was his dying wish
that you and seven of your
closest friends would play it.
Lavar Burton was a maybe.
So, please, choose a seat.
Cool.
So a 100-year-old man designed
a 30-year-old video game?
This I've got to see.
Once you're seated
behind your computers,
a photograph of you
will be taken
and an avatar will be made
from your likeness.
I didn't bring my likeness.
All right, everyone,
let's begin.
[Typing]
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Sync and corrections by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
Resync for WEB-DL by Norther
[Whizzing]
- Nice!
- Cool.
- Old school.
- Cool, cool, cool.
Which one is me?
I assume nothing
because I'm not racist.
Aww! We're adorable!
Why did this thing take photos
if it was going to completely
fabricate random body shapes?
That's what I'm saying!
My hair looks good, though.
Orange button is jump.
[Boinging]
Whee!
Which guy am I?
There's a door here.
[Door clicks]
- Peace. Love.
- What's that?
- I think it's a hippie.
- Peace. Love.
Aww!
Annie, stop "awing" everything.
Don't be jaded.
He's saying "peace."
- Hello.
- Sex.
- Did he say "sex"?
- Drugs. Sex.
Oh, my God.
Hold on, I'm coming.
- Oh! Oh! Ow! Ow!
- Darn! Shoot!
Dang it. Um...
Jeff, you just murdered Annie.
Well, better than
doing nothing!
- I'm not sure that's the case.
- That's debatable.
You guys, help me.
- The way you helped Annie?
- Sex.
Before we engage,
we should hang back and study
their tactics.
- What?
- Group sex.
Oh, my God!
Oh, cool, I'm alive.
- Pierce?
- This game makes no sense.
- What happened to you?
- I don't want to talk about it.
Pierce, point the joystick
right.
So I'm supposed to
just guess that?
Where are the instructions?
[Overlapping chatter]
Take that! Take that!
Yeah, we rule!
Oh, you guys are alive.
You re-spawn in the study room
when you die.
Here, I'll show you.
- Hey!
- Jeffrey! Shame on you!
"Hang back and study
their tactics"?
Let him get it
out of his system.
Ah, forget it.
Let's just keep moving.
[Dinging]
[Electronic pulse]
Now what?
Welcome to Hawkthorne.
That's dad's voice.
Dad?
[Electronic whoosh]
Piercinald, in 1980,
you said that video games,
not moist towelettes,
were the business
of the future.
Today, moist towelettes are
stocked in every supermarket,
while arcade after arcade
closes.
He's got a point.
Nevertheless,
I designed this game
to be played upon my death
by you and whatever
cabal of fruits,
junkies, and sluts
you call your friends.
Her name is Britta.
Only one player can win...
the first to reach my throne
inside Castle Hawkthorne.
Their reward, Pierce,
will be your inheritance.
- What?
- His inheritance? What?
So you see, Pierce,
turns out you were right.
Video games are important.
[Laughs]
Worst son ever!
Well, great.
How do I fight you guys?
Which button fights?
- Pierce, stop.
- Pierce, relax.
Pierce, stay in the game,
stay in the game.
Pierce, calm down.
- Nobody's gonna fight you.
- Why not?
Because when you're friends
with someone for three years,
it's weird to steal
their family's money.
And there wouldn't be
a lot of sport in beating you.
- Look at yourself.
- Yeah, he's right.
You're playing the game wrong.
[All scream]
Why is Harry Belafonte in here?
It's Gilbert.
You're not supposed to
cooperate,
you're supposed to compete.
Thanks for the advice,
but I think we can choose
how we want to play.
- I suppose we can.
- Is he being ominous?
Why are you being ominous?
[High-pitched beeps]
Whoa.
We can pick stuff up?
This game is more complex
than you can imagine.
And aside from its programmers,
who have all been deported
back to China,
I'm the one who knows
how it works.
[Screaming
and overlapping chatter]
Run, run!
He's gonna throw a knife!
Go!
Jump! Jump!
[Screaming and yelling]
Wah!
[Descending electronic tone]
[Fast-paced music]
Wait! What are you...?
[Beeps]
He's a psychopath!
He's suffo...
[electronic tones]
[Descending tone]
[Laughs] Yeah.
Hey, look, buddy,
I know it must have sucked
being colonel Sanders'
manservant and all,
but Pierce is technically
our friend,
and we're not gonna watch you
screw him over.
Perhaps you should be
asking yourselves
how you intend to stop me.
How about if we come over
there and kick your ass?
Go get him, Troy.
Be my guest.
But 30 seconds after you
leave your chairs,
the weight sensors
will recognize it
as an automatic forfeit.
Weight sensors?
[Whizzing]
That's it.
Let's get that jag!
- Yeah!
- Get him!
- Kick that hippie's ass!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Let's go!
Move, move, move!
- I think he left a note.
- What?
"After you've squandered
the last of your savings,
"I'll watch you writhe,
penniless, in the gutter,
"through a telescope
in the penthouse office
of Hawthorne Tower."
[Musical tones]
You can leave notes.
This game is incredible.
Pierce?
[Electronic pulse]
- No, Pierce!
- Please, no!
We need you!
Just let me die.
Pierce, so Gilbert
knows a couple tricks.
Big deal.
We outnumber him.
And most importantly,
while he's fighting for greed,
we're fighting for friendship,
which means we can't lose,
okay?
- Okay.
- Okay!
[Descending tone]
I guess there's no hug button.
Everybody
keep Pierce protected.
We have to get him to the Throne
of Hawkthorne before Gilbert.
And don't forget, when you die,
you go all the way back
to the study room.
So... Don't die.
Good pep talk, Jeff.
Yeah, I used to love dying,
but that speech really
turned me around.
Whatever.
[Peaceful music playing]
What's that?
Kill it!
It's a girl milking a cow,
Pierce.
I'll check it out.
I owe Jeff that.
I wasn't gonna say it.
I am Hilda.
I live in the village.
- Lesbian.
- Shh!
[Electronic tones]
[Beeps]
I can help with that.
I have information
on many topics.
Cool.
[Beep]
The throne is in Castle
Hawkthorne, north of here.
You unlock the castle with the
white crystal of discipline,
which you must free
from the black caverns.
I'm picking up on
some hidden symbolism.
Right,
"white crystal."
You think dad was into meth?
You can usually get supplies
in a town like this.
Man, why can't my mom be here?
She always said my video game
knowledge would come in handy.
I never believed her.
Everybody split up
and take a hut.
Our only chance of beating
Gilbert is to cover more ground.
[Beeps]
I have information
on the following topics.
[Electronic tones]
[Beeps]
Holy crap.
Where have you been
my whole life?
[Hammering tones]
I buy and sell weapons
and armor.
[Electronic tones]
Cool. We need weapons.
[Beeps]
Ooh. Well, what's free?
Can we have a torch?
- Thief! Thief!
- Annie, put it back.
Sorry. Sorry.
Arr! Arr!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, oh! Oh, no!
- What are you doing?
- It was an accident!
- Arrr!
- He's dying!
- Arrrrrr!
- All right, hold on, hold on!
Arrr! Arrr!
Now what are you doing?
He was suffering!
Yeah, from axe wounds!
Well, if this isn't
worth any points, what is?
You're asking me? I'm still
looking for a pong paddle.
- Let's play poker.
- Oh, now we're talking.
Check the desk.
I'll check the dresser.
How do I straighten
that painting?
You can't.
Stop playing like a girl.
[Electronic tones]
[Beep]
Stop playing like a girl?
Here's the thing
about women, Jeff.
We don't hack and slash
our way through life
because we're one with life.
- Help me hide the body.
- Oh, my lord. Oh, my lord.
Shirley, these things happen
in video games.
- They do?
- Yes.
We can't get hung up
on real world morality.
We need to survive and win.
Hello, I'm the blacksmith's
wife... Aah! Help!
- Oh, crap!
- Guard the door.
What?
[Beeps]
Shirley!
No witnesses!
Grab everything you can carry.
I'll check upstairs
for any more family.
Don't give me that look.
These are your loose ends.
I'm just tying 'em up.
This is so cool.
Where are your clothes?
Pierce taught me poker.
I'm not good at it.
You still talking to this girl?
Yeah, she only has three moves
that you activate with basic
patterns of stimulus.
I've never felt this way
before.
- Abed, don't get weird.
- Oh, I won't.
She's not ready
for anything serious,
but she wants me
to meet her family.
- My father is the blacksmith.
- Her father's a blacksmith.
- Hello!
- Everybody go shopping?
That's all we did.
Is that hut on fire?
Oh, my.
What an unexplained tragedy.
Don't we look comfy
at a cauldron.
Check it out.
[Electronic tones]
[Beeps]
Ooh, see, I'll put
all of this in here,
and then that,
and then I'll hit this.
[Electronic pulses] What is it?
I assume, like,
a strength potion.
Then I assume it's poison.
You're just jealous
because we found a world
where I know what I'm doing.
This place is 20 cat turds
and a pixies poster
from being your apartment.
[Crying]
What's with
the St. Pauli girl?
Hilda's parents lived there.
Now she has no family.
She'll be forced to marry
a male villager
or take her chances
in the wilderness.
What kind of game is this?
- Oh, crap, it's Gilbert.
- Well, well, well.
Looks like someone's
one step behind.
Yeah, if you're looking
for equipment, tough luck.
The store was lost
in a freak accident.
I hardly need equipment,
young lady.
While you were shopping, I
gained enough levels to do this.
Uh-huh,
come on and bring it!
He's shooting lightning
and I'm naked!
Get behind us!
We have armor!
Oh! Whoa!
Aah!
Oh, great! Gilbert!
Oh, great!
Evil Jedi lightning Gilbert!
[Groans] Oh!
Britta, drink that super
strength potion you made.
Oh, right, right, right, right.
Hurry up, Britta!
I'm trying, I'm trying!
Aah!
Damn it, I thought we could
count on Britta
to not screw up drinking.
This'll be fun.
[Electronic pulses]
What the hell?
Here's hoping we can
count on her
to screw up making potions.
[Music playing]
[Groans]
[Descending tone]
[Cheering]
Unbelievable.
Jeff bet all our lives
on Britta and won,
and I lost my pants
to a pair of nines.
[Whiz]
[Sighs]
Very well.
Let's play.
[Typing]
Abed, are you sure about this?
Yeah. It just feels like
the right thing to do.
Hey, I made it back.
You guys never died.
How did you beat Gilbert?
Oh, you know.
Teamwork.
We were headed
for the black caves
to find the white crystal.
We were just saying goodbye
to Abed.
I'm gonna stay here
in the village with Hilda
and help her rebuild her life.
Abed, she's a program.
People have said
similar things about me.
Uh-oh. He's playing
the rain man card.
Let's bounce.
I've got an inheritance to win.
[Music playing]
♪ ♪
[Swooping tone]
Offensive.
Called it.
Shut up, Britta.
♪ ♪
[Swooping tone]
You did great in there, Jeff.
Shut up, Pierce.
[Beep]
[Musical tones]
♪ ♪
Okay, duck.
Stay ducked.
Okay, unduck.
Okay, now jump.
I think we're almost there.
Thank God.
This cave is the worst.
I know, I don't know
what's more offensive...
the actual racism
or the insulting notion
that it might somehow
rub off on us.
[Turkey gobbling]
Look out! Jive turkeys!
Kill them before
they start multiplying!
[Overlapping grunts, groans,
and chatter]
- Yeah, suck on this!
- Take that, jive turkey!
[Groans]
[Turkey gobbling]
[Swooping tone]
All right!
The white crystal!
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
- Get it!
I'll take it.
I've earned it
by having friends.
[Music playing]
This is it.
[Cheering]
It certainly is.
- No, man!
- You again?
Now I'll have that crystal.
I think you'll have this.
[Zapping]
Whoops.
Arrows!
[Dinging]
[Electronic pulses]
What? Come on!
[Electronic tones]
[Beeps]
Where'd you get all that stuff?
You've only been alive
for an hour.
[Swooping tone]
[All screaming]
[Electronic tones]
Well, that was not fair.
What the hell, Gilbert?
You're cheating, which I
have no problem with,
but you're getting caught,
and that's not cool!
Yeah, don't be a knob.
That inheritance
is rightfully mine!
Rightfully?
I'm his son.
- So am I.
- Oh.
What?
That can't be true.
- You're half... white.
- Nice save.
Do you remember
your childhood nanny, Etta?
Well, Etta had a hot cousin.
My mother.
So you see, Pierce,
I am your half-brother,
and I am more your father's son
than you ever were,
so shut up and play the game.
- Why you...
- Let's go, Pierce.
[Whizzing]
Okay, look,
I know things seem hopeless
because he's all the way to
the castle with the crystal
and we're starting over,
but here's the thing...
we're better at this game now.
We've died and been reborn,
and that makes us heroes.
[Cheering]
- Charge!
- Let's get him!
[All screaming]
[Descending tone]
[Foreboding music]
♪ ♪
I guess the fact that
we're still playing
means he hasn't won yet.
Yeah, but what's the point?
He'll just keep cheating
until he wins.
Why are all the trees cut down?
Isn't this where
Abed's village was?
- Hello, old friends.
- Abed!
You remember Hilda.
I live in the village.
I love Abed.
Did she just say your name?
Yeah, if you max out
a character's trust
and affection levels,
you can gain access
to a front-end
scripting language.
Watch.
[Beeps]
Cool cool cool!
She can make babies for me.
Oh, and I can't?
I can't.
Come on inside.
I built this from scratch.
Check out my castle.
- Oh, it's nice.
- Wow.
I hope this isn't blood gold.
This is my family.
Baby Abed has my eyes
and her bonnet.
Each baby is capable of
executing custom code,
which means you can
write a code
that makes one baby
tell another baby what to do,
much like real children
on a playground.
Oh, Abed, but...
Annie, let's find
the tin man's heart later.
Abed, how much stuff
do you have here
and what can we make with it?
- That depends.
- On?
On what you can imagine.
Cool, cool, cool.
Welcome,
you are the first to make it
to the Throne of Hawkthorne.
Let me take a look at you.
According to your complexion,
I think you might be
Gilbert Lawson.
Is this true?
Just a moment.
Hello, Gilbert.
Due to the nature
of our relationship,
I'll need your
electronic signature
on this legally-binding
agreement.
[Musical tones]
It dictates that you
will never, ever
besmirch the Hawthorne name
with any outlandish notions
regarding you
genealogical origins.
You are the bastard offspring
of a colored seductress
and an unknown,
weak-willed miscegenist...
It's a simple question,
Gilbert.
Do you agree?
Thank you for being honest,
Gilbert.
No!
I'm your son!
I'm sorry, Gilbert.
I always knew
you'd disappoint me.
Cool cool cool!
Ah, I see
you've chosen teamwork.
A coward's strategy.
I will upgrade your challenge
accordingly.
[Grunts]
[Electronic whooshing]
♪ ♪
I bequeath my fortune
to no inferiors.
♪ ♪
[Electronic gunfire]
- Yeah!
- Attack!
What's this now?
[Laughs]
Whoo hoo hoo hoo!
Here we go!
Get him!
Aim for the joints!
Cool cool cool!
- Take that!
- Get him!
Die, racism!
[Groans]
[Electronic gunfire]
♪ Troy and Abed shooting lava ♪
[Laughter] Yeah!
[Groaning]
Take that!
[Laughs]
- Aah!
- Aah! Oh, no! Aah!
[Laughs]
Hey!
Look at me now, dad!
[Thunk]
Aah!
[Groans]
[Boulders crashing]
[Labored breathing]
I suppose
you're wondering, player,
why record myself
breathing weird
and letting you destroy me.
Because I am a man of honor.
So you've earned
the pleasure of my death.
But I didn't.
I'm not the one that beat you.
Yes, you are.
We're forfeiting.
Warning.
Player forfeit in 30.
Gilbert, you're right.
You were more his son than me.
You took all his crap
and you didn't even
get to take his name.
He once sat on me in church
just so he could see better.
We've only been playing
this game a couple of hours.
You've been playing it
your whole life,
and now it's time
for your reward, brother.
So get in there
and kill our dad.
Thank you, Pierce.
Wait a second.
Here, take this.
- Oh!
- Whoa!
- You may need it.
- Oh, Pierce.
You really don't know how
this works, do you?
Are you always carrying that?
Not in the shower.
[Sighs]
[Click, explosion]
[Electronic beeps]
[Winning music playing]
[Fireworks exploding]
I'd like to thank you again
for today
and offer my apologies
for my conduct.
I wasn't myself.
Family can make a person
do a lot of crazy things.
I understand. I have an uncle
who makes his own pizza.
- Don't worry about it.
- Yeah, totally.
If it would make it up
to any of you in any way,
there's a bar in town
called Skeepers,
and I hear they make
a specialty drink...
a Margarita, in fact,
and it's served in a glass
an entire yard long.
- My treat.
- Score.
This is the greatest day
of my life.
I've always wanted
to have a brother.
Hey, hey, settle a bet.
The word "mulatto,"
is it okay or just borderline?
- We apologize for him.
- Oh, that's okay. He's family.
[Typing]
Hilda, my love, I said
I'd come back for you.
I just think that
in a parallel universe,
- Blorgons are...
- Hold on.
A baby.
I wasn't expecting this.
Guess we'll have to support it.
I guess I could get
some kind of job,
maybe at Beans and More.
I'll probably have to work
double shifts, but...
oh, I see.
While you're off, climbing
the ladder at Beans and More,
I'll just stay home
and raise him alone.
That's fine. I'll just
give up on my dreams.
- Here we go.
- What?
He needs to learn
a strong man can cry.
So, what were you saying
about Blorgons?
Blorgons...
in this other universe,
they're actually called
Glorbons.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org