Look, 12:00.
History of Ice Cream class
is letting out.
- It's as informative as it is delicious.
- That class should've been ours.
I hear the final is a sundae bar.
I don't get history. If I wanted
to know what happened in Europe...
a long time ago,
I'd watch Game of Thrones.
That show takes place in a fantasy
realm. This is about the real world.
- Not the show.
- You need to think before you speak.
I hear this teacher's a real hard-ass.
He's British and has a degree.
I can't have a hard-buns teacher.
I'm starting a business.
When am I supposed to see my family?
Ben took his first steps without me.
Quick impression... who am I?
You guys.
Dead on.
I know The History of Ice Cream
would have been fun...
but not only will this class be much
less likely to give us type 2 diabetes...
we might actually learn so...
Son of a bitch.
Those annoying Germans are back?
I thought they transferred after
they lost their foosball scholarship.
I heard they were juicing.
No, them leaving would mean
Greendale got slightly better...
which, as we know,
does not happen.
Lukas, Karl,
I see you've grown a new douche bag.
My name is Reinhold.
I believe you know my brother,
Juergen.
There was some bad blood
between you two, ja?
Don't worry.
If there is one thing Germans don't do,
it's hold a grudge.
- Unless we're talking Die Hard 3.
- Or the 20th century.
Morning, everyone.
Morning, sir.
I am Professor Cornwallis.
I know what you're all thinking,
and the answer is yes.
I am a direct descendant
of General Sir Charles Cornwallis...
who surrendered the British forces
at Yorktown.
- Was anyone thinking that?
- No.
History is written by the victors.
Of course, we all know the quote.
What does it mean?
According to Oxford University...
it means that my 20 years'
loyal service there...
means nothing
next to a little slipup with a coed.
But what it really means...
is that history can be seen
from a multitude of vantage points.
So for your first test on Monday...
Oh, come on.
I'm confused.
When do we get our ice cream?
I want to challenge you
to look at history from all perspectives.
How would the story read
if it was written not by the victors...
but by the vanquished?
Ja, how indeed?
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I was recalling a very funny episode
of the German version of The Nanny.
Franlein gets a...
It wouldn't translate.
♪ Give me some more
Time in a dream ♪
♪ Give me the hope
To run out of steam ♪
♪ Somebody said It can be here ♪
♪ We could be roped up
Tied up dead in a year ♪
♪ I can't count the reasons
I should stay ♪
♪ One by one they all
Just fade away ♪
And I still have those pants.
True story.
Oh, we have fun.
Sorry. I should've realised
that might be startling.
Dr. Ken Kedan, Greater Greendale
Mental Health Services.
Kevin, does this gentleman
look familiar to you?
I'm sorry. He doesn't.
Kevin? His name is Chang.
Oh, of course.
That explains the note.
"Hello, my name is Kevin.
I have Changnesia"? What is that?
Not uncommon for victims
of memory loss...
to experience syntactical confusion.
Thus, the inappropriate insertion of...
- his name into an unrelated phrase.
- No, he's always dean that.
Once we learned of the connection
to Greendale, we realised...
it'd be the perfect environment
for immersive therapy.
What? No, absolutely not.
I can't have an unbalanced nut job
traipsing around on my campus.
Put that on the rack, put that
in the fridge. Get him out of here.
Sorry. Your school board
already signed off on it.
Kevin is now your responsibility.
- I just felt a disturbance.
- Did you have dairy this morning?
Could be that.
Or it could be that great evil is nearby.
I'll take a provisional Lactaid.
Won't be needing the Lactaid.
Guys, this is our study room.
Please leave. And take that
mushroom cloud of Drakkar with you.
Why must he hurt so with his words?
He's like a less funny Hans Rickles.
I'm not here to argue, Angela Jerk-els.
Beat it.
Someone must've changed
the channel to USA...
because I just watched
a Burn Notice.
Who's Angela Jerk-els?
I can assure you, we are here
for no reason other than to study.
Our usual off-campus haunt,
Der Kaffee Hausen is closed...
for the shooting
of an esoteric art film.
Tomorrow it shall reopen...
und we shall be out
of your heavily product-laden hair.
Jeff, it's just a little table
in the corner of the room.
- Why don't we just let them have it?
- That's called appeasement.
And everyone knows if you give
the Germans something small...
like the study room or Austria...
they end up wanting something big,
like Earth.
Jeff's right. If there were more people
in the world like Annie...
we'd all be speaking Vietnamese
right now.
That was my war.
I had fiashbacks for years.
- Pierce, you moved to Canada.
- And it was hell.
Those people call ham "bacon."
This is silly.
I'm just gonna walk over there...
and tell them they are welcome
to share our room.
Delightful.
So today, we study in here.
Und tonight, we dine in hell.
Doktor Blitz,
Knight of the Atlantis Guild...
wielder of the four-pronged
trident in "Spawncraft."
- How did you know?
- I recognised your catchphrase:
"Tonight we dine in hell!"
I'm Spacetimer 8032.
- You are Spacetimer 8032?
- The one and only.
It's wonderful to meet you, brother.
What was that all about?
You two seemed pretty chummy.
That man saved my life.
In a video game.
Let me get this as straight
as I can get things.
You authorised this? After everything
that happened last year?
Hear us out.
They offered money.
Did it ever occur to you
that this man is a psychopath...
who may be faking
his own Changnesia?
Now he has me saying it.
Amdeansia. Amdeansia.
I'm all turned around.
If he is faking,
you're welcome to prove it.
We get the money either way.
Oh, I will prove it.
And I'll have fun doing it.
Now, what to wear?
See? I know those guys
were annoying yesterday...
but aren't you glad we didn't turn it
into a whole big macho war thing?
You're right.
I can't believe I doubted you.
Hey, what's that sound you make
when you see something shocking?
- Yeah, that's it.
- What are you doing at our table?
What happened
to Der Kaffee Hausen?
Our time in this room yesterday
proved more pleasant than expected.
It's got a good energy.
That table is ours. This room is ours.
You guys need to leave.
- Hey, Karl.
- Hi, Abed.
I am afraid it is you
who must do the making like a tree...
which is to say leaving. Security.
- You want us to leave?
- There a problem here?
Yeah. These Düssel-dorks won't
leave our study room.
Nice. I don't understand
any of these puns.
- I think I need to learn history.
- You have a sign-in sheet?
You're asking for our papers?
I thought this was America,
not Arizona.
We have a sign-in sheet. Lukas.
Perhaps we should all just go home
and see our families...
and think things through?
Looks like the room is theirs.
Shirley, call your babysitter,
because this means...
Let me guess.
War?
- Let the lady finish her sentence.
- Thank you, Jeff.
War. Yeah.
We'd like to sign out Study Room F.
It would appear that in this battle,
our bulge was a little bit bigger.
Guten bye-bye. Excuse me.
Don't touch.
Damn them
and their perfectly crafted timepieces.
What else do you have available?
It's like a Darren Aronofsky film.
I'll get this. My fifth father-in-law
was an electrician.
You pick up a thing or two.
Everybody grab me, please!
Nobody grab him.
Pierce, just let go.
- You'd like that, wouldn't you?
- Of the thing, Pierce.
It smells like barbecue.
We're getting up earlier tomorrow.
Oh, look at them.
Hi.
Thanks again for taking me in.
We must have been great pals
before my Changnesia, huh?
Oh, my... That's it. You may
have fooled that handsome doctor...
but you can't fool me.
Oh, how convenient.
Showing up here with Changnesia
after you staged a coup...
almost blew up the school...
and locked me in a basement
for months.
Without so much as a drop
of moisturizer.
I did all that?
I mean, Chang did all that?
If that's true, then Chang, who is me,
deserves to go to jail.
Well, he did.
And you do.
This is the worst thing that's happened
to me in my 96 hours of memory.
And that failed ventriloquist's name
was Slobodan Milošević.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yes.
For the essay portion of your test
on Monday...
you will be asked to describe
a historical battle...
from the perspectives
of both the winners and the losers.
No dioramas.
Guten luck on the examination.
We will be preparing for it...
in Study Room F, as in "fictory."
I like the way your old chair cradles
mein k'naidels.
I just made that up.
English is my second language.
Jeff, stop.
- It's over.
- No.
These guys are horrible.
- Totally. Except Karl.
- Really, Abed?
Karl's not horrible?
Even though he took your home?
When I was growing up,
it was just me and my mom.
I didn't have much of a family,
that is, until I met you guys.
So excuse me if I'm not willing
to give up the place...
where we became a family.
So, what are we gonna do?
We literally can't get up any earlier.
Many years ago, before the concept
of "too soon" existed...
there was a show about a bunch of
goofy Nazis running a prison camp...
- and that show was called...
- Hogan's Heroes?
- Hogan's Heroes.
- Yeah.
And while, for a latchkey kid
with no Jewish friends...
it was a bit desensitizing...
it still taught me
that the loveable misfits always win...
and the bumbling Germans
always lose.
All we need is a clever ruse...
Strike that. All we need is a ruse.
You had me at "ruse."
- That was the last thing I said.
- Good thing you said it.
Welcome to Oktoberfest.
- What is this?
- Call it a peace offering.
You won, we lost.
Let's end this dumb war and move on.
Care for some authentic blutwurst?
This stuff's the real deal.
We got it down in Little Munich.
It's been banned by the FDA.
No, Karl.
That blutwurst was probably injected...
with a laxative to make us
pull a Grete Waitz in our trousers.
I promise you, there's nothing gross
in this sausage.
It's just pig's blood
stuffed into a cow's intestine.
Gott,
that must be nearly 100 luftballons.
Idiot. Do not accept their gifts.
Something is clearly up.
Please, these are just small tokens
of our friendship.
Oh, come on.
Dirndls, blutwurst, luftballons.
A cartoonishly large cake.
This is a ruse.
It is exactly like an episode
of Hogan's Villains.
Ruse? This is no ruse.
Just take that large cake
back to the study room...
and enjoy it there.
So there's nothing hiding inside
this giant German chocolate cake?
Ask Abed.
You can trust him. He's a friend.
Nope. Just solid cake.
Then you wouldn't mind
if I cut the cake?
Or save it for later.
You don't have to share it.
Shirley stayed up all night
baking that for you.
I just used the eggs I would've used
for my son's breakfast.
But it would be so easy for me
to carve into this cake...
and serve us all.
Wait!
Damn it. Sorry. We thought
you were stupider than this.
Troy.
Should I release the tear gas
or has that ship sailed?
An excellent attempt, Winger,
but we are smarter than you.
And once again, it shall be us...
who are savouring the smooth
and somewhat hoppy taste of victory.
Beer me, bitte.
Here you go.
As they say in Ferris Bueller,
"dankeschön."
And as they say
in the movie Gotcha!:
Gotcha.
- Busted.
- Busted? For what?
But there were dozens of students
at that Oktoberfest.
But you were the only
German students...
celebrating German culture.
And here at Greendale,
that is a big fat no-no.
We frown on anyone celebrating
their own cultural heritage.
I mean, if the Hasidic Student Union
wants to host a Kwanzaa celebration...
you go, Jews.
Hanukkah? No, sir.
It's why I keep a detailed list
of every student's race and nationality.
To prevent racism and nationalism.
This is an outrage.
Relax. It's not like you're expelled.
You're just banned
from certain campus amenities.
Water fountains, swimming pools.
Most of these are water-based.
Oh, and the study rooms.
I gotta take this. Bye-bye.
Dean Pelton. If I don't offer you
a receipt, your education is free.
Chang did what?
Oh, cool.
What are we protesting?
You guys. You've been hogging
that study room for three years.
Somebody finally stood up to you,
and you had them banned.
Why must our people
always be the victims?
- What do we want?
- Justice!
- When do we want it?
- Now!
- What do we want?
- Justice!
Oh, my God.
This whole time we thought
the Germans were the Germans...
but it turns out,
we're the Germans.
Hang on. You guys are all siding
with the Germans?
You realise these guys are, like,
contractor-grade tools.
They signed out that room
fair and square...
and then you had to take it too far,
like you always do with that room.
- Yeah!
Damn it!
I signed this room out!
And I have a final tomorrow!
They lost a pen.
Come back in a few hours,
we're playing "Dungeons & Dragons."
- Yes?
- I left my notebook.
Come back later.
I'm trying to prove a point.
You're like those guys
on Hogan's Heroes, the Nazis.
You take that back.
I'm Jewish.
Yeah, Leonard. Don't call me a Nazi.
You are wearing an SS T-shirt.
Open 2.
- What are you doing here?
- You, sir, have been bailed out.
We are going to nurse you
back to health.
But why? Why take me back in
after everything I did to you?
When I heard you had checked into
jail, I realised you couldn't be faking.
The real Chang would never
have remorse for what he did.
I believe you, Kevin.
Plus, curing Changnesia,
that's a human-interest story.
Puts Greendale on the map.
But your health comes second...
First, to the school.
Oh, let's not hug.
Do you mind getting my...? Okay.
Probably shouldn't step on it.
I feel guilty eating this cake.
And not for the usual reasons.
This is what happens
when a group of people...
blindly follows a charismatic
golden-throated leader.
Are you comparing me to Hitler?
- Yeah.
- There are similarities.
Hang on.
Nobody's even willing to consider...
that I might be the Hitler
of this group?
We were the good guys. How could
everybody think we're the bad guys?
We are. When Karl and I were raiding
the Diamond North Caves...
I was facing 50 death beetles.
He saved me.
When I had a chance to return
the favour, I told him it was solid cake.
You were just following orders.
There's probably a way
I can make it up to him.
- I'll give him my four-pronged trident.
- Why not call it a quadrident?
There you people are.
I believe we have something
to discuss.
Oh, my God.
You clever British bastard.
- You set this up to teach us a lesson.
- What?
Making the school pretend
to hate us...
to show us that one man's hero
is another man's villain.
Of course. We aren't Nazis.
I tip my cap to you, sir.
Lesson learned.
Are you actually suggesting
that a professor at Greendale...
would set up an elaborate ruse
just to teach seven students a lesson?
- Yes.
- That's a Wednesday.
Oh, my God.
I've made a terrible mistake
coming here.
So this wasn't part of the class?
Then why are you here?
You had a test today,
and you all missed it.
F's for everyone.
Maybe it's not too late
to get out of my contract.
- I really am Hitler.
- Yeah.
So it's just decided?
No vote or anything?
I hate this. I wish there was a way
that we could make it up to people.
That's it.
We need to make reparations.
We have to start giving back...
because Greendale has given us
so much.
It gave us the study room.
And that study room is our home.
But our home
is more than those four walls.
And our family
is more than the seven of us.
It's all of Greendale.
And everyone deserves to have
what we have.
What do you know?
Greendale just got slightly better.
It's good to be back.
Should we go celebrate
at Skeeper's?
Oh, come on, Shirley.
We all have lives.
There you are. I am so proud how
you stepped up and made amends.
And everyone forgave you.
Because when it comes
right down to it...
Greendale's a forgiving place.
It really is.
Keep that in mind
the next 20 seconds.
- Remember that people can Chang.
- People can what?
Hi, I'm Kevin.
He has Changnesia.
- And you know what that sound is.
- It's the Troy and Abed podcast.
Sponsored by Shirley's Sandwiches,
home of the fried-chicken skin wrap.
Is it inside? Is it outside?
You find out.
- Our guest today is from Germany.
- Karl, guten tag. How are you doing?
Great.
Now's the part where we get real.
Friendship, loyalty,
betrayal, redemption.
- Is this an apology?
- Yes.
For being a guest,
we want you to have this.
Gift certificate to Shirley's Sandwiches,
home of the triple-fried Monte Cristo.
- We challenge you to taste the bread.
- This coupon is a $5 bill.
That's all the time we have.
For Troy Barnes, I'm Abed Nadir.
For Abed Nadir, I'm Troy Barnes.
- And we're out.
Thanks for doing this.
So will you be
on my podcast tomorrow?
We've got a thing.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org