- Troy and Abed back from summer.
Wait a minute.
Something's changed.
There's 12 additional thumbtacks on
that board. They're driving me crazy.
No, I meant this.
Trying out the hipster look.
It's cool, but also not.
Hey, guys, have a good summer?
Take them off.
Happy first day of school.
Good morning. I brought brownies.
Congratulations, it's me.
I see we've all reinvented ourselves
over the summer.
A little late
to the hipster party much?
A little much on the "much" much?
We should get to class.
Where's Pierce?
- I don't know.
- Hey-o.
Sorry, I'm late.
Damn Mexican cleaning woman
did a cha-cha on my glasses...
so I gotta wear this old pair.
Abed. Abed.
- Abed.
- Yeah?
- Did you go to your happy place?
- Yeah.
Did you envision a babbling brook
like I described?
I started with a babbling brook, then
layered in elements from our world.
I'm sure fans of the brook
will complain, but it was limiting.
- Keep it simple.
- It was a babbling brook.
Okay. Here's the deal, Jessica Biel.
The first day of senior year
is emotional for everyone...
so I hereby therapize you
to go to your happy place...
whenever you feel stressed.
- I found my lucky notebook.
- Found my lucky charm.
Abed, you ready for our last
first day of school?
Are you ready, buddy?
I just need a minute.
This is my show It's about me.
And all my friends on Abed TV.
My happy place Nothing but fun.
Nothing but laughs and smiles
And then we rerun.
For those times
When life's too hard to face
I'll find some happy
In my happy place
Abed's Happy Community College
Show is filmed...
before a live audience
inside of my head.
I can't believe we're getting
into this class.
I can't believe
there's a History of Ice Cream.
Seniors.
Hey.
There they are.
I missed you guys.
- Seniors.
- Speaking of seniors...
I've decided
I'm gonna do senioritis this year.
You know, just hanging out...
and blowing off classes,
pulling pranks, not saying my G's.
I'll pull some pranks with you.
Okay. Or Jeff or whoever. You know,
whoever's around, whatever.
Abed, after class we're still doing
our first-day-of-school tradition?
- You know it.
- We make wishes in the fountain.
Fellas, I hate to tell you,
wishes aren't real.
If you want something bad,
you have to work for it.
- Or use a spell.
- All of our wishes come true.
Last year, Troy wished
we got Bin Laden and the Dorito taco.
But Obama got credit for both.
Could you wish for Jeff
to be on time?
No. No wasting wishes
on impossibilities.
We have to make this year count,
especially since it's the last one.
Oh, no. Is all this for
The History of Ice Cream?
Overbooked.
It's first come, first serve now.
- Just like real ice cream.
- Guys, over here.
- Oh, Jeffrey.
- Jeff.
Jeff, I can't believe
that you came early.
Don't you read Garrett's Twitter?
He posted a crisis alert about it.
I came early to save seats.
Oh, you know what, girls?
I gave you the old flyer.
Instagram for Besties is in Room 44.
Showing up early, helping others,
sending girls away?
Could this be
a whole new Jeff Winger?
Don't ruin it by approving it.
Oh, so that's progressed.
I mean, it's progressed,
but it hasn't "progressed" progressed.
It's progressive.
- Good luck, Troy.
- Hey.
You can't just walk in here.
I've been pissing in jars for an hour
trying to keep this seat.
Leonard, keep those...
Yes. All right, all right, all right.
Simmer dean.
This can't be good.
He's dressed as himself.
Greendale's registration system
has been hacked.
That's right. Someone hacked
into the supply closet...
and counterfeited these
History of Ice Cream admission cards.
Whoever did this is very good.
There is only one fair way
to solve this.
So follow me to...
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
the Hunger Deans.
Thank you. Thank you.
There are 35 tests of strength
and agility.
The winner of each one
of these contests...
will be awarded a red rubber ball.
No ball, no ice cream.
And these
are impossible to counterfeit...
because each one has been marked
by my distinct bite print.
- Oh, Lord, no.
- Yeah.
We need to take this class. It's the only
history credit this semester.
Whatevs. We'll take it next semes.
Ter. Semester.
But I need it now.
Okay.
I took some extra classes online...
and I'm one history credit away
from graduating.
Jeff, you're graduating early?
Well, graduating after 30
can't be characterised as early.
- When were you gonna tell us, Jeff?
- I was working on a speech.
Believe me, it tied in a lot of things.
There was a lot of resolutions
and epiphanies.
It would have gone down
a lot better...
after we had taken
the ice cream class together.
That's why you held our seats,
your own selfish reasons.
No, I want us
to take the class together.
I just want it to be the last class
we take together.
- I should've phrased that differently.
- Win your ball. What do I care?
I've got a senior prank to pull.
Shirley.
Abed, ready to make some wishes?
Make chocolate hot dogs a reality?
Go with Britta.
I'll just hang out here and watch.
- Really? Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
F-I-N-E or F-Y-N-E?
We made one of them a code
for "not fine."
F-Y-N-E.
Okay, he's fine. Let's go.
See you around, old Jeff.
No, new Jeff. New Jeff does not
just look out for himself.
New Jeff is gonna win
seven red balls.
Because he is not gonna take that
class unless you guys are with me.
Look, we're gonna have to leave
this place sometime.
Like an ice cream cone
melting in the sun...
our time here can't last forever.
That was part of the speech
I was writing.
- Hey, guys. What's going on?
- Oh, just making plans for the future.
Can't stay at Greendale forever.
Hey, is mine different than yours?
Look out below.
Coming in for a Ian-dean.
Amelia Earhart?
Close. I am America's sexiest aviator,
Leo DiCaprio.
And just as his character
lost his mind...
so have I lost
your student records.
What? I can't believe it.
Yeah, Amelia Earhart
would have been faster.
As you know, our student records
are stored on a Microsoft Paint file...
which I was assured
was future-proof.
Meanwhile, our extended warranty
is not being honoured...
by the restaurant
that used to be Circuit City.
But I think the fairest way
to handle this...
is to have everyone
repeat the last three years.
You can't be serious.
In-dean, I am.
We're gonna be here forever.
Forever.
I'm gonna stay in here forever.
Gentlemen and ladies.
My first red ball is way up high.
To touch my ball, first touch the sky.
Go.
- Give it up, Leonard.
- I'm gonna eat your ice cream, Winger.
- You? You're premed.
- I want ice cream.
Yeah, well,
I wanna graduate with dignity.
Come over.
Jeff's really going after that ball.
There's gotta be a joke in there
somewhere.
That's my first ball. New Jeff.
Give me a minute.
This one! This one!
No.
If we're doing the first three years
over again, I could change majors.
I've always been curious
about forensics.
Did you know you could major
in antics?
You need a tomfoolery prereq.
They waive it for women.
This is lunacy. We are not gonna
start over as freshmen.
Hey, there's a freshman mixer tonight.
Are you guys freshmen?
We can be.
This prank is amazing.
He's gonna come in here later...
and have the creepy feeling
someone was in here.
- We should go before we get caught.
- Aren't we gonna do something?
Do something?
All right. A prank on a prank.
Let's move everything on his desk
over an inch except his stapler.
Then he'll think we moved his stapler.
There's so many levels to this.
How about we fill his car
with popcorn?
That sounds messy.
Okay. Keys. Keys.
Okay, I'm the dean.
I come into my office,
turn on the light.
"Oh, my, did my stapler grow legs
and move?"
Then come over here for coffee.
I would hide my keys in...
- Heels.
- You got skills.
Look who got his ball.
Not my ball, your ball.
I wanted you guys to see it.
- New Jeff.
- Is that blood on your shirt?
Oh, no, it's cool. It's Leonard's.
Two balls.
This is gonna be so good
when I finally get it.
It's a little weird doing this
without Abed.
Come on, it'll be fun.
I'll put my Britta twist on it.
I got skills. I got skills.
- Sorry.
- Let's get this started.
We always do the first one together.
One, two, three.
- A great school year.
- A thousand wishes.
Great school year?
- First wish is always for 1000 wishes.
- But we have all these coins.
- Yeah, but the coins aren't the wishes.
- Oh, I didn't know that.
I wish for Britta
to have 499 of my remaining wishes.
Thank you.
- I wish to end all wars.
- That's another rule.
No wishes containing the word "all."
Guaranteed ironic consequences.
I don't think
anyone's gonna miss wars.
Star Wars, thumb wars.
Wow, Storage Wars.
Fine.
- You can't get in.
- I'm taking that penny back.
I already told you,
the pennies aren't wishes.
You can't flip a wish.
That's ridiculous.
- Your rules are ridiculous.
- They're Abed's rules.
They're awesome.
They always work.
Well, Abed's not here...
so unwish.
- You can't do that.
- I just did.
- Unwish.
- No. Rewish.
- Un-unwish.
- Give me! Unwish!
- No!
No! Oh, I'm sorry.
What...? You're helping me!
You're helping. I like it.
Unwish!
- Unwish!
- Why does this feel good?
Stupid, selfish Jeff coming here
ruining our senior year.
Great, my G's are back.
It's crummy Jeff is leaving early,
but we're all graduating eventually.
But why the rush? What, so Jeff can
run off and be a gross lawyer again?
Troy and Abed start drinking coffee?
I become a boring
hospital administrator?
- Who wants to do that?
- You do. Right?
Hospital administration.
Can't wait to be buried alive under
a pile of paperwork and bedpans...
trying to summon the courage
to ask out Dr. Patel...
the gorgeous neurosurgeon
who doesn't know I exist.
This isn't a conversation, is it?
The sad, slow march
toward death begins.
Senioritis.
Ready, set...
Third ball.
Fourth ball.
Well, well, well.
Looks like someone
wants to be a hero.
A big man.
A huge, throbbing, sweaty...
I wanna get my history credit
and get out of here.
And I just need to know
how bad you want it.
Next competition will be particularly
difficult for some of you...
because it requires
complete emotional commitment.
The tango. I will be the judge.
There can only be one winner...
so choose your partners wisely.
Come on, Winger.
Water under the bridge, right?
- Partners?
- Sorry, my dance card's full.
For my partner
in the tango competition, I choose...
the dean.
The fountain works.
All these balls.
I'm so close, I can taste it.
Pierce, only you could turn
a freshman mixer into a disaster!
I was this close
to getting those two girls.
Look how close you're holding your
fingers together. That's your penis.
Guys, great news.
After just one forensics class, I found
a way to retrieve our student records.
It turns out there's a backup,
and it's in this safe.
- I have a theory, dean.
- Do tell.
I don't think you want me
to graduate.
Don't be absurd, Jeffrey.
I want success
for all Greendale students.
Oh, really? Then answer me this.
What happened
to the other history class?
What other history class?
The second history class,
the one that actually taught history...
that disappeared from the schedule
after I took summer classes.
You're telling yourself a fantasy.
Who really made those counterfeited
ice cream tickets?
Who's so good
that they got your handwriting...
with its hearts and flourishes?
Oh, God, you're right.
I can't let you go, Jeffrey.
You weren't supposed to compete.
You were supposed to walk away
with the group.
You can't not get rid of me
that easily.
Oh, God. Why'd I make it feats
of strength and grace?
It's... It's as if I wanted you to win.
But that can't be true.
Smile.
Best friends.
So let's hug it out. Okay.
Here. One more ball to go.
But it's another dance contest,
so I think I got it.
What's wrong with Abed?
Don't. We're redoing our first
three years. That's what I want.
It's okay, Abed. Here's a trick I use
when I feel overwhelmed.
Just imagine a happy place
and then go there.
Greendale Babies.
They're happy and they're free.
Fun for you and me.
Greendale Babies forever.
Greendale Babies will be right back.
Forever.
Pierce, what did you do to Abed?
Gay balls.
Nailed it.
- Don't ask.
- Don't tell.
Poor Abed.
Is he in his imagination emporium?
Dreamatorium?
No, this seems like something new.
Abed was having some anxiety
about all the changes this year...
so I may have told him
to go to a happy place in his mind.
You told him to go somewhere
in his mind?
Do you realise who you told that to?
The last competition to win a red ball
begins in one minute.
Honestly, Jeff, you can go.
No one will think you're selfish.
- This looks bad.
- I wish I hadn't broken Abed.
There is one thing we could try.
Oh, okay.
Hey, let's play pretend.
Yeah, we could be cowboys.
We could be spacemen.
That's right, baby Pierce.
We can play forever.
- It's not working.
- What's not working?
Okay, contestants,
final competition begins right now.
God, I hate new Jeff.
Hey, guys, I have something to say.
Like always.
I was just outside Babyville.
- There's nothing outside Babyville.
- You know what? There is.
And it was scary,
because change is always scary.
But then I thought of you guys,
and I wasn't so scared.
Abed, when you brought
this group together...
you changed our lives.
But then we changed each other.
And we're gonna keep changing
in unexpected ways.
We'll still be friends even if we don't
all become professors at Greendale...
blind/blonde marathon up next
open a restaurant...
or move into the same
apartment building after Pierce dies.
And even if we go somewhere,
we're not going anywhere.
That was a killer speech, Jeff.
I didn't say anything.
I literally just walked up.
I made the speech for you.
It hit all the right notes.
I was trying to hang on to this moment
because I was afraid of the future.
But then I realised
all of this was once the future.
It was different from what I'd known
before, and it was happening so fast.
But in the end, or in the now, I guess,
it turned out great.
And just like ice cream, we've melted
together and made a new...
I just had to run the scenario
to figure it out.
- Sorry I missed the fountain.
- It's okay.
Britta introduced a new rule:
No rules.
We can discuss it.
When they were incepting,
I got their balls.
- Hey. That... Over there.
- Come on, get out of the way.
Now that we're out
of History of Ice Cream...
I can finally take
Advanced Claims Denial.
You should take forensics.
Can somebody tell me
what the hell we just did?
Jeffrey. Jeffrey, wait.
What are you...? You smell
like the floor of a movie theatre.
Yeah, but not for the usual reasons.
I have had the worst day.
Our dance photo didn't come out,
someone moved my stapler...
and, worst of all, I hurt you.
You'll be happy to know that we'll
be offering another history class...
because I care about you.
Not because I found out
if we don't offer a real history class...
we'll lose $40,000 in grant money.
Thank you, dean. You didn't have
to come all this way to tell me that.
Oh, no, it wasn't a problem.
It's on my way.
Tell me you're breaking into
that condo.
No, I bought it.
Now we'll be like almost roomies.
Oh, good, you got wine.
I've got Friends With Benefits.
No subtext.
I don't know why I was so worried
about change.
This year's gonna be great.
I'll be right over.
"Hello. My name is Kevin.
I have Changnesia."
- Sure this will work?
- Guaranteed to. It's an antic.
Not so fast, you two.
- Get ready to run.
- In these heels?
Where'd you girls get those dresses?
They're fabulous.
They're charming.
- Not so fast, mister.
- Excuse you?
Excuse me.
Thank you, sir. Not for you.
- Hello, it's Britta.
- Okay, I know a man when I see one.
Oh, Lord, no
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org