His name is Archie DeCoste.
Age: 22.
Total years spent in high school: Seven.
SAT score: Zero.
And he was recently arrested for
selling marijuana to a police officer...
at a police station.
So you want us to help
you recruit this idiot...
instead of an honours student
or a science genius?
Do we go to the same Greendale?
But let me reveal the fortune
inside this cookie.
Family net worth: $8 million.
Ladies and gentlemen...
this is what we in the community
college recruiting game call a whale.
The perfect mix of low intellect,
high lack of ambition...
and limitless parental support.
So a rich dumb-dumb
who will never graduate...
and keep dropping money into
the school. Got it.
Is there much money in this...
or is it like that endorsement deal
you made with Let's Potato Chips?
If you don't like the crispy-licious
taste of Let's...
feel free to eat
that other greasy brand.
- Splingles? Not this guy.
- Thank you, Troy.
And I will explain the value
of this whale...
by describing one who's been
swimming right under your nose.
Pierce Hawthorne has taken 80 percent
of Greendale's classes more than twice.
He is the only Greendale student who
has ever paid for a premium locker...
or the extended pencil warranty.
Pierce cannot know about this,
okay?
He's a big baby who throws tantrums
when anyone else gets attention.
Remember when Kerri Strug
visited our campus?
That was horrible.
I have scheduled Archie's visit for
tomorrow when Pierce has no classes.
Guys, I'm asking,
as treasurer of the Forensics Club.
The dean said we could use
whale money for a new body farm.
- Who wants to help?
- I'm in. Sounds like a romper.
We do need money. The Biology
Department has been dissecting...
the same dead pig for 10 years.
If we land this kid,
we can buy a hundred dead pigs...
and make everybody happy.
I'll help, but I started a new PE class.
I've been avoiding it for three years,
but you can't run from running forever.
I'm in PE too.
I made room in my trophy case.
Then I remembered classes
don't give out trophies...
so I put a fishbowl there instead.
It's been quite the week.
So the rest of us will have
to pick up the slack...
and, yes, Jeffrey,
I assume you're out...
because of your track record
of literally being too cool for school.
Actually, you can count me in
on this one.
- What?
- You had me at "no Pierce."
He's been all over me lately
to hang out. It's weird.
You just want to be a part
of something.
Admit it, Thanksgiving softened
that Winger underbelly.
Britta.
Now, let's set sail
and hunt that whale.
- Yeah.
- Hey, let's do this.
You know
what the commercial says.
"Keep your damn hands
off my Let's."
♪ Give me some more
Time in a dream ♪
♪ Give me the hope
To run out of steam ♪
♪ Somebody said It can be here ♪
♪ We could be roped up
Tied up dead in a year ♪
♪ I can't count the reasons
I should stay ♪
♪ One by one they all
Just fade away ♪
Hey, Jeff, there you are.
I was thinking we could swing by
this great barbershop I know.
You're looking a little stubbly and
nobody handles a razor like an Italian.
They develop nimble fingers
from pleasing their mistresses.
Thank you for opening my eyes
to two new stereotypes.
Now, how can I put this?
No, I don't want to go.
Not now, not ever. No.
No prob.
We'll work around your skedge.
- Okay. Pierce is gone.
- Yes.
Walking Dead has left.
Resume Operation Deadliest Catch.
Archie is gonna love this banner.
The name-brand glitter really shows.
- School board guys in the hizzy.
- Richie. Richie, pace yourself.
Hey, there, dean.
Just thought we'd pop in...
and check on the big whale hunt.
What a day we have planned
for young Archie.
Library tour,
calculator lab demonstration...
And it all culminates in
the Spirit of Greendale reception.
Magnitude is a soft yes.
That's a get.
As much as we love
that Magnitude...
- your tour may be lacking a little...
- Tour sucks, bro.
- What?
- You gotta think big.
- Hookers, blow, hookers.
- Oh, my.
He's been mixing.
But there is some wisdom there.
We need this whale money.
The kid likes snowboarding.
Maybe Shaun White finds his way
on the faculty roster.
He likes to party.
Maybe Greendale suddenly has a frat.
The Delta Cubes or whatever.
- You're not considering this, are you?
- No. Greendale stands on its own.
No hookers, no blow,
no Shaun White frat.
College dean threatening
a fraternity.
You'll never shut down
the Delta Cubes.
- What?
- Delta Cubes, Delta Cubes...
Look, it's your call, Craig.
Don't let this whale swim away.
Cruise by Skeeper's Express
for a refill?
I'll second that motion.
Been working on victory dances.
Basketball...
football...
and crab soccer.
That one's the hard one.
That's nice.
Hey, when I was in grade school...
PE was about being picked on
and picked last...
but you'll put me on your team,
right?
Right. But also wrong.
- PE is about survival of the fittest.
- Line up, class.
Welcome to PEE.
I'm Coach Jason Chapman.
Physical Education Education?
Thought that was a typo
in the course "cartalog."
It started as a typo...
but it's grown into one of Greendale's
most successful programmes.
Anyone can take PE.
I teach my student coaches
to teach PE.
- Something funny, Coach Barnes?
- No, it's just...
You're teaching us
how to be gym teachers.
Gym teachers?
A gym is a building...
a man-made structure inside
which physical education teachers...
teach physical education
to physical education students.
Pop quiz, Coach Barnes. A student is
choking on a plastic golf ball.
- What do you do?
- I...
How many cones does it take
to line a soccer field?
What if students are talking
during stretches?
When my kids talk past bedtime,
I use my angry voice and I say:
"The next peep I hear will be the last."
And I give them one of these:
Not bad, Coach Bennett.
- Look at me.
- I see you.
Two hours late?
It's the lack of follow-through
that makes Archie so appealing...
but still send a text, right?
Okay, Abed, I told you
we're not doing the fraternity idea.
Delta Cubes will never die.
We've only just begun to fight.
You only began yesterday.
- Whale, ho. Look alive, everyone.
- What are you guys all doing out here?
- Oh, no. Pierce will ruin everything.
- What's an Archie?
- Why does he get a banner?
- Jeff, do something.
There you are, Pierce. Thought
you were gonna cancel our plans.
- Plans?
- To spend the entire day together...
away from everyone else.
Oh, yeah. Those plans.
Suck it, bozos. You're getting ditched
by the cool kids.
Oh, what a day we're gonna have.
Text me the instant I can ditch him.
Hey, guys. Sweet campus.
Welcome to Greendale.
I'm Bean Pelton. "Bean" Pelton?
Dean Pelton. Gosh, I'm nervous.
Please enroll in our school,
please, please.
Nice scooter, Archie.
City College gave it to me
as a present.
City College?
City College bought you a Vespa?
Brand-new.
So, Archie, have you heard about our
Half-Pipes and Hash Pipes class?
- Taught by Professor Shaun White.
- What?
Yeah. Let me tell you about it
in our Mountain Dew Cool Zone Tent.
Put up a tent,
write "Mountain Dew" on it.
Here we go. Let's keep going.
This is our library.
Okay. Archie, why don't you
hang 10 on the web...
while I talk business.
And you know what?
- You can take that computer.
- Sweet.
- I can drop it off an overpass.
- I shouldn't have heard that.
Dean, you're giving him
our computers?
Because he is a 22-year-old stonerhead
whose parents bought him a GED.
Which college is
he going to choose?
Vespa State
or Look at our Library University?
Those school board guys were right.
- Britta, where do we get drugs?
- Really?
Look who stumbled
onto the high road.
This is a slippery slope.
City College slipped that slope
when they slipped him that scooter.
But they sure slipped up
when they let him set foot on our soil.
Three, two, one.
Time!
Coach Barnes, it seems dodge ball
storage isn't quite in your skill set...
much like table tennis prep.
Excellent job, Coach Bennett.
You have the spatial reasoning skills
of a young Kevin Miller...
a really good PE teacher I know.
The skill of ranking others
in order of ability is crucial.
In this next drill,
our two best student coaches...
will split the rest of the class.
Coach Bennett, Coach Neil.
- Yeah.
- Pick your teams.
- Coach Donovan.
- Coach Goldman.
- Coach McKenna.
- Coach Cutler.
- Coach Winston.
- Coach Dornetto.
- Coach Guest.
- Coach Panos.
Choose wisely.
You're one decision away
from victory or defeat.
Coach Marzec.
Well picked, Coach Bennett.
Your team wins.
We won. Nice.
The barbershop.
A reminder of a bygone era
when men were men...
and women were sex cooks
who did laundry.
I've been getting a shave here
for decades.
And, apparently, reading the same
eight magazines the entire time.
Yeah, National Geographic's got some
tribal boob shots that are exquisite.
There's something about a breast that's
never been touched by white hands.
You are a complicated man.
Silvio, spin up lucky number seven.
You know what?
That feels good, I'll give you that.
Now that soda goblet gets
you free refills in the cafeteria...
and it was painted
by our Professor Ed Hardy.
- Who teaches bikini class.
- Oh, yeah!
Check out that bling. I want that.
You heard him, Annie.
Bling the king.
- Just take it off of him. There you go.
- Thank you.
Delta Cubes, prepare to bond
through embarrassment.
Pacifiers in.
Commence...
Code Dean! Code Dean!
Gosh dean it, Abed.
I told you, no fraternities!
There's soda all over my kicks.
Britta, give Archie your scarf
so he can dry his kicks.
- Dry his kicks. Put your back into it.
- No.
Line drawn.
If I wanted to wait on a rich man
hand and foot...
I would've gone to Dubai
with that sheik I met at Trader Joe's.
Don't worry about her, Archie.
Onward to the microbrew pizzatorium.
I think all a man needs in life is
a close shave, a cold beer...
and, you know,
maybe a faithful dog.
I had a chocolate lab growing up.
Rosie.
She used to wake me up
every morning by licking my feet.
Mine was Walter,
a German Shepherd.
Followed me to school every day.
I'd look out the window
and there he was...
dropping a steaming fat one
on the lawn.
Would someone please tell me
why I've been shaving my own face...
all these years like a sucker?
This state-of-the-art
mock locker room...
or "mocker room,"
simulates conditions...
- of an actual locker room.
- Don't we have an actual locker room?
You think you're ready for that,
Coach Barnes?
For our next drill, drama students
will play the role of PE students...
and you will oversee them
in a mocker room setting.
My character just had
her first period.
Mine has eczema.
- Coach Bennett, care to go first?
- Yes.
Keep your hands to yourself!
Running will get you five laps, mister.
Joey! I will come in that shower
and kick your bare ass!
Sorry, Coach Bennett.
I have never seen
such natural disciplinary skills.
You're up next, Coach Barnes.
Entertain us with your ineptitude.
How's the foam machine coming,
Leonard?
Memories will be made tonight.
Destiny. Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
Oh, I did get your Christmas card.
No. So... No, no. No time to pre-party.
You and the girls get in position
and wait for my signal.
- Strippers?
- Oh, tons.
It's good for the school.
The whale is here. Balloon drop, go.
There you go. Release the whores.
- Oh, yeah.
- No way!
Pierce.
I was wrong about this shop.
It really is special.
Well, if you like the place so much,
why don't you gay marry it?
You probably didn't notice, Jeff, but I've
been trying to get us some alone time.
I might have picked up on that.
I'm no stranger to father issues.
I know confronting your dad
couldn't have been easy.
And I just wanna say
I'm proud of you.
Well...
if you're so proud...
why don't you gay marry me?
You guys, behave! Hit the showers!
Everybody in the showers!
Please, stop hitting each other!
Hit the showers!
Cut! Scene!
Shirley, help. I can't control these
drama students or their characters.
No! No!
PE is survival of the fittest, Troy.
Hey, your phone's buzzing.
It's from Annie. You sly dog.
"Need more time.
Keep Pierce busy."
Keep me busy?
Look, the group is giving
some big shot a tour...
so it's my job to keep you busy.
You know how you get jealous.
So that's why you spent the day
with me?
- You drew the short straw.
- Well, that's how it started...
but I really did end up having
a good time.
Yeah, I used to regret not having a son
to bring here.
I'm glad I didn't have kids.
They just end up disappointing you.
So, Archie, having a good time?
Getting cray up in this club?
Sicker than ever, bro.
I've made my decision, dean.
I'm about to get all up
in this Greendale.
Human Beings, it's official.
Say hello to our newest Greendalian,
Archie DeCoste!
- Pop, pop!
I want that to be my thing now.
I don't think you can do that.
Magnitude, you're not to say
"pop, pop" ever again.
- Not pop?
- That's right. Find a new thing.
Get him out of here.
Here we go! We're back!
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Pop, pop!
Well, we did it.
We did what we had to do
and I feel great about it.
- It's all for Greendale.
- All for Greendale.
You look sad for someone
whose Forensics Club...
can now afford that
state-of-the-art body farm.
I can smell the corpses now.
None of this is weighing on you?
The only thing weighing on me
is tons and tons of whale money.
- Jeffrey.
- Hey. Landed a whale, huh?
Yeah, but I'm starting to feel
like maybe we...
Archie goes to Greendale now.
Moving forward, Annie.
We all paid a price.
Don't hear Jeffrey grumbling.
And he had to spend a day
with Walking Dead.
- That's true.
- You know what?
I can't believe I'm gonna say this.
Don't talk about Pierce like that.
Look, maybe the only reason...
he can be so unpleasant is
because we expect him to be.
If we don't treat him
like such a dick...
Well, he'll still be one
98 percent of the time...
but the 2 percent he's tolerable,
it might be worth it.
Who put the salt in his cereal, huh?
Look, I for one am still proud of
what we did for Greendale.
I've been up all night
trying out new catchphrases.
Diggity doo?
My God, what have we done?
I thought you dropped PEE.
I did, but I lost my keys
in the mocker.
I had to hitchhike home last night
in a burrito truck.
It's not as fun as it sounds.
- I'm sorry for how I acted in class.
- Don't apologise.
You were the fittest. You survived.
Still, no one deserves to be mocked
for being mock-locked...
in a mock locker.
Friends should help friends survive.
Oh, jeez! Hi.
So I'm gonna help you learn to teach
the most unteachable student there is.
Well done, Coach Barnes.
You as well, Coach Bennett.
You know, I was supposed to teach
you two to teach other people...
but, instead,
you ended up teaching me.
I did it.
I used the water fountain.
Archie, wake up.
Chillax, bro. It's not even noon.
I will neither chill nor relax.
All this hoopla is not
what Greendale really is.
Greendale is a nice welcome banner.
Greendale is a foamless cafeteria.
And Greendale is Magnitude saying,
"pop, pop."
Now, I am a man of very little integrity
and I let students get away...
with practically anything
on campus.
But I will not allow Greendale to lose
the things that make it Greendale.
I would love for you to enroll
in my school...
but I will not change it for you.
Greendale will stay Greendale,
no matter what.
You know what?
Everybody kisses my ass...
because my dad is loaded.
And they always give me free stuff,
like that Jet Ski I sunk.
But it would be pretty sweet
to be treated like a normal dude.
So I'm in.
Magnitude. You usually have
the perfect blend of brevity and wit...
that sums up situations like this.
Pop, pop!
- Oh, that's so good!
- So good!
I think we all learned today that
all human beings deserve dignity.
Delta Cubes, Delta Cubes,
Delta Cubes!
Delta Cubes,
Operation Slack Attack.
- Slack Attack?
- Oh, yeah.
Delta Cubes, Delta Cubes...
Mark my words, Delta Cubes,
you'll pay for this!
- Is this seat taken?
- Free country.
You know, I was thinking...
I might start coming here
more often.
I like the vibe.
You know what sport I never got?
Golf.
No argument here.
They lost me immediately
with the clown clothes.
You know, I belong to a dozen
country clubs. Never played.
I just hit on the waitresses.
Something about
a country club waitress...
that just makes you wanna
pay your dues every year.
Get your damn hand off of my Let's.
Honestly, after all that,
you still eat Splingles?
Yeah, Troy. Splingles have
30 percent less fat.
They're the fit chip.
You know, I kind of have a headache.
Maybe you should go home.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org