And then, in the season finale...
they reveal the whole thing was
a dream when the inspector wakes up...
next to a very young
and very topless Cheryl Tiegs.
Even Pierce loves this show now?
It's not Inspector Spacetime. It's
the American version, and a travesty.
- It's obvious, sexist, and the timing is...
- Honey, I'm dean.
- What the hell is wrong with you?
- Oh, Jeffrey, you are too much.
Why, I was doing some house cleaning
the other day, Deana Reed style...
when I realised, gosh, golly,
it's been ages since we had a dance.
So this Friday we are going back
to Greendale's golden age...
with an old-fashioned sock hop. Health
Department requires you wear shoes.
What a coinci-dean.
Throwing a dance the same day...
the CDC is confiscating
our drinking fountains.
- Well...
- Placating students with a fun event.
Classic bread and circuses.
In Rome, the emperor
would distract the populace...
by allocating money
for bread and circuses.
I'm trying to get away
from filtering everything through TV.
Time I showed growth.
"It's been three and a half seasons,"
the old me would've said.
Anyhoo, it is a Sadie Hawkins dance,
which means girls ask the boys.
Oh, I love those.
So, ladies, get out there
and make yourselves useful.
So there's one day a year when women
are free to choose their own mates?
What is this, cave-person times?
I have already started
on a Sadie Hawkins banner...
so this is pretty much set in stone.
Then maybe I'll throw my own dance.
One that doesn't conform
to your oppressive gender norms.
Give me a break.
You think a dance
can just be thrown together willy-nilly?
You think I decide to just do a
rainforest theme and buy palm fronds...
and rig the sprinkler system...?
I gotta write this down.
♪ Give me some more
Time in a dream ♪
♪ Give me the hope
To run out of steam ♪
♪ Somebody said It can be here ♪
♪ We could be roped up
Tied up dead in a year ♪
♪ I can't count the reasons
I should stay ♪
♪ One by one they all
Just fade away ♪
So, Britta, you're gonna throw
a protest dance? Is that a thing?
It is now.
And instead of Sadie Hawkins, my
dance will honour a real feminist icon...
someone who worked for
women's rights every day of the year...
Sophie B. Hawkins.
It wasn't really...
You know what, Britta? You're right.
A Sophie B. Hawkins dance
is just what this school needs.
Thanks, Jeff.
To celebrate Sophie B. Hawkins
and all her accomplishments.
Jeez, Winger, who's throwing
this dance, me or you?
Britta, I think you meant to say
Susan B. Anthony...
not Sophie B. Hawkins.
Britta for the whoops. Didn't you have
a cat named Susan B. Anthony?
How'd you Britta that?
I didn't Britta anything.
I meant Sophie B. Hawkins.
Really?
Your plan was to throw a dance...
honouring the singer of
"Damn I wish I Was Your Lover"?
And "As I Lay Me Down,"
which is the far superior song.
- That is a good song.
- Yeah.
Yes.
I am throwing
a Sophie B. Hawkins dance.
And it is gonna be amazing.
And when people come
they're gonna be like:
"Damn. She straight Britta'd this."
Because, that's right,
I'm taking it back.
You're really doing this? As one who
faked being a lawyer for seven years...
I appreciate your commitment to
the bit, but just admit you were wrong.
- So you can say I Britta'd it?
- Yes. That goes without saying.
But come on, it was a small mistake.
Call this off before it becomes a
full-scale "Brit-astrophe." I coined that.
If you don't wanna come to my dance...
you are free to go
to the Sadie Hawkins dance...
which will be happening
at the same time across the cafeteria.
- Our school has limited venue options.
- Oh, I wouldn't miss it.
Oh, and one last thing.
You do realise that if you call it
a Sophie B. Hawkins dance...
people will expect Sophie B. Hawkins
to actually be there, right?
Yes.
And when she comes I'm gonna be like
"I Will Remember You" doubting me.
That's a Sarah McLachlan song.
So, Abed, I was thinking about
what you said about showing growth...
and I was thinking
maybe one way to do that...
- is to meet new people and...
- Where's this going?
Can I set you up with a date
for the dance?
Blind date. I've always thought of myself
as more of an acquired taste, but okay.
If you're open to meeting someone,
there's eligible ladies in my church.
Shirley, I'm already finding
a date forAbed. I asked first.
There's no reason we can't both help.
Why don't we each pick a girl...
and let Abed decide,
instead of making it a competition?
- That's a competition.
- So it is.
Only for the loser.
- I need the computer.
- There are, like, dozens of computers.
- But my e-mail's on this one.
- Pierce.
- Jeez, what's up your butt?
- I may have lied about...
meaning Sophie B. Hawkins.
I didn't want Jeff to make fun.
And then I may have lied to cover
that lie, and now I'm in deep lies.
So what? So you told a lie, big deal.
The important thing is
never to admit it.
I was thinking about coming clean.
And give Winger the satisfaction?
Hell, no.
Besides, anything can happen between
now and the dance.
An asteroid could hit.
Do you wanna be the schmuck who
apologizes just before the world ends?
That kind of makes sense. Thank you.
Damn right it makes sense.
You're talking to the wisest man
on campus.
Now seriously,
I need to get to my e-mail.
- The post office is about to close.
- Pierce.
Check out my friend Britta's
Sophie B. Hawkins dance.
I'll be spinning hits
from yesterday and today.
Which are the same to me
since I have Changnesia.
The guy's Teflon.
No matter how much awful he does...
- he keeps getting another chance.
- He's like the Colin Farrell of people.
Wanna help me with Britta's dance?
Could be a chance for classic high jinks.
In the interest of growth
I'm avoiding high jinks.
And capers, romps, and exploits.
Escapades are a grey area.
Abed.
- This is Kat.
- Hi, Kat. Nice to meet you.
She wants to ask you something.
Isn't she perfect? She's like one of
those quirky girls from the movies.
I saw her in the cafeteria
trying to pay for lunch with a song.
I asked if you'd go to the Sadie Hawkins
dance with me into the balloon.
Could you hear it?
- Sure, I'd be happy to go with you.
- Super-duper, Mr. Cooper.
- Nice.
- So you chose the girl I picked.
It's cool. It's not like
it was a competition or anything.
Just be gentle when you tell Shirley
that she was the loser.
- Or do you want me to tell her?
- It's cool. I'll handle it.
So was that girl an alien
or a toddler with a growing disease?
Hello, Abed. I talked to a lovely girl...
at church and she'd be happy
to go to the dance.
- I appreciate it, but...
- I hope you will consider it...
and not just because saying no
would crush this girl...
but because I don't want you to miss
the opportunity of a lifetime.
You're right.
- I'd love to go to Britta's dance with her.
- Good, I'll set it up.
Oh, I hope this doesn't hurt
Annie's feelings.
- Maybe I should go tell her.
- No need. I'll handle it.
Oh, okay. Bye-bye.
At the risk of discovering I'm living
parallel lives like in Awake...
- don't you already have a date?
- Yep. Now I have two.
Which means I can do the
two-dates-in-one-night sitcom trope.
I'll wear two outfits.
Mix up their names.
- Hide under a table.
- What about growth?
I tried to go in a grounded direction but
ended up in an implausible situation.
Like Shirley said, it's a once-in-lifetime
opportunity for high jinks.
- I can't pass it up.
- You already passed up...
- a great opportunity for high jinks.
- I did?
Britta's dance?
You think two dates is crazy?
Planning a dance is high jinks city.
Population: High jinks.
Troy, I need your help.
Get some ice.
Wacky ice.
The ice will be wacky.
- Looks good, huh?
- I'm so excited.
Thank you for the corsage.
- It matches your carnation. How cute.
- I'm glad you like it.
I was afraid you'd think
it was old-fashioned.
I like old-fashioned. I find it refreshing.
Speaking of refreshing, I'm gonna
get us some punch. Be right back.
Hi, I'm Kevin.
Apparently I'm your DJ tonight.
I really don't know what I'm doing...
so if you have a request,
please be specific.
I have Changnesia.
- Can I help you?
- I wanted to try on a different look.
I'm pretty indecisive, so I may be
back here a few times, if that's okay.
Cool.
I'm also gonna need
to check this Gideons Bible...
and this jelly-bean kaleidoscope.
Icebreakers.
Hey, Britta. Where's Sophie B.?
She backstage drinking Zima
and counting her Beanie Babies?
Sorry, I can't divulge that.
- Stars and their privacy, you know.
- But she'll definitely be here?
Oh, yeah. Sophie be coming.
So it just be coincidence that somebody
posted a Craigslist ad an hour ago...
that says,
"Looking for Sophie B. Hawkins..."
or convincing Sophie B. Hawkins
impersonator...
"to play community college
dance tonight. Very little money."
It's weird how in demand she is.
Good thing we booked her early.
Britta, we're running low on chips.
Here's what I'm thinking.
I go to the Sadie Hawkins dance
as the snack inspector...
doing random spot checks,
and confiscate their chips.
All I need is a disguise.
Or you could just go to the supply
closet and get some more chips.
Okay, but I still need
to use the moustache probably.
Here, in lieu of flowers, I got you this.
- It's quirky.
- Thanks, governor.
I'll just put it in me invisible sack.
Okay, I'm gonna get us some punch.
Hey. How are things going
with you and Jessica?
Are you two, as they say on TV,
making a connection?
Unless that means sex,
in which case I hope you're not.
Things are great. Actually,
Jessica did mention she's cold.
Could she borrow your sweater?
The one you wore last week.
- I think it's still in your locker.
- I guess I could check.
- Could you? That'd be great.
- Okay.
Hey, roomie.
What do you think of Kat?
Did she tell you she plays the saw?
- I thought she was in a kazoo band?
- They need a rhythm section, duh.
Well, keep me posted.
- I'm gonna go say hi to Britta.
- No, don't.
You have something
in your teeth. A lot.
- I do? What is it?
- Can't tell in this light. But it's there.
You should check it in the bathroom.
The second-floor one.
I will. Thank you. You're a good friend.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hello, Jeffrey.
Are you enjoying the sock hop?
A sock hop Britta has all but Britta'd
by not Britta'ing her own dance.
Well, the night is young.
I'm surprised you let her
share the cafeteria.
Oh, I didn't want to.
But once she guaranteed the presence
of a certain someone, I couldn't say no.
I wouldn't get your hopes up
for Sophie B...
- Oh, it's me.
- Shall we dance?
- You reading the Bible?
- No spoilers.
I'm really hoping that things
turn around for this Job guy.
So how do I look?
Good. Except you gotta lose the hat.
Doesn't go with the minister's daughter.
- You know what I'm doing.
- Yeah. You're on two dates at once.
- I've been watching since you came in.
- I'm not good with faces.
Is that a judgmental or happy face?
I think it's awesome.
It's one of my favourite bits.
Like when a dog acts embarrassed:
Or when a guy chases a girl and
does that public declaration of love.
It's not realistic. It's turning
something private into a performance.
I think the dog's trained.
I was talking about the
public declaration of love.
- Oh, you're messing with me.
- Yes, I was.
This thing's turning out to be tougher
than I thought. Wanna help?
I'd like to, but I still got 1200 pages
left of this Bible. Yes, of course I would.
Cool. Cool, cool, cool.
Tonight's Sadie Hawkins dance
is brought to you by Hawthorne Wipes.
For the little lady
who knows her place in the kitchen.
And tonight's Sophie B. Hawkins dance
is brought to you by Hawthorne Wipes.
Perfect for cleaning the dashboard
of your '92 Subaru.
Quite a turnout, Britta.
Yep. Didn't know Sophie B. Hawkins
was so big at Greendale.
Oh, yeah.
A large percentage of Greendale
students gave up in the mid-'90s.
For many of them, Sophie B. Hawkins is
the most recent music they're aware of.
I mean, her coming here is
gonna be a huge boost to their spirits.
Great.
Whereas, her not showing up
would be enough to push these people...
to a dark place and really question
whether life is worth living at all.
Okay, bye-bye.
So how long have you been
doing Bible studies?
I mean, making hats out of duct tape.
Oh, duct-tape hat...
You never saw the
Star wars movies?
We were taught popular films
were the work of the devil.
If you're talking about Phantom Menace,
you were taught right.
Telegram.
Yeah, it's urgent. Be right back.
Pierce,
Sophie B. Hawkins isn't coming.
Everyone's gonna know I'm a liar.
Help me.
Oh, Britta.
Let me tell you a story about a friend
of mine that everyone called a liar.
- His name was Bernie Madoff.
- Pierce, he was a liar.
He stole billions of dollars
from his clients.
Has this been confirmed?
Oh, my God.
I Britta'd it.
Bernie?
- Oh, hi, Shirley.
- Hello, Annie.
Abed seems to be having a good time,
which is all that matters.
You're right.
- Looks like he made the right choice.
- He certainly did.
So we agree. The best woman won.
She certainly did.
- He's on two dates, isn't he?
- He certainly is.
This is the most fun I've ever had
on a work-study gig.
And I used to run the frozen-yogurt
machine before that guy broke it.
Many close calls.
Keep forgetting details...
using the wrong names,
having to duck behind plants.
- This night has been perfect.
- Oh, what else is on the list?
Sorry.
If this were a movie,
this would be the part where we kiss.
You're right. Except we're doing
a sitcom trope, so it'd be out of place.
Time to go get caught
and make a plea to the girl I like.
I'm gonna go with Jessica. She seems
to be the audience favourite. Okay, bye.
- You thought you'd get away with this?
- Let me explain.
What about wanting to grow?
Was that a lie so you could do...
another world-famous
Abed TV adventure?
These are real people you're messing
with. Kat is Hula-Hooping all by herself.
Abed, in the real world,
people can actually get hurt.
- Message for the party.
- This is great.
So I got a request for,
"You suck at this. Get off the stage."
Okay, I don't know if that's the band
or the song.
Again, apologies. Changnesia.
Well, it blew up in my face in a
slightly different way than I planned.
Can I help you?
- Where's Rachel?
- She said she had to go.
- Where?
- I don't know. She seemed upset.
She ran out of here
without tagging half this stuff.
I mean, whose water wings are these?
- Come back here.
- Never mind.
I know.
I'm sorry.
I did mean what I said about growth.
But you were both so intent on
getting me dates, I couldn't help myself.
It was wrong, and hurtful.
I see that now.
Well, maybe setting you up
was a bad idea.
Yeah, I guess neither of our girls
were really right for you.
The worst part is
I met a girl tonight that I really do like.
I was so busy chasing one trope,
I missed one under my nose...
The girl I liked
was under my nose.
I screwed things up.
I don't know if I can make them right.
Wait. This one's real, right?
Yeah, I'm really sad.
Well, go find her, dummy.
Yeah, haven't you ever seen a movie?
Sophie. Sophie. Sophie.
I hate to say I told you so,
but I'm gonna say it to Britta's face.
Sophie. Sophie. Sophie.
What is the nature of hope?
Sophie's not coming, guys.
Looks like someone underestimated
the time it takes to plan a dance.
Hey, hey, hey. It's Sophie B. Hawkins.
Good evening. I'm Sophie B. Hawkins.
I think you know this one.
Oh, man.
Did you do this?
If it's possible to make something
happen by willing it then, yes, I did.
Sorry, Sophie.
- I have something to say.
- Hey.
- Come on, man.
- Come on.
There was a girl here tonight.
Her name was Rachel.
I met her, and it was very pleasant.
And I made a mistake.
And now I'd very much like to
continue this conversation in private.
Wow, viva lost love.
- You came back.
- That was pretty embarrassing.
I had to...
It was.
But I'm glad I did it.
So would you like to go out sometime?
I would like that.
Wanna pretend
you're just going out with me on a bet?
Oh, I'd like that very much.
- But maybe we should try normal first.
- Sure.
- I prefer "As I Lay Me Down."
- Me too.
- I can't believe she pulled this off.
- I know.
According to dean law,
I must now give her my amulet.
What?
Well, she had a little help
from a wise old man...
who was the official supplier
of moist towelettes to the Lilith Fair...
- between 1997 and 1999.
- I knew it.
You're safe.
You did this? But why?
Because in the face of all logic
and reason, Britta didn't back down.
- That makes no sense.
- And I didn't like you being a jerk to her.
- She was acting crazy.
- Yeah, but what choice did she have?
You make fun of her, you use her name
as a synonym for screwing up.
Cut her some slack, Jeff.
She helped you reconcile
with your dad.
For Pete's sake, let her be happy.
I know it's probably impossible
to read my texts...
without them sounding sarcastic...
but I assure you,
this one is as earnest as they come.
Congratulations
on an awesome dance.
You Britta'd the hell out of this thing.
Can you do one
where you wish you had ice cream?
Damn, I wish I had some ice cream.
So good.
Okay, can you do one
where you wish I was Batman?
- Fine, but this is the last one.
- Okay.
Damn, I wish Abed was Batman
- I love it so much.
- So good.
All right, you guys are taking
advantage of Ms. B. Hawkins.
- But... But...
- But you nothing, she's an artist.
She is not here to do your bidding.
Sorry about that.
Now, if you could just sing
"Dean, I wish I was Your Lover"...
with these new lyrics.
It's for my voicemail.
- Who's Jeff Winger?
- Just sing the damn song.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org