This is from all of us, Troy.
When you're sailing around the world...
...you'll be going through
a lot of countries.
So we got you a universal translator.
Cool.
Thanks, guys.
I didn't know going-away parties
could be so much fun.
- I should leave all the time.
- Let's not forget it's okay to be sad too.
Britta, do you get kickbacks
from Big Buzz Kill?
- I'm serious.
- We know.
The truth is a member of our family
is leaving.
For a year, maybe more.
Psychology has taught me
the human mind has a tendency...
...to rechannel separation anxiety...
...in the form of frivolity
and giddiness, and...
I don't want us to waste our chance
to acknowledge...
...how much we're gonna miss you.
- Attention, Greendale.
- Oh, announcements.
- Announcements.
- Oh, I love these.
- I'm standing here with Abed Nadir...
...who has chosen
to give his best friend, Troy...
...the very special
going-away present...
...of declaring a school-wide game
of Hot Lava.
- Cool.
- Oh, that sounds like fun.
- No. Process your feelings.
- Hot Lava is the sweet...
...classic children's game...
...in which you are not allowed
to touch the fioor or you're dead.
I think it's cute. And while I normally
don't condone climbing on furniture...
...Troy and Abed's friendship
has been such a special...
...and magical part of Greendale,
we owe it to ourselves...
...to honour it.
Abed, anything to add?
Yes, take this seriously.
Stay on furniture. No books, no bags.
Dead can't talk.
No coming back as a lava monster.
- Yes. Hot Lava.
- Come on, guys...
...this is classic avoidance.
I have to go talk to him.
Because the non-awesome often need
incentive to do awesome stuff...
...the survivor will win my near-mint
condition issue of Space Clone...
...valued by the Comics Authority
at $50,000.
Wh...? I'm sorry?
The floor turns to lava in 10...
...nine, eight, seven...
Did you say 15 or 50,000?
- ...six...
- Oh, who am I kidding?
Help, lava.
...five, four, three, two...
COMMUNITY
LAVA WORLD
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Professor Duncan?
You stay back, Britta.
I'm not afraid to push a girl
into make-believe lava.
- It's been my primary strategy.
- I'm staying in the game...
...so I can talk to Abed. I'm worried.
What I'm worried about is money.
My self-published novels
aren't going to publish themselves.
Don't regress to primal behaviour
just because it's allowed.
We're human beings,
not the editors of Teen Vogue.
A terrible example
for today's young women.
Well, I'm sorry, Britta,
but it's either you or me.
And I'm me.
- No.
- Yes, yes, yes.
Real nice, Winger.
This is why the English
never win any sports.
Because everyone else cheats.
Britta, there you are.
Sweet, sweet, portable chairs.
Plastic gold.
Four-legged diamonds.
You claiming this?
Lava joust?
You hit your heads
on each other's heads?
Get real.
Once the last of the chairs are gone...
...a sofa hopper like you
won't last 20 minutes.
You wanna join this alliance
or you wanna join the lava?
Fine. But I'm not learning
the new names for anything.
Centipeding isn't the fastest form
of travel...
...but if we find more chairs,
we can do the Inchworm...
...Scootenanny...
...Reverse Danny Thomas.
Think this game's gotten
a little out of hand?
Feels normal enough for a school
that's on 911's blocked caller list.
I like that Abed wanted
to send Troy off.
Send him off or put off sending him?
I think this imaginary lava
might symbolise Abed's fear of change.
That diagnosis symbolizes
your lack of a psych degree.
Mama mahogany.
- Feast your feet on that stack of sticks.
- Too easy. Could be a trap.
As if someone else is taking this game
as seriously as you.
Let's keep this centipede rolling.
Give me a chair.
So stupid.
Come on.
- Locker, locker, locker.
- Locker Boys.
- Locker.
- Locker, locker, locker.
Winger, Edison and Perry.
What a delicious combination.
Locker, locker, locker.
What are we getting from this
extra level of commitment?
We're getting your chairs, food...
...and the names
of your same-sex celebrity crushes.
Everyone has one, don't lie.
Then you're free to go, into lava.
Locker, locker, locker.
Stand down or meet your doom,
Chang.
You're in no position to make threats.
Our truce ended when you banished us...
- ...from the pay phone bench.
- You used that to upset the balance.
By the vapours of Magmarath,
we will restore it.
- You have gods?
- Locker boys.
- Earn your M&M's.
- Locker.
Troy and Abed intimidation stance.
I guess that actually looked
the way it did in my head.
Hi, kids.
I'm criminology professor
Buzz Hickey...
...and this, this is just a little
something I threw together.
Jump.
- Centipede, centipede.
- Okay.
Pull harder. Pull harder.
Pull harder.
My same-sex celebrity crush
is Nathan Fillion.
Nathan Fillion.
Jeff, Annie. Get to Shirley Island.
We'll meet you there.
Abed, save yourself.
Abed, before Troy dies in lava...
...you can save yourself emotionally...
...by honestly experiencing the pain
of him leaving Greendale.
We can do this in three steps.
Britta, jump to that trash can.
Troy, start inchworming.
- Third step?
- Third step's survival. Good luck.
Seriously? Troy.
Sorry, Britta, Abed knows best.
I'll remember you as slowing us down
and complaining a lot.
Oh, my... No!
They abandoned you?
This game's doing bad things
to people.
I'm just in it for the money.
My son's getting gay married.
The flowers alone, you have no idea.
I get it.
I lived in New York.
All right, Miss Perry, climb aboard.
It's fake killing time.
Welcome to Shirley Island.
No furniture beyond this point.
Leave weapons at the door
and spare doors at the entrance.
Then came the now-now times...
...when the floors were covered
with the burny touch.
- You made it.
- Friends.
Welcome to Shirley Island,
where all your dreams come true...
...if you dream of standing on a table
and pissing in a jar. Where's Britta?
- She didn't make it.
- Oh, that's too bad.
- Poor Britta.
- It's okay.
Her sacrifice got us this far,
and now we can't lose.
Why not?
Because now we're on Shirley Island,
and according to legend, so is The Orb.
I'm sure I have no idea
what you're speaking of.
- This is a place of peace.
- And profit.
- Come again?
- You're not really playing.
You're a merchant,
and more power to you.
But don't withhold power
from others just to make money.
- We want The Orb.
- Abed.
I'm still raw from what happened
with Britta back there.
I mean, fun is fun,
but I don't want my last day here...
...to be a day
where everyone hates me.
Last day?
Citizens of Shirley Island.
What have you brought to my door?
Stay back.
My God, it's Hickey.
And he's got Chair Walkers.
Come out with your feet on the floor...
...and there will be no need
for nudging or jostling.
I did not skip my son's birthday
for second place.
I wanna say something to you guys
about mental health.
Is that Britta? Is she alive?
- Why did you think she was dead?
- We kind of left her.
Left her for dead?
Sounds bad when you put it that way.
You do realise this isn't just
a pile of chairs, right?
This is a crib, and you're curled up
inside there, sucking your thumb...
...because you're too scared
to say goodbye.
Well, it's time to grow up.
The adults are here,
and we're gonna tear down your fort.
Chair Walkers, attack.
My name was Vicki. Tell my story.
These are my only pants.
I can't get them dirty.
I'm actually British.
- Leonard. Butter them up.
- You got it.
Cirque du So Long,
you high-stepping acro-bastards.
- Have any rolling chairs?
- Behind the curtain.
Abandon fort.
Women and man-children first.
Hey, seat feet.
Chair to dance?
Yes.
Britta, I'm your friend.
I can't hear dead people, Annie.
- I'm in a world of imagination.
- Then imagine what the floor looks like.
I don't have to. I'll just
imagine where you're about to be.
- The same as imagining the floor.
- You just admitted that's where you'll be.
- Knock, knock.
- Not gonna say, "Who's there?"
- Someone on the floor is knocking.
- You have to say, "Who's there?"
- Floor.
- What?
- That's who's there.
- Yeah. But it's for you.
Give us The Orb.
We can save Shirley Island.
The Orb can't save Shirley Island
because Shirley Island is The Orb.
In a cool way like Keyser Soze
or a lame way like Jewel of the Nile?
You tell Buzz Hickey
that Shirley Bennett said...
Don't wanna waste time. Think of
something cool, give me credit.
But the door I'm knocking on
is your home...
- ...if I'm the floor, it means you're dead.
- If you're the floor, you're already dead.
Just do it right. Knock, knock.
Knock, knock.
Who's there, bitch?
Floor.
Floor!
- Troy and Abed in a bubble
Hickey, you chicken.
He gutted us. Retreat.
Hello?
I'm the only one left.
I won 50,000 bucks.
That's 50,000 lottery tickets.
You can't outrun your emotions.
I had a dream like this,
but it was sexual.
I will force you two
to grieve properly even if it kills us all.
Go away, Britta.
Sorry about our butts touching.
Go into the vents.
They'll never find us there.
I say we take a stand here.
- Someone's gotta win sometime.
- Not if we never kill each other.
- Then we can play forever.
- Right. Wait.
Abed, the floor can't be lava forever.
The game's gotta end.
It's not a game for me. I'm seeing
real lava because you're leaving.
It's embarrassing, and I don't
wanna be crazy, but I am crazy, so...
I made a game that made you
and everyone else see what I see.
I don't want it to be there.
I want you to be able to leave.
I don't think the lava goes away
until you stop leaving.
So the only way I can help you...
...is by giving up my chance
to be one person?
You guys ready for closure?
Of your caskets?
Guys, stop, okay?
The lava's real to Abed.
- It's not a game to him.
- Oh, no.
You know what I think?
I think he's used to getting his own way.
I think he's never met me.
Abed. Abed.
Unbelievable.
When this game is over,
I'm gonna shove you back.
Abed, give me your other hand.
It's down to us.
You or Britta will be the winner.
I'm not leaving, okay? Just... I promise.
The floor's not lava.
Just give me your hand.
I don't think the lava's here
because you're leaving.
I think it's here because I won't let go.
Sorry.
- Bye.
- Abed.
Abed. Abed.
Abed!
Abed! Abed!
Abed.
He's fake dead.
Forever.
Shut up.
What? Stop.
He's not really dead.
But he's really playing dead,
and he's not gonna stop.
Here.
Congratulations, you win.
You don't get it.
No one gets Abed.
I got him a little.
This is my fault.
I don't deserve to fake live.
Wait. No.
- I can fix him.
- How?
I don't know. In real life, I don't know,
but I can fake fix him.
SPACE
CLONE
- I can clone him. I'll clone him.
- Go on.
I just need his DNA.
Let's get his DNA.
Don't touch the lava.
You might be onto something.
I'm gonna find discarded technology
from this once great civilisation...
...and start a cloning machine.
Okay, I'm placing
this cellular regeneration sequencer...
...on the spot where he died.
- Here, don't forget this.
- This is a laser guidance system...
...that keeps the regeneration sequence
from jib-jabbing.
Jib-jabbing?
Initiate regeneration sequence.
- It worked.
- We made a perfect clone of Abed.
Actually, Britta's work was sloppy.
I'm not an exact replication.
I have Abed's abilities and memories,
but I'm missing his wild emotionality.
Although I think I may be able
to let Troy go now.
I don't know.
I haven't been completely honest.
I'm really scared to go on my trip.
Well, you don't have to go.
Your clone can.
Right.
BORCHERT HALL
GREENDALE
So you guys are all cloned up too,
huh?
- Yeah.
- Believe in cloning.
- Well...
CHILDISH
TYCOON
Guess that's my ride.
I'm so excited for you.
You're gonna see the world...
...and experience new cultures.
All culture has been homogenized
by 50 years of American imperialism...
...but at least the candy bar wrappers
will...
God, there I go.
Almost Britta'd our goodbye, huh?
I'm the worst.
You're the best, and I love you.
- I'm better at sex than Jeff, right?
- I've yet to have anyone worse.
All I ever wanted in high school
was for Troy Barnes to notice me...
...and then I ended up living with you.
- I'm pretty lucky.
- I'm not.
I had a chance to be your friend in high
school, but I was busy trying to be cool.
I missed out on four more years
of Annie.
You are the coolest guy I know.
I hope I make you proud.
I've never stepped foot
outside of Colorado.
You're becoming much cooler than me
by doing this.
- Thanks for looking out for me.
- Thank you for putting up...
...with the boring, old mom
in your study group.
You made a furniture fortress.
You're the badass
from our study group.
Clone Troy.
Clone Abed.
When I cloned you, I had to
patch parts of your DNA...
...with genes from a homing pigeon.
You may notice side effects,
like a compulsion to come back.
Cool. Clone hug?
You're really gonna pilot this thing
all on your own?
Pierce's will stated that someone...
...would be assigned to me
to verify I don't cheat.
Captain Barnes.
We should set sail while the wind
is still in our favour, don't you think?
Engage.
Troy, I know it's gonna be difficult
for you to interact with me...
No, no. That was the original Troy.
I'm his clone.
Let's get the lead out, Burton.
Aye, aye, sir.
Starting from landlocked Colorado
may not have been the best idea.
Drive to the river
then take the river to the ocean.
I never thought I'd see you.
I have a couple Star Trek questions,
if you don't mind.
No, go ahead.
"What time did you have to get up
in the morning?
Every writer write for one character?
What's a best boy?"
I saw it in the credits once.
"Why don't they call it Planet Trek?"
You never go to a star.
You... Not one episode.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org