It's settled.
Urinals in the women's restroom
will be turned into planters.
On to chores.
We need some able bodies...
...to clear out a space
in the storage room.
- I'll do it.
- Really?
Annie goes from easy chores
to hardest.
That's true.
- I'll do it too.
- Yeah, me too.
- Okay, that concludes this meeting.
- Oh, man.
Nobody picks up on my patterns.
What am I gonna say next?
Graham cracker. You didn't know.
Hey, it's the... couple.
Rachel got Pile of Bullets.
Interactive Old West-themed
VCR game from the '90s.
I found it at Goodwill.
Between a Thighmaster
and a Dick Tracy Burger King glass.
- Happy anniversary.
- Anniversary?
- I guess I should learn your name, lady.
- Oh, Rachel.
Rachel. Nice to meet you, Rachel.
You can go.
Okay.
- Anniversary?
- Been dating for one of your months.
Our relationship is 12 times
more efficient, so a year.
Sleep cycles are in sync,
communicate with eyebrows.
She knows my Netflix password.
Jeff's password.
- I'm changing that.
- I changed it.
- To what?
- Nice try.
Can Rachel come to our place
to play this?
- Can't afford to take her anywhere.
- My brother's in town...
...and I'm broke too.
I was gonna make him dinner tonight.
Cool. Double date?
Dinner and 1993 interactive VCR game?
- What are you making?
- Salmon.
- Buttered noodles.
- Buttered noodles are my favourite.
Quick announcement
for two of Greendale's finest.
Payday is postponed until next week,
so this...
...is my freestyle rap apology.
Well, I'm a peanut bar
And I'm here to say
Your cheques will arrive
On another day
Another day, another dime
Another dollar
Another stuffed shirt
With another white collar
Criminals, Wall Street
Taking the pie
And all the black man gets
Is a plate of white lies
Prisons recruiting them
Police be shooting them
Rap artists looting them
Labels all diluting them
Barack Obama is scared of me
'Cause I don't swallow knowledge
And I spit it for free
Let me clear my throat
I don't know what that was, I don't.
I don't know what that was.
-= www.OpenSubtitles.org =-
So nice to have the Edison kids
under one roof again.
Remember when we used to
cut carrots for Mom?
- Yes.
- I need a soda.
Oh, okay.
One, two, three.
Door's busted.
- Landlord's in jail and money's tight.
- Yeah.
Oh, my God.
- Anthony, thank you.
- Yeah.
Hey, Abed, a quick word?
What would you think about
my brother moving in?
- Do I just keep cutting carrots?
- Yes, Anthony.
- He has money. He's handy.
- You're putting me on the spot.
My concern would be he's a Viking,
might only use our home...
...as a temporary base
before moving inland.
A good guy. We can't afford to keep
splitting the rent. Have a better idea?
- How about Rachel?
- That a joke?
Is it cool if I poop?
No, Anthony. Just cut the carrots.
You've been dating Rachel for a month.
I don't think you heard his question.
The answer is yes.
We have been dating
for the equivalent of a year.
I've been hearing about that
for two years.
Can't microwave a relationship like a
burrito. Ain't living with your girlfriend.
Ain't living with your "keep cutting
carrots or ask if he can poop" brother.
Rachel's on her way.
I'd like to practise my smile.
I guess it was just air.
Why are we organising
a storage room?
- How is this not a janitor's job?
- Can I ask you something?
Why the hell do you have
all those muscles...
...if you're gonna bitch
about moving boxes?
Is the air working in here? I'm sweating
like a Catholic on Judgement Day.
- A little Protestant humour. Got more.
- Oh, can't wait.
Nothing.
Wait. There's something in there
blocking the vent.
You gonna open it?
You realise nothing good has ever
been found in a vent, right? It's a vent.
"Intro to Chemistry." Third edition.
Mint. Two hundred dollars retail...
- ...160 on the street.
- Why are there books in an air duct?
Why is there hot sauce
in the bathroom? It's Greendale.
- Must be stolen.
- Have to tell the dean.
Hold on.
Let's just calm down
and have a slow, pleasant chat...
...about possibilities.
- What kind?
- All kinds. Anything is possible.
We might one day have hover cars.
Kale might be poisonous. And we might
not have to get the dean involved here.
- Jeffrey, these are stolen.
- From who?
By who? How long ago?
It's "from whom," "by whom."
But he nailed the third question.
Look, we are the committee
that deals with Greendale's problems.
You see anything on our list
about a pile of missing books...
...worth more than the school
they're in?
One thing's for sure. If we hand
these over, they'll really go missing.
Think that money's gonna be used
to cut our pay cheques...
...or to make another
rapping peanut costume?
- I can't believe what I'm hearing.
- Wanna go to heaven?
- Walk away, more for us.
- I'm an accomplice now.
I'll only get into heaven
by turning you in.
But what about your restaurant?
What about your kids?
Ms. Bennett, when God talks to you,
what language does he use?
Because in my experience, when he
thinks you deserve something...
...he drops it on you
like a ton of bricks.
All right. But if we're gonna do this,
we're gonna do this clean and safe.
We're gonna move these
to my restaurant...
...sit on them
until we know they're cold.
Price them through a third party
and unload them in a single score.
None of that nickel-and-dime crap.
I don't wanna leave a trail.
- Yeah, great.
- Wonderful.
- Okay. Let's count these babies up.
Yeah, great.
When we were kids...
...Anthony and I would play
Time Machine.
We would go, "Oh, no.
We're in barbarian times.
Quick. Back to the time machine."
And then we would run
back to the time machine.
It's true.
That's why Abed is like a brother
to me. You guys are alike.
I can't accept that based on one story.
Rachel, did you tell Annie
about your Waterpik?
I suppose now
is as good a time as any.
I own a Waterpik.
Annie has one too. You guys care
for your teeth same amount.
Share a bathroom, it'd go smoothly.
- Anthony could fix our cabinets.
- Rachel used to mop floors at Kmart.
This a real conversation
or are we bugged by the feds?
Abed.
Sidebar.
What do you think happens
after you die?
- I don't know.
- You're lucky.
- Stop trying to sell me on Rachel.
- Stop pitching Anthony.
- You're like ice cream cake. Overkill.
- We need a roommate.
- I vote Rachel.
- Anthony.
- Flip a coin?
- Coins create parallel timelines.
- Rock, Paper, Scissors?
- That's a nine-sided coin.
What about Pile of Bullets?
You wanna decide on a roommate...
...with a 1993 Old West-themed
VCR game?
Rachel or I win, Rachel moves in.
You or Anthony win, I'll surrender...
- ...count down days until he eats me.
- All right, it's settled.
- Is this working?
- It's a handshake in progress.
Who wants to play Pile of Bullets?
- Not me.
- You have to.
- We don't have to.
- Not okay. We do have to.
One day we'll tell you why.
For now,
let's simply retire to the TV area.
For the highest stakes
1993 interactive VCR game...
...of your entire young adult lives.
Okay, let's see what you got.
Yeah. Okay.
I know somebody that knows people.
I can get you a price per book,
find a buyer and make a deal.
- For half.
- That's ridiculous.
I'm assuming more than half the risk.
- Half is fair.
- Not really.
Because they're ours,
all 100 percent of them.
Giving you half is not fair, it's silly.
Okay, good luck.
You wanna re-blindfold me?
I know we're in E-9 in the east wing.
I know that
because it smells like weed.
Not my weed.
Look, I'm willing to give her half.
- You can have half of Jeff's share.
- Not what I meant.
You're offering her half of the total.
Either half of all of our money
or half of your share.
Either way, you walk
with about 16 percent.
- Not fair.
- Damn right.
Here's what is:
25 percent for each of us.
Take it or leave it, Britta.
Legalize it
Don't Chang...
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Look, if something sketchy
is happening, I don't care.
So I'm just gonna back out...
- ...of the room now and...
- He can't leave.
No! No!
I didn't see anything.
I did not see anything.
- Britta, find some rope.
- I've got rope.
"Each player starts
with six bullet tokens...
...10 gold certificates,
and a colour-coded posse token."
There's two types of tokens?
I'm sure we'll figure it out.
Howdy.
You look like a real group
of gunslingers.
Everyone in town's mighty scared
what with all the gold and the outlaws.
- Only one of us can make it out alive.
- Are we robbing the town?
By now, you should have
your bullets, your gold...
...and two Wild West tokens each.
Hang on to those tokens
no matter what.
- There's two kinds of tokens.
- Two each?
Now, when you hear
the word "draw"...
...or see a square
with a colour or number matching...
...one of you or your opponent's cards,
the first one of you to say "bang"...
...wins the challenged player's token
and the amount of their bid in gold.
- What's going on?
- Ready?
- Yes?
- I'm not.
- We supposed to be bidding?
- Draw!
- I bid.
- Rattler.
- Bang five.
- Bang?
- Bang-bang five.
- Not bad.
Collect your tokens
and let's get on to the next round.
- What you doing?
- He said, "collect your tokens."
- He can't see you.
- Didn't Abed shoot whoever's five?
Draw!
Odd-numbered players,
give up two cards! Draw!
We have numbers?
Okay. Okay, I don't think
we're doing this right.
Sure this is a game
and not some art film?
- What do we do?
- Rewind, start over.
Okay, I'll allow it.
No, it's okay.
We gave it our best shot, no?
I'm sorry, Rachel, is this your home?
Oh, God, no, I'm sorry.
- We're playing.
- But it doesn't make any sense.
- Sounds like Anthony wants to forfeit.
- He doesn't. Don't forfeit.
Rachel, we can do this.
- Just focus, okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
- Howdy.
I love textbooks.
That's why I stole these.
- All right, knock it off.
- What?
You gotta make it sound believable
or you're not getting out of here.
- I'm trying.
- Try harder. Go.
I love textbooks.
That's why I stole them.
Look at this one.
Stolen textbooks are the best kind.
I stole all these books and put them
in this room so I could come kiss them.
That's all, thank you.
Please, I'm on parole.
Exactly. So keep your mouth shut
or we'll send this file to everybody.
- What do you mean "everybody"?
- Everybody.
- I can't do this anymore.
- What?
I'm out. It's too far, it's too evil.
Look, you guys can split the money.
I'm just gonna leave quietly.
Goodbye.
- What the hell? What the hell?
- Yeah?
I can't let you leave until we're done.
This is not what God
wants you to be doing today.
We had our chance to think about that.
He dropped this like a ton of bricks.
- Right, Hickey?
- Oh, yeah, definitely.
Not to say that this isn't getting insane.
Blackhat Bill
sure ain't the forgiving type.
- You! Green player!
- Yes, partner?
- You can do better than that.
- Yes, partner.
- Pick a player that you wanna draw.
- I choose Anthony. Draw a card.
Keep this
for when you're in quick draw.
- Rachel, your turn.
- What do I do?
You roll. Here.
- There. My turn.
- Stop. Snake bite. Lose a turn.
Anti-venom.
- I'll take two.
- Draw!
- I bid five bullets. Eleven.
- Six.
Pass. Reverse.
Hold it!
Did you remember to say "yee-haw"?
Anyone that didn't loses a turn.
Collect your coins.
I'll trade you two snakes for a bullet.
Just say yes.
- I don't wanna die.
- Stop her, Rachel, stop her.
No. Bid five.
- Tornado!
Nine, tornado.
- Pass. Seven.
- Reverse.
- Two tornado.
- Pass.
- Double.
- Draw!
- Come on. You son of a bitch.
- Come on.
- Come on, come on.
Come on.
If one of you rolled
your bullet number...
...you're the winner.
Fast-forward to the red screen
to get your gold.
Well, more food for the buzzards.
Looks like modern times...
...have come after all.
See you in the city.
I wanna go home.
- Me too.
- We have to play again.
Abed, I think you're having
one of your special times.
- I'm gonna give you space.
- Want you to move in here.
But that's not resolved.
Anthony might move in, so...
- We want one of you to live with us.
- Settling it with Pile of Bullets.
That is not an explanation...
...that should make anybody
want to live here.
I don't like this side of you...
...and I do not like that side
of VCR technology.
I am glad that it's a dead medium.
That was very uncomfortable.
I don't really know
how girlfriends work...
...but I don't think
you have one anymore.
Okay, cool. See you there.
I'm meeting my guy in an hour.
He wants to see a sample,
set a price then do the exchange.
Oh, brother. Britta doesn't know
how much she's getting...
...from this guy none of us will ever see
again. She knows one thing for sure.
She'll be right back with it
so you can divvy it up...
...even stephen.
Man, that's rich. What's supposed to
stop her from robbing you guys blind?
- What are you gonna do, call the cops?
- I'll go with her.
- Oh, yeah. Good plan.
- Leave Hickey, two of you do the deal.
Yeah, what the hell? When
did I volunteer for Guantanamo duty...
...while you two traipse off...
...to the Cuban equivalent
of Las Vegas?
Havana, right?
Don't listen to Jeff.
He's trying to divide us.
Says the woman who's willing
to take care of the cash by herself.
As if you're Mr. Trustworthy.
Why do you have
so much access to rope?
You're the one who left the door
unlocked so Chang could get in.
- You didn't do that on purpose?
- Guys. Guys.
Calm down.
I'm sure we can work this out.
We just need to stay cool
and talk it through.
I'm sorry.
That didn't work out the way I planned.
But you didn't leave me any choice.
You were acting poorly, I didn't know
if I could trust you anymore.
You dragged me into this.
I didn't want this.
- You're packing?
- Yeah.
- You're leaving?
Because of last night?
Yeah. I just think there's
some unresolved issues here.
You're right.
I'm still really hurt
by Mom turning her back on me...
...when I went to rehab.
And I guess part of me
was mad at you...
...for siding with her...
...so I thought you moving in here
was some kind of moral victory.
What? No. Unresolved issues involving
the black guy in all these photographs.
- Troy?
- Hey, I don't know his name, man.
I just know he's clearly left
some kind of vacuum.
And screw you.
What did I have to do with Mom?
I was 13.
- Hey.
- Hi. I'm here to do my third-act apology.
- I don't think...
- Wait. Don't reject it...
...until the whole thing's
been served up.
Open your locker please.
Hey.
- Hey.
- I wanna tell you something.
This is adorable.
Just because it's adorable
doesn't mean it's not important.
Listen. I've been accelerating
our relationship.
I've been worried
I wouldn't pass a lot of the tests.
Because I thought
if Annie was around...
- ...I'd have less chance of screwing up.
- You're not screwing things up.
That's good to know.
The problem with me will always be
that I can never know for sure.
Not a huge amount of people in my life
that haven't eventually kicked me out...
...and I don't always see it coming.
I don't want it to happen with you.
Don't manipulate me,
don't keep secrets from me...
...and we'll probably be okay.
Cool.
It stopped raining.
Yeah, it sure did.
You hired a stunt person.
No, I did not.
Where'd you get these?
They were an inheritance
from my father.
He was a collector.
- How many?
- A hundred and twenty.
- Well, for the whole bunch, maybe 20.
- Thousand?
- Dollars.
- $20,000?
Twenty non-thousand dollars.
Regular dollars.
Might get that from a recycling place.
These are misprints. Check page 105.
Well, I can't
because there's no page numbers.
Well, that would be a problem.
You know, "Class, turn to page..."
"There is no page."
"Oh, well, if there's no page number,
you can't turn to it, so..."
I have better things to do with my life.
Though we haven't been saying it...
...Troy was an important part
of our apartment. He kept the peace.
Yeah.
Going a little crazy without him.
Maybe we need to live with a therapist.
Or at least someone crazier than us.
- Let's give Craigslist another try.
- Craigslist is the way to go.
You guys all wearing
the same clothes from yesterday?
- We've been through some stuff.
- We learned something.
No, we didn't.
We learned that sometimes
there's no lesson.
- How's that learning?
- We played Pile of Bullets.
- Get this meeting over with?
- How'd the cleanup go?
Don't step, don't step to me
I like coffee and water
Don't step to me
Damn it, I lost it.
I lost it!
Okay. I will get back to you. Thanks.
- Who was that?
- They want me...
...for that Wild West videotape
board game thing.
- Pile of Bullets?
- Yeah.
Devon, you pick up that phone now
and tell them you want this part.
These VCR games
is where everything is headed.
Can't you see that?
You just became the Luke Skywalker...
...of the new Star Wars.
- We've gotta move.
- We do?
Oh, yes, indeedy.
We have got to move to Los Angeles.
But I work here.
Oh, please.
You call Apple Computers work?
What kind of company
offers "stock options"...
...as a Christmas bonus?
That ship is sinking.
Sweetie, remember when
we were talking about trying cocaine?
Yeah.
I think we should start
looking for some right now.
Because we're gonna be able
to afford it.
Okay. I mean, if you're sure.
I've never been more sure
about anything in my entire life.
Pile of Bullets.
Oh, yes.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org