I am the system.
I consume humanity.
- There is no escape.
- Objection!
Jeff Winger, hero-at-law
Best lawyer you ever saw
Hero to freedom
Defender of liberty
South of the 40 at Lincoln
You park for free
Jeff
Are you a good person being sued,
oppressed or beaten?
I can help,
and that's the Winger Guarantee.
Call 555-her...
Maybe you should've spent
less money on special effects.
Yeah. Thanks a lot,
Francis Ford Repo Man.
Jeff Winger, loser-at-law
Rented office in a mini mall
Relax, Tango. I come in peace.
Way I see it, I screwed you...
...I got screwed back.
Now we can bygone the bygones.
I got a juicy new client
and a bone to throw you.
Hear about that bridge
that collapsed?
A human could say that
without salivating.
I represent Marvin Humphries,
the engineer who designed it.
He wants to seek damages.
From what? His own pencil?
From the only school reckless enough
to give him a degree in engineering.
City-funded school,
deep government pockets.
Maybe you've heard of it.
Greendale Community College.
Weird choice, by the way,
bachelor's degree on the wall.
You're gonna sue my school,
you're bothering to tell me?
You have access there.
I need Marvin's records to prove
that he was irresponsibly educated.
- Well, why don't you just subpoena?
- Right.
So they can have a shredding party.
That's the difference
between you and Greendale, Alan.
They wouldn't shred evidence.
It's a good place for good people.
It's a diploma mill.
It turns idiots
into bridge collapsers...
...and Jeff Winger into an attorney
that thought he could...
...help people?
Jeff, I once saw you
convince an arson victim...
...that he liked his house better burnt.
God, look what that school
did to you.
It took all your money,
it took four years of your life.
And worst of all,
it took your Winger moves.
I still got my Winger moves.
Prove it. Get me Humphries' records.
Because the next bone you get thrown
might be through a dude's zipper...
...in the warehouse district and I can't
guarantee you it'll be from me.
I might be broke, desperate,
nearly homeless...
...but I still got one thing deep down
inside that gives me power... That was it.
That was all I had.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Welcome back, human beings.
Dean Pelton here, wishing you
another magic year at Greendale...
...ranked America's number two
community college...
...by
greendalecommunitycollege.com.
Regarding the recent tragedy
surrounding a certain collapsed bridge...
...we'll be observing a moment
of silence on the quad...
...followed by four years of silence
to the press.
I told you you'd be back.
Shut up, Leonard. I'm not here.
I'm just a figment
of your creeping dementia.
Hi.
How would I go about
getting records for certain alumni?
Why would you think a stranger
could just walk in here and do that?
You're Rita.
- Rhonda.
- I've always regretted not telling you...
...how much you remind me
of my aunt.
It's more disarming than it sounds.
I have a very attractive aunt.
Rhonda, why are you wearing
Jeff Winger's...?
Jeffrey.
Are you looking for your friends?
They don't go here anymore.
Looking for something
in front of you the whole time?
He's asking for records...
...for a certain alumni.
In the midst of all this
Marvin Humphries business...
...I doubt this is a coincidence.
You're here to save me, aren't you?
Yes.
I thought I might contact alumni...
...to form a committee.
The Save Greendale Committee.
Working title.
Jeffrey, I'm gonna cry.
- Please don't.
- Request denied.
Rhonda will let you
in the records room.
It's actually your old study room.
After you and your friends left,
it was closed for sentimental reasons.
And asbestos reasons,
but it's clean as a whistle now.
"Harassment reports,
hazardous waste citations...
...herpes, water fountains."
Come on. Where's Humphries?
- I see your value now.
- Abed, why?
It's a callback to when
we met first season.
Me calling years "seasons"
is a callback to my dialogue and...
I know what makes you off-putting...
- ...but why are you here?
- Dean called me about the committee.
- Can I join?
- Oh, no. Who else did he call?
Just me. I called everyone else.
Jeffrey.
Jeff.
- Is that cool?
- It's the coolest.
Jeff, if you wanted to save Greendale,
why didn't you call us first?
Well, you guys just got sprung
from this joint.
And I figured you had careers
to get started.
- Yeah, working hard.
- Yes.
- Yeah. So many things.
- Yeah. Sandwiches...
Us, always doing stuff.
What have they done to our home?
The table's buried.
- I got it.
- This is where we became a family.
Where Jeff made us a family.
We can repilot.
This could be like Scrubs season nine,
a revamp, a do-over.
- Jeff could come back as a teacher.
- I'm not gonna be a teacher, Abed.
Come on.
Sit in your chair.
Complete the table.
- We wanna help you save Greendale.
- Yeah.
- Greendale. Greendale. Greendale.
- Save it.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
Give him space.
Repiloting can be intense.
New people show up,
regulars shift roles or even fall away.
In Scrubs, Zach was only
in the first six episodes.
That son of a bitch.
After everything Scrubs did for him?
I'm sorry.
Vision boarding.
Okay, vision boarding...
Oh, hi, Jeffrey.
I have to warn you about something
because it's the right thing to do.
First, why is there a big empty box on
your desk that says "Humphries" on it?
The press has been calling
about Humphries.
I didn't want any details
about his enrolment here...
...to be spun against us...
...so now there are no details.
That was his thesis.
Okay. So sue me.
This ain't Harvard, Jeffrey.
Okay, my job is to give
a certain number of degrees per year...
...or we could get shut down.
And that would be bad because...?
Because then I wouldn't have a job.
And, you know, Greendale
is a good place for good people.
That whole spiel, huh?
Yeah.
That whole spiel.
Wing Blade.
Shock me by impressing me.
- He shredded Humphries.
- What?
I told you.
How could you let this happen?
Sir, I have to ask you
to leave the concierge desk.
Jeff, this case was all I had.
I am screwed.
My wife left,
my girlfriend dumped me.
And they're sisters,
whole family's pissed.
Shut up. Bring me paperwork
for filing a class action.
Letters of intent, engagement,
everything. Multiple copies.
Winger, you just lost our client!
Yeah. But I can create five new ones.
So dusty. Let's get this off.
- Season nine of Scrubs.
- And that's the Winger Guarantee.
Okay. Maybe we should brainstorm
fundraising ideas...
...that aren't bake sales.
Or opening a zoo where the humans are
in cages and the animals come to visit.
Are you okay, Jeff?
You left kind of freaked out.
Well, I can't stop thinking this school
might be in trouble...
- ...because of this bridge guy.
- He's the one making bad bridges.
That's like me blaming owls
for how much I suck at analogies.
Sometimes a student will claim,
in court...
...that their school ruined their life...
...and they'll win.
You wanna save Greendale?
Make it litigation-proof.
- How?
- Think like the enemy.
How did Greendale damage you,
Annie?
It didn't.
I love hospital administration.
- Is that your job?
- Well, not yet.
But I administer
things to hospitals, like these. Pen?
- "Futurza"?
- They're a rising star in pharmaceuticals.
They invented fibromyalgia
and the cure for fibromyalgia.
You push drugs now? That's ironic.
I push pens, Britta.
Speaking of irony,
how's the therapy market? Depressed?
- I'm on sabbatical.
- You're Jewish?
I'm doing hands-on research
about the psychology of alcoholism.
You're a bartender, aren't you?
Which is basically
like a modern-day therapist.
Somebody tells me about a murder,
I can't tell anyone.
You're even bad at bartending.
What about you?
Abed's working on the next
billion-dollar social media app.
And when it takes off,
all I gotta do is sue him.
- It's foolproof.
- You're programming now, Abed?
Didn't get any work
with your four-year film degree?
Directing a commercial.
Still haven't been paid.
I'll cut you a cheque tomorrow,
but just so we're clear, you quit.
- Differences.
- I asked you to put the phone number...
- ...on the screen.
- I didn't like the number. 555?
- The number of my business.
- Sounds fake.
Every number starts with 555.
Are there only 10,000 numbers?
Abed, you quit?
Said you got fired. You haven't paid
rent in our apartment in months.
Sell him a pill that will help him
give up on his dreams.
Relaxabrex doesn't make you give up
on your dreams. That's a side effect.
At least the drugs I sell don't
get slurped out of my belly button.
- That's only on Tummy Tuesdays! Sorry...
- It's okay to...
Andre left again.
It's not like last time.
He's staying with family.
He took the boys, he took the dog.
He took the DVR.
Hundred and sixty-six episodes
of Bones just gone.
It was my fault this time.
I cheated on him...
...with Shirley's Sandwiches.
I threw the money into expanding.
I just didn't think I could fail.
Okay.
Well, just so you know...
...this is the sort of stuff...
...that someone could use
to make a claim against a school.
I have to go to the bathroom again.
While I'm gone...
...I want you to think about what I said.
As an exercise.
Do you guys feel weird
about doing this without Magnitude?
That's everything you asked for.
- Who are you flipping?
- My friends...
...who are now the
Save Greendale Committee...
...which I created.
Classic Winger.
I forgot what it was like
to be good at being bad.
So just close the deal
and bring it home to Daddy.
Sorry, Alan. Change of daddies.
- I'll take it from here.
- But it's my case.
- Humphries was your case.
- Jeff...
- ...you're scaring me.
- Good.
Guys like you should be more scared.
You trust-funded, body-sprayed,
Eli Roth DVD-owner.
You're an amateur monster and you
stomped on the grave of a real monster...
...who was willing to stay buried
because real monsters have shame...
...because they wish that... You're not
worth the monologue. Give me your tie.
- What?
- No monologue for you. Give me your tie.
That's for making me go
to this school.
That's for making
the last four years happen.
And now I get to make them
un-happen for me...
...and the only people I care about.
I failed my husband, I failed my kids.
I've failed Bones.
I'm helping to hook a whole new batch
of little Annies on Adderall.
I've spent so much time with computers
your tears are 1s and 0s to me.
Yeah, you were a real
Hallmark card before.
I'm much sadder than the rest of you.
I will figure out why later.
Jeff, full disclosure.
Our lives are worse
than the day we got here.
Well, that is a serious allegation
to arrive at all by yourselves.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
And we've come to a decision
as a group...
...and please don't judge us
for suggesting it.
- I'll back you up no matter...
- We decided to reenroll at Greendale.
What? Are you nuts?
Greendale! Greendale! Greendale!
You guys wanna keep it down?
- Chang?
- Kevin?
Chang. I've dropped the amnesia thing,
copped to my crimes and went to jail.
Now I'm on work release.
- Working as what?
- Math teacher.
- Explain the pyjamas.
- Work release from house arrest...
...but I don't have a home.
See this? This won't let me travel...
...a hundred yards from this.
And this only has a 30-yard cord,
so I can only travel...
- You do the math.
- You said you teach math.
Exactly. I teach it, you do it.
Chang was faking his Changnesia?
Seriously rehired a teacher they fired
for trying to burn down the school?
After being rehired as a guard after
being fired for impersonating a teacher.
That's insane, and I'm Abed.
Worse than insane. Irresponsible.
- Evil.
- I don't believe in evil.
But this school clearly got a finger
up its butt as a child.
This place ruins lives.
If that were true...
...then what could we
possibly do about it?
Make them dance, Winger.
Jeff, what's your evil
legal nemesis doing here?
Nemesis?
No, we were partners again...
...until I lost my usefulness.
I may be evil...
...but your friend here
is so much more dangerous.
Tell them how it took you 30 minutes
to make them think...
...they wanted to sue their own school.
I did it.
Sorry.
Anyway, I'll leave you
to pick up these pieces.
I'm gonna go score some blow.
My dealer's a gym teacher here.
You were lying to us?
I never lied to you.
I showed you the right truth.
Britta, when we met,
you were an eclectic anarchist.
How did you become
the group's airhead?
- Thank you?
- And, Shirley...
...you've gone from an
independent divorcée...
...striking out on her own...
...to a bankrupt fry cook
hoping for a call from her husband.
Troy, your entire identity
has been consumed...
- ...by your relationship with another man.
- You found my Clive Owen Tumblr.
What happened to Annie,
unstoppable go-getter?
There was that gas leak last year.
Oh, don't blame it all
on the gas leak year.
This was a four-year process.
We went in one end as real people...
...and out the other end
as mixed-up cartoons.
- Cool.
- Sure.
Coming from the guy who's had
how many psychotic breaks?
Including gas leak year?
You all came here
with a chance to be something.
And you all had that taken away
from you. Get something back.
Seek damages.
Sign here.
But you're our hero.
- I mean, in the commercial...
- The commercial was a lie.
You staged a robot fight?
Yeah. In real life, the robot wins.
Troy?
If Jeff didn't change, then Jeff is right.
Case closed. Let's make some money.
Okay, Jeff, if this is
what you really want to do...
...I'll sign.
The choice to make is yours.
No, it's yours.
We're putting Greendale
in your hands.
- Do we all have to say something?
- No, you can just sign it.
- You brought us together.
- With lies.
But what you do is above lying,
remember?
You show us the right truth.
You won't regret this.
I'd like to take the study room table
in back and burn it.
Burn it? Why?
The same reason I never returned
Time Bandits to Blockbuster.
Nobody else deserves it.
Jesus.
- Looks as if you've lost your way.
- Pierce?
Continue on this path,
you might miss your last chance...
...to see the Pierce Hawthorne
Museum of Gender Sensitivity...
...and Sexual Potency
on the central quad.
The museum and this hologram...
...were donated in compliance
with a court order...
...I'm not allowed to discuss.
Let's just say some women
can't take a compliment.
Unbelievable.
What I am allowed to discuss
is Greendale.
And I'll say this:
don't turn your back on it.
Take it from a man
with no legal right to be there.
You're in a special place.
A crappy place, sure, but only because
it gives crappy people...
...a chance to sort themselves out.
Did I sound gay at the end?
Do you wanna do another take?
- Jeffrey, I'm not decent.
- I know.
These are the signatures
of the five people...
...that are crazy enough
to care about this toilet.
And tonight, I almost got them
to sue it.
- Heed the warning.
- It's not easy being dean, Jeffrey.
Then stop being the dean.
It's my whole ideantity.
I mean... See what I did there?
That's proof.
Get your crap together.
Your job is not to hand out degrees.
Your job is to make this a toilet...
...that people don't have to be crazy
to care about.
But you could stay here
and help me save the school.
For how much money?
I can't offer you any money.
I could offer you a job.
You just described slavery.
I mean, there's nothing in the budget
for school-saver...
...but I could hire you as...
Screw you, Abed.
I'd be depressed
if these samples from work...
...weren't giving me
a new outlook on life.
If you're interested in learning more, ask
your doctor if Joyvatrex is right for you.
Oh, honey.
If we sue Greendale,
can I be a surprise witness?
- Wait. Don't tell me.
- Stop.
- We shouldn't sue the school.
- Oh, come on!
Are you trying to give us
emotional whiplash?
Look, if you feel there's more work
to be done on yourselves...
...then as crappy as this place is,
it's a place that you can do it.
- You got a job teaching here.
- I don't wanna talk about it.
Well, then, I'm getting back
into forensic science.
That was my actual dream.
It's my fault I bailed on it.
A film degree
doesn't make me a filmmaker.
I need to work with others.
- I need to figure out who I am.
- I'll help you.
Get out of my brain.
I need to learn
how to really run a business...
...by my own standards,
not Greendale's.
I'm gonna get a four-year
psych degree, then a master's...
...and become a real psychologist.
Or you could find another major.
A real psychologist.
- How about English?
- Psychology.
All right, what's important
is no matter what...
...we'll be trying to talk Britta into
doing something different together.
Burn, hopelessness.
Oh, my God!
It's a fire! Somebody help us!
Little victories
count for a lot around here.
Good.
Even if you never asked
to win in the first place.
And you have to enjoy
those nice moments while you can.
He does a voice-over wrap-up
at the end of every episode.
Cool.
Because around here,
they never last very long.
Once more. More teacher-y.
I wanna kill myself.
Use that.
Are you a good person?
Yes, unlike you.
I can guarantee,
the Winger beaten you.
Not anymore.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org