Okay, we'll get an estimate
on adding grass to the soccer field.
Good meeting.
Oh, Jeff, what time's dinner?
- Dinner?
- Jeff, you didn't invite Shirley?
Well, it's Tuesday. Shirley always goes
to Elijah's karate practise on Tuesdays.
It's okay. Part of making sacrifices
for my loved ones...
...is not expecting my loved ones
to make sacrifices.
- I can do tomorrow.
- I can't.
- I'm free on Fridays and Mondays...
- We're not moving it.
When Shirley can have dinner,
we'll have another dinner...
...because it's just dinner.
And there's no need to manipulate each
other. You know that's what you do.
You know you're doing it now
with that face.
You don't like my face?
Hello, Save Greendale Committee.
This is David and Bixel.
They're app designers.
They'd like to beta test their latest
social-networking app on our campus...
...which could be good for us.
Look what Facebook did for Harvard.
Hey, guys, Bixel and I
would like to introduce you...
...to a little app
called MeowMeowBeenz.
MeowMeowBeenz lets you say
how much you like...
...who you like, when you like...
...all from a standard
non-boost mobile phone.
Let's see how it works.
Bixel, what did you think
of the way the dean introduced us?
I thought he did great.
That's why I'm giving him
five MeowMeowBeenz.
Well, Bixel, I'm sorry,
but I thought his intro was just okay.
That's why I'm gonna give him
two out of five MeowMeowBeenz.
My MeowMeowBeenz.
With MeowMeowBeenz,
students can rate teachers.
Teachers can rate students.
Everyone and anyone
can rate each other.
- MeowMeowBeenz.
You know, I could...
I fought for this country...
...and I know you don't get to pick
and choose the parts you fight for...
...but I know...
I should go number two soon.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Hurry up.
I'm late for Human Rights class.
I'm sorry.
Why is Starburns
carrying Garrett's books?
It's like toast bossing crackers around.
- I mean, I guess.
- Garrett's got three MeowMeowBeenz.
- Starburns is at two.
- People are using this stupid app?
- It's effective.
- No, it's effectively stupid.
There was a rating system in place
called "cool people get more"...
...and it was working fine.
MeowMeowBeenz takes everything
about human interaction...
...and reduces it
to explicit, objective numbers.
I've never felt more alive.
As long as you're happy, I'm unsettled.
Hey, guys.
- What happened to you?
- I sat so long, my feet fell asleep.
Then I noticed limping
was getting MeowMeowBeenz...
...so I just kind of started committing.
Did you understand a word he said?
Hey, here you go. Here you go.
Nobody is gonna down-vote a guy
on his birthday.
- Wait. Are you using MeowMeowBeenz?
- If you can't kill it, join it.
You get older, you see warning signs.
Mark Zuckerberg
is Fidel Castro in flip-flops.
MeowMeowBeenz is gonna make
East Berlin look like Woodstock.
You take my word for that.
Do you own stock
in Trivial Pursuit's Baby Boom Edition?
Britta, please tell me
you're not using this app.
I liked the idea at first,
giving a voice to the unheard...
...but then Annie told me
that the rating system...
...is exponentially weighted.
As your ratings go up, your ratings of
other people become more important.
- No.
- It means the more others like you...
...the more likeable you make others.
Makes sense.
- You know who else it made sense to?
- Say "Hitler" and I'm giving you a two.
You not registered? The longer you
wait, the harder to get your number up.
Annie. Listen to yourself.
You're learning its language.
You're letting a video game play you.
I gotta set these people straight.
Hey, hey, you've got a...
Students of Greendale!
We don't have to worship a calculator!
There is no formula for people!
You're punishing me for being alive!
That's the general idea, baby.
You're gonna think I'm joking,
but you were getting through more...
- ...with mustard on your lip.
- Shut up.
He's not kidding.
I thought I was imagining it.
When you had mustard on your lip,
I was open to your opinion.
Maybe it dilutes or distracts
from your excessive intensity.
from your stupid butt.
- How you doing, Rog?
- Oh, don't be...
Hey, Charlotte.
I see what you did there.
Vicki, I love this.
- Shirley's a five.
- How?
She's nice to people, Jeff.
You know Shirley.
Oh, Vicki, thank you.
Did you just give me
four MeowMeowBeenz?
I love my four from Vicki.
No.
Stop it!
I didn't mean it.
Yeah. I do know Shirley.
We should be having brownies.
I'm going to help Shirley.
Not a bad idea.
She could make you a two again.
Screw your twos,
and screw MeowMeowBeenz.
I know that's your one talking.
- What are you doing?
- Registering for MeowMeowBeenz.
I'm gonna become a five
and expose this for the sham it is.
Oh, now you're
speaking my language.
That's unintentional, trust me.
Make sure you know the reason
you're doing something...
...or you'll fail before you start.
- That's actually a good point.
- It is? Why?
Oh, come on.
I'm like, "That's two cups,"
and she's like, "What?"
I'm like,
"Two cups, balls back, tops off."
All right, Trent, Mulch, Dave...
...Herpie, Clutch, Dirt Mouth, Rope,
Tingles, Cat Woman, Steve.
All right, keep it floppy.
Haul it, ball it, never call it.
- Girls are objects.
- Yeah!
Two MeowMeowBeenz.
Congratulations.
Abed was just explaining
that the fives get to choose...
...what setting
the air conditioning is on.
Yep.
Is it me,
or are more people wearing grey?
I feel like someone's about
to hand me a Starburst.
Wear neutral colours.
Looking like you wanna move up...
- ...can get you moved down.
- Abed, hey.
- Hey, come here.
- Hi. Come on.
Those are other threes. We talk
about how we're glad we're not twos.
Small talk, guys.
I make small talk now.
Hello, Jeffrey. I see you decided
to join MeowMeowBeenz.
Oh, it's a great tool for living.
- You look great.
- Know what you're doing.
I'm watching you, okay?
Yeah, you'll be watching my hinder,
Mama...
...and choking on its billowing plume
of highly rated dust.
Fours and above only.
These are snacks for the fives.
Yeah? You're a two.
Leonard, would you rather a three
serve the fives food?
No.
It is no secret
that the threes and twos...
...are growing suspicious
of the fours and fives.
All I know is that it's my birthday.
What if we give these people
something to believe in again?
- Koogler?
- Hey.
I know what you guys think of me,
okay?
"Hey, it's Koogler. You know, he's cool.
He likes to get laid. He's not that old."
I'm a five because I know what the twos
and the threes need. What do we need?
Entertainment.
A talent show.
An event where threes and twos
can rise and fall.
- Helps people believe in the system.
- Give my spot to someone else.
I don't wanna be a five.
I was happy as a three. I'm miserable.
Oh, dear Abed. So humble.
You people are monsters.
Well, if there's nothing else, then.
Speak.
Headline items.
Twos broke into a supply closet
and stole a box of peanut butter.
The futurization of the campus decor
is almost complete.
And a few hours ago,
Jeff Winger became a four.
That's nice.
You there, girl.
How many MeowMeowBeenz?
Two.
- Two? Are you lost, Two?
- Yes.
Are you lost, Two?
I'll escort her to the common area.
- You're a four? I don't recognise you.
- He's new Beenz.
Bye-bye, new Beenz.
Threes and twos must leave Building 1
after 7.
Building 1 after 7 is fours only.
- What are you doing?
- How goes the revolution?
I can't break a four.
It's impossible to get any higher
without half the fives.
- They got this thing locked up.
- They're nervous.
They're hosting a talent show
to prove anyone can be a five.
If you enter, you'll be centre stage
with all eyes on you...
...and you can tell everyone
this isn't democracy.
This is tyranny.
Can you put some mustard...?
I shouldn't have to put mustard
on my face for this to make sense.
You know
we have to take this system down.
You know, I once loved a two.
Matthew.
He was my everything.
But numbers change.
I'll keep your secret, new Beenz.
It says you're next.
Now, Jeffrey,
I beg you not to take this risk.
You know what they say.
Fives have lives, fours have chores,
threes have fleas, twos have blues...
...and ones don't get a rhyme
because they're garbage.
Craig, I got this.
No. No, please.
Not The Outlands! Please!
Boo on you!
The fives have spoken.
And you...
...are not very good and...
What? No! Please!
I'm just not very good
at public speaking and...
Last chance, Jeffrey.
Showtime.
My name is Jeff Winger.
I recently became a four.
Funny thing is, when I was a two...
...I didn't actually have any less.
But I did have a lot of crazy friends.
Hey, my name's Tommy Talouca.
I'm from hallway C. I'm a two.
I gotta get to the cafeteria
before they run out of apples.
What is with twos and apples?
You're given three kinds of fruit.
Mix it up.
Then you become a four.
And you get that... That four walk.
You know what I'm talking about?
It's like one of these.
And they got a little trail
of twos behind them...
...and they're like,
"Hey, is there an apple up there?"
What else is going on?
He's killing it.
There came a time
when I has to ask myself...
...did I even wanna be a three?
Or did I just hate myself
for being a two?
I don't know.
All I know is...
...I sure do love them apples!
Oh, the Koog approogs. That's a five.
Yeah!
Review, review! Meow, meow, meow!
Down here, guys.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Can I get a picture?
I want my future kids
to know this happened.
I admire your optimism, Garrett.
- What the hell?
- I don't wanna hear it.
I got this far to take Shirley down.
- What about everyone else?
- Look around you. Everyone wanted this.
Fives only, ma'am.
Oh, great. Come on.
You... You think
this system's gonna last forever?
I'm gonna free people's minds.
I'm a psych major.
Words are my weapons.
I'm a security guard.
Weapons are my weapons.
Welcome, fives,
to the inaugural fancy future dance.
I'm glad you don't think
making Jeff a five was a mistake.
I believe in taking risks.
Yeah. Jeff's really cool.
Couldn't help but notice...
...that Shirley didn't clap with
the rest of you after my performance.
Is she always so different?
I can't concentrate
on the dance moves.
You don't believe the rumours, do you,
that Jeff manipulated his way to the top?
Shirley, I can hear what you're saying.
You're trying to manipulate someone
into thinking I'm manipulative.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
No one knows
Do you wanna have this conversation,
or just keep flexing your veiny arms...
...and throwing out apples?
Tranquillity is advancement.
A happy three is a future four.
Twos and Threes, you're accepting
a life you don't have to live.
Stand up for yourselves!
Really?
- Fine. Give me that.
- Hey.
You're all alive.
You are all alive.
Look at the mustard on my face,
but listen to my words.
- You're one of the angriest...
- You're angry.
The rules got changed on you.
You can't just be cool
and be in charge now.
No, you have to gossip and give out
food and make people feel guilty.
Okay, yeah. I bust my ass
making a world full of selfish idiots...
...remember my name.
Call it hard work, but don't tell me
the system measures who's nice.
Actually, it kind of does.
Security, banish them to The Outlands
with the rest of the ones.
- No! No! No!
- Okay, okay, okay.
Ladies and gentlemen, please put your
tray tables in their party positions.
So sayeth Captain Koogler.
Actually, keep the tray tables
where they are, Koogler.
The rule of the fives is over.
Long live the review-lution!
No!
That comes down?
- Okay, all right, all right, all right.
- All right.
- Happy?
- Are you happy?
I knew you couldn't go
to that stupid dinner.
- That's why I didn't invite you.
- It's nice to be invited.
Sure, if you're a control freak.
Oh, and you clearly hate control.
No. I love it.
I guess it's easy to pretend
that you don't when you got it.
You'd think we'd be better friends...
...because we're big fans of
the same thing.
You there. Ones.
You are permitted back indoors
by decree of Britta, the Mother of Ones.
And do I hear correctly that as a five...
...you felt you could park
in handicap spots?
Well, you see,
that's just part of the Koogler style.
It's human-crap style.
Rate him.
Okay, well, that's low.
All fives must be cleansed of
their five filth and reduced to oneness.
Jeff. Hey, Shirley. I'm not a five
anymore. I'm a one like everyone else.
I'm like everyone else.
Who's next?
All right, time to pull the plug.
Oh, great Mother of Ones...
...mustard-faced saviour...
...there is still a five hiding among us
that has not been cleansed.
Nonsense.
All fives were reduced to oneness...
...in the great purge
of about two minutes ago.
This five cheats.
It never registered, yet was given a five
from outside the system.
Behold.
The MeowMeowBeenz app.
Its beta test ended days ago.
It's now available in the app store,
99 cents.
Five stars.
This five lied to us...
...used us, judged us...
...yet exempts itself from judgment.
It's selling our information to spammers
because I am getting a lot more e-mail...
...and trust me,
my penis needs no enlargement.
So how do you cleanse a five
that's unregistered?
Delete it.
By the way, guys, it's a Saturday.
You're all in school for nothing.
Go home and get some sleep.
- No.
No! No. Wait.
No, don't go! Where are you going?
No.
Attention, Greendale.
I'd like to propose we forget everything
that happened over the last few days.
I don't anticipate a lot of pushback
on that. I think we're all embarrassed.
- Hey there.
- Oh, hey.
So I was thinking about checking out
this new restaurant tonight.
Oh, that's sweet, but I can't tonight.
Not even takeout?
We could eat in the study room.
Oh, I think I have time for that, Jeffrey.
What?
I'm not gonna take it off.
I still got two days left on the rental.
Every once in a while,
a film comes along...
...that takes a serious look
at higher education.
This is not one of them.
Gentlemen...
...assume the party.
This summer, fun has a new name.
- Koogler?
- Koogler!
- Koogler.
- Koogler! Koogler!
Hope you don't mind if I play through.
Hammer Road Pictures invites you
to meet the man, the myth...
I'm photocopying my rear end.
- ...the Koogler.
- Koogler.
I guess I have what you might call
an aversion to education.
Do you even have a career plan?
- Yeah, does getting laid count?
- No!
Mitchell D. Hurwitz is Koogler,
Rated R.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org