So according to the demonologist,
the gymnasium is clean.
- We're running out of to-do stars.
- Yes.
- Already dealt with.
- It's hard to believe.
Somewhere along the way,
we started turning this school around.
- The hell was that?
- What was what?
Long, quiet lull. Don't like it.
It's called contentment.
Exactly.
Someone's always got a problem.
I've got a problem. I don't like Abed's
problem with our lack of problems.
Okay.
I commented on his commentary.
I just drew a circle around Abed, baby.
"I don't think it's nice to pigeonhole
people's gimmicks."
"You hear me, Two-Voice?"
Abed, let us have a moment
of peace and stillness.
They're kind of rare around here.
- Calm before the storm.
- Says the storm generator.
All right, fine. Let's be content.
Attention,
students and faculty of Greendale.
I pressed this button on accident...
...but might as well check in.
How are you?
Fine.
That's nice. I'm good too.
I love you guys.
We love you too.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
The information you've requested...
Is on the Internet.
School board, baby.
School board guys coming in.
I would appreciate some knocking.
Do you know what goes on in here?
Heads-up. There's an insurance
appraiser coming tomorrow.
Your ass is getting appraised,
insurance-style.
- What does that mean?
- We hope it means we find out...
...that your school
is very, very valuable to the city.
Hey, how hilarious would that be?
Are you guys drunk?
- Good luck proving it before we're not.
- Yeah.
Pa-pa-papaya.
Mango.
Strawberry.
- Too ripe.
- You've been doing this for 30 minutes.
So what?
I made all the vegetables disappear.
A lot more than this happens
in 30 minutes.
- We're relaxed and happy.
- I care more about this...
- ...than anything I've ever cared about.
- Best $199 I've ever spent.
It's 3 dollars.
What are you playing?
That's control software
for some kind of irrigation equipment.
It's fun.
Save Greendale Committee, unite.
An insurance appraiser
is coming tomorrow...
...to inspect the school.
If he doesn't appraise us good...
...the school is doomed, doomed.
- Call to adventure. Call to adventure.
- What's an insurance appraiser?
Something that sounds normal
and boring but is scary.
Like a raised mole
or a turkey deep fryer.
Only one man qualified
to appraise insurance...
...and he died 2000 years ago
on a cross.
I've seen insurance appraisers bleed.
Their blood's different, darker.
Everyone, take a breath.
You're overreacting because this school
is addicted to crisis.
You're like Hurricane Katrina dogs
that won't let anyone pet them anymore.
But the weird thing
we need to get used to is this:
The school's in decent shape.
This doesn't have to be a big deal.
I wrote a paper on those dogs.
We've worked hard all semester
to save this school.
Truth is, we did.
So relax.
- Are you sure, Jeffrey?
- I promise.
Heart's in the right place,
but he's wrong.
Greendale is a crazy place where
crazy things happen. I have a plan.
Pretend we have a renowned
Physics Department.
- Dean, start learning Swedish.
- I'll do my best.
Hickey, you keep in touch
with any criminals you busted?
- Five.
- Get them for costume measurements.
We need to make a particle accelerator
out of boxes.
Nope. Nobody do any of that.
Abed, outside.
- There is no story.
- Everything's a story, Jeff.
Getting out of bed is a story.
This is a story.
Study room, we're content.
I'm concerned. Skip fruit-matching.
Dean enters with the insurance story.
Call, refusal.
You're dragging me across a threshold
demanding there be no story.
Puts me into a world
I'm gonna have to adapt to.
You have to do it by yourself, please.
Okay?
Because if this appraisal is a story...
...that means we're in trouble,
and we are not in trouble.
Because if we are...
No more stories.
So we'll see you later.
After no story.
No story.
So be it.
Let the lack of story...
Hey.
Oh, put one trap behind each cabinet.
Although, I think we're good.
The cafeteria food killed...
- ...most of the roaches anyway.
- Hey, check it out.
- Is this a wedding ring?
- Are you kidding? What...?
I lost this my first week here.
Oh, who's the lucky...?
It's my mom's.
I started wearing it because...
...I don't know, everybody dreams
of settling down, right?
And because it fits.
She had huge fingers for a woman.
Part of what killed her, really.
I'm not dreaming about settling down.
Well, maybe you already have.
You're teaching, and you like it.
- You love Greendale.
- No, I love Scotch and myself.
I tolerate Greendale.
It's a good school.
There's no need to get sentimental.
This is going to be
the most boring thing to happen here...
...since Britta dated Troy.
All right, no story.
Wait.
If there's no story,
what am I explaining?
I'm in a story.
Okay, think, Abed, think.
How do you shake a story?
The answer is in the teacher's lounge.
Oh, hey, Janelle, how are you?
- Here he comes, here he comes.
- Okay.
Hi, my name is Ronald Mohammed.
Go ahead, heard them all.
The city of Greendale
has sent me here...
...to assess
this campus's level of liability.
Now, what do I mean by liability?
Well, the city defines liability
as any asserted...
...or non-asserted perturbation
by any qualifying party.
What's a party? A party is a person
or a group of persons...
...or an event celebrating a person
or a party of persons' birth, marriage...
Don't panic, Jeffrey.
I'm fine.
I'm the only one who's not panicking.
Please. You can lie to yourself,
but don't lie to me.
But the city defines a dog...
...as any living entity
with four legs and a tail.
So raccoons, bears...
...mountain lions, mice,
these are all just different sizes of dog.
What do I mean by size?
- Tell you a story.
- What's that supposed to mean?
I know how much you feel
for the campus, Jeff.
How much you feel in general.
And I know you think it's a weakness,
but believe me, it's your strength.
- You got something in your teeth.
- You got something in your chest.
Four hundred thousand gallons
of liquefied horse meat.
Here I come.
Just...
And you shall find that salt is the taste
of another man's bread...
...and hard is the way up and down
another man's stairs.
Dante. Let's proceed.
No! It's always a story.
Everything is a story.
Wait, wait, wait. Story feeds on conflict.
If I stop resisting,
it'll stop being a story.
No, Abed.
Me with a beard?
Keep fighting the story.
Keep fighting it until it falls apart.
I'm right.
I mean, I'm wrong.
I mean, I'm right. I mean, I'm wrong.
Unsubscribe.
For the final stage of my appraisal...
...I'm gonna randomly select
one of your vending machines...
...to see if it can be rocked
using human strength...
...enough to tip and crush me.
Now, in the U.S., each year...
...six people die this way...
...and five of them
are insurance appraisers...
...so I take this very seriously.
Here we go.
- Okay.
- Sorry we're late.
Hey, look. It's Ronald Mohammed.
How about that name?
All right, what's the damage?
How much is this scampy little hole
in the earth gonna cost us this year?
Well, your gas leak is repaired, all
your fire exits actually lead outside...
...and I am told that no new species
have been discovered here in a week.
I have to say, I was brought in here
to estimate Greendale's liability...
...but at this point in time, I'd describe
this campus as an actual property asset.
This property has value.
Oh, yeah!
Best news ever.
- This property has value.
- It has value.
- That means we can sell it.
- We can finally sell it.
Wait, wait, wait.
Press stop on Dave Matthews.
- What?
- We can start courting businesses...
...to unload this school
on the private sector.
What do you mean?
This is a huge chunk of real estate,
which generates no tax revenue...
...and takes money
from the Education budget.
That's because
it's a community college.
Well, excuse us for taking longer
to see that was the problem.
Maybe we're not as smart as you.
I mean, we only went to Yale.
Oh, no, you didn't.
- Yes, I did.
- We should call T.J.Maxx right away.
Dude, I told you. This jacket looks fine.
No, to talk about selling this place.
Oh, right. Yeah, T.J.Maxx, Marshalls.
What about Ben & Jerry's?
Oh, Richie, you're my friend,
but that is the last thing you need.
Tough love received, bro.
I did it. This school is story-free.
We can be content now forever.
Let me be one of the six this year.
Craig. Craig, this vending machine
is not gonna tip over and crush you.
Why not? Why?
Because we fixed it
when we saved Greendale.
We saved Greendale.
And now they're gonna sell it.
If I come over there...
...there are gonna be two sounds:
me hitting you twice.
Hello, Greendale, as you know,
our school will soon be replaced...
...by a sandwich university.
However,
every ending is also a beginning.
Sure, things may look bad now...
...some of us may have no idea
where we're going or what to do, but...
Okay, okay,
I should've written this out.
I thought I'd be able to come up
with something on the fly.
Moving on to phase two,
the actual saving of Greendale.
Annie...
I've generated a few ideas
involving social media...
- ...that I think might do the trick.
- Annie...
You want us to tweet "Savegreendale"?
I'm sorry, Annie.
The reason I have 48 followers
is that I don't exploit them.
They come to me for atheistic rants
and photos of my meals...
...not this obnoxiousness.
We need to make people aware
that Greendale exists and needs help.
- Why?
- Because once the Internet...
- ...knows about something, it changes.
- Right.
Just ask Chris Brown or China.
Jeff, you made Annie cry.
Well, if it's any consolation, this is
the last time that will ever happen.
I know how to save Greendale.
Treasure. Buried treasure.
Okay, I'm tapped.
We all wish we could do something,
Annie, but I think that concludes...
...the last meeting
of the Save Greendale Committee...
...the committee that did its darnedest.
Wait! Are we sure we can't stop
the school from being sold to Subway?
I'm afraid so, Chang.
Okay, I just wanted to make sure.
Screw you, guys. It's time to get paid.
Chang just unexpectedly
betrayed the group for the last time.
Greendale's gonna make
a great Subway Sandwich University.
Research shows
most of your graduates...
- ...end up working for our restaurants.
- By design. We're proud of our school.
Proud of Subway School.
This campus is yours now.
If you wanna dynamite it, all we ask
is that you let us light the fuse.
Yeah, we hate this place.
- You just said you were proud of it.
- Proud of its potential.
Love its potential.
This'll be your office.
Why?
Okay, we'll check in on that later.
What, can't wait
until Greendale's corpse is cold...
...before you put it
on a 6-inch white bun?
Young lady, that's not fair.
Subway doesn't call its bread "buns,"
and we don't serve white.
We serve Italian, honey oat...
- ...nine-grain wheat.
- Thanks for making my joke accurate.
- Now it's hilarious.
- Classes are over, kids.
We're helping the dean pack.
This is still Greendale for two hours.
Enjoy it.
Wait. You don't call your bread "buns."
What do you call them?
Bread.
Bread is a substance. What do you call
the units of bread you use, "breads"?
You okay?
I just wish we had more time.
I could turn things around, I swear.
Look.
I got one of these label things.
I mean, it makes custom labels.
This was gonna help me
get organised.
Where should we start?
Pack up these pictures?
They're not really mine.
They're Greendale history.
Here's our 1987 civil rights march.
This was when we started offering
Photoshop classes.
And that's Russell Borchert.
Borchert, Borchert, loved computers...
Yes, yes, "More than women's butts
or hooters." Very mature, you two.
Was there any truth to that legend?
The legend
that a Greendale computer professor...
...made love to a computer...
...and died of the first computer virus?
Sure.
The truth is,
Greendale had a computer professor.
By the way,
he was a millionaire and a genius.
He has sex with one computer,
and that's his legacy?
So after all my work,
how will I be remembered?
The bald dean with glasses, I guess.
You aware
there's an engraved plate on this, says:
- "The truth is behind this picture"?
- Of course. I'm not an idiot.
Whoa, wait. It meant literally?
What is it?
You were teaching
Fundamentals of Law?
Yeah.
Think you could make the transition
to teaching Sandwich Law?
It's essentially the same, I'm sure,
just a bit more focused.
Here.
That's a Subway black card.
It entitles you to
5-dollar footlongs for life.
For life, Mr. Winger.
For life.
- Hey.
So, what are you gonna do?
I'm thinking I'm gonna transfer
to city college...
...but I'm knowing
I'm gonna be a bartender.
You?
- Subway offered me a job.
- Nice.
I'm worried about Abed and Annie.
They're not ready for this to end.
They're part of the
adulthood-begins-at-30 generation.
And I'm...
I'm actually looking forward
to a little bit of...
- Sanity?
- Yes. Sanity.
Yeah. I mean, it's over,
but on the other hand, it's over.
Amen. And to think this all started
because you wanted to...
Nail you.
Yeah, I regret nothing.
Don't. I mean, after everything
that has happened here...
...what did either of us
really get done aside from each other?
Exactly. And what are either of us
gonna be leaving with?
I should go clean out my locker,
she said at the age of 33.
Let's get married.
- What?
- Yeah, right?
I mean, this is what matters, isn't it?
This is what keeps this all
from being pointless.
Let's do what people do. Get a house we
can't afford, a dog that makes us angry.
Dedicate an entire cabinet
to grocery bags...
...realise we have a favourite brand
of olive oil?
Yes. Marry me.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, this feels right.
Let's get out of here
and never look back.
First, let's lock these doors
and pull these shades.
- We've never had sex on the new table.
- Yes, two for two.
Medium roughness, high tempo?
Let's make it a number eight.
Buried treasure!
Lock the doors, close the blinds.
We could save Greendale, Jeff.
There may be treasure on campus.
Hidden, buried treasure.
Treasure!
We need to call an emergency meeting...
...somewhere safe
where no one can hear or see...
...because we have to
keep this a secret...
...because it's a buried treasure!
Buried treasure!
Buried treasure,
buried treasure, buried treasure.
Buried treasure, buried treasure,
buried treasure.
Buried treasure, buried treasure.
Interesting.
Emergency meeting.
And that's how
I ended up at Greendale.
Isn't it strange how it took
this school shutting down...
...for you and I to know each other?
- What's up next for you?
- Don't know.
Maybe go stay with family
in Lincolnshire.
- Lincolnshire?
- Yeah.
- Where in Lincolnshire?
- Just a little town called Scunthorpe.
Scunthorpe?
I was stationed around Scunthorpe.
- No.
- Oh, wait, wait.
O'er the lady's smocks I tarry
Through the hollyhocks and glen
For a piss and a thrush
In Scunthorpe
- Then it's off to Henningpen
I love that.
Oh, where in God's name
did you learn that song?
- In Stainsbury Pub.
- My family practically lived...
- ...in Stainsbury's.
- I lost my virginity at Stainsbury's.
My mother was a Stainsbury whore.
Mine was missing a thumb.
Oh, my God.
- Two thumbs, she got both.
- Two thumbs.
I mean,
you may have slept with my aunt...
...but given the circumstances, cheers.
- Cheers, yeah.
- Yeah.
So you're gonna stay with your family
till you get your bearings?
I've got a cousin, Clive,
who's got a spare room.
- You and he would really get along.
- Really?
Yeah.
Who is paying for popcorn? Decide by
flipping a coin at www.coinflip.com