This is Russell Borchert,
computer genius...
...anti-deodorant activist,
and millionaire.
He was rich for having invented
the nine-track cassette...
...which the eight-track industry
paid to keep quiet.
He funnelled that wealth into
a computer school called Greendale...
...where he obsessively pursued
a new project...
...a machine that can process feelings.
He apparently used nothing but gold
to assemble his circuitry...
...believing it to be a better conductor
of human emotion.
It was a weird time.
The Bionic Woman won an Emmy.
Rumours spread about his relationship
with computers...
...and one day, he disappeared.
Hence the legend that he died
of the first computer virus.
The city bought the campus,
and life went on.
His body was never found,
nor was his immense wealth.
Some people said he hid his money
using a portal to another dimension.
Those people were on LSD.
Everyone else said
he had a secret vault in his office.
Well, where is his office?
Good question.
We found this confession
written by Greendale's first dean.
"To protect the student health
and the school's reputation...
...I have sealed off
the Computer Department...
...and removed the stairwell
to that section."
Section that remains on this campus,
its secrets untouched...
...including possibly Borchert's millions.
If we found it we could buy it
from the city before Subway.
Then I could really go nuts
with this place.
This adventure I usually have
to force upon us.
It is falling into our laps.
We're like the Goonies.
- Except our story tracks logically.
- And we're not talking over each other.
- Everyone talks at the same time. Sorry.
- Can you stop?
Here are your blueprints.
Sorry it took long.
- You can't fight city hall.
- You can. That's why it took so long.
- I'll be damned. Will you look at that?
- It's so clear now.
The entire school
is shaped like a penis.
No, that. It says right here that
this stairway leads to sublevel three.
Is that where the teachers' lounge is?
What the hell does your penis
look like?
Obviously a cluster of buildings.
Let's have a laugh at the freak.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Missing stairwell would be in this area.
Eyes peeled.
Serial killers and people that
hide treasure leave weird little clues.
Check it out. Look at the bottle
held by the school's first...
...and least acceptable mascot,
Big Chief Drunky.
X marks the spot, baby.
Hey, Hickey, maybe you shouldn't be...
Okay.
- Shirley, will you lock the door?
- Okay.
There you go.
It's just a bunch of wires.
Exactly what they want us to think.
Oh, my God.
Wait, wait, wait!
The sparks may be spelling out
the next clue.
Jeff, do something.
Is Duncan okay?
He'll live, but his food's gonna taste
like burnt aluminium for a while.
It's pronounced "aluminium."
See, he's fine.
Okay, guys, stop it. Now.
Nobody wants to admit it's over,
but come on.
Oh, look, it's Jeff Winger, fun police...
...here to pull over our smiles...
...because our mouths
have tinted windows.
- Britta and I are getting married.
- What?
Married? Well, you're gonna need
way more doves than this.
What does this look like,
an hour-long episode of The Office?
There's pick-axing
and electric zapping.
Don't even acknowledge it.
We are not acknowledging this.
You guys are ridiculous together.
We're ridiculous?
What do you call this?
Secret trapdoor!
- Who's got rope?
- I'm offended by that question.
Richie and Carl from the school board.
That's right. We got names.
Open this door now.
- Wait, I know where the keys are.
- You hear that?
When we get in there,
you're gonna be in big trouble.
Here they are. Here they are.
- Which one is it?
- Well, it's never the first one...
- ...so we can cancel this one out.
- Come on.
I guess now this is the first one,
so it should be the next one.
- Oh, damn.
- You know what? I got it.
- Get out of the way.
- Richie, be careful.
Don't worry. I've been drinking.
Oh, hello. Would you like some tea?
The tea is swell.
Do you think they can hea...?
I think that...
Oh, come on.
You know it's just as loud as...
Everybody, shut up!
Guys, I think this is the lost section
of Greendale.
Nobody's been in here since the '70s.
- How do you know?
- The debate team topic is:
"Who's hotter,
Elliott Gould or Donald Sutherland?"
- Donald Sutherland.
- Scary.
- Oh, relax.
If it's like a regular dungeon,
it's only as dangerous...
...as whoever invited you.
Abed, if there's killer robots down here,
you'll tell them we're on your side.
Won't know them from ordinary robots
until they kill us.
Well, what do we do now?
Split up.
Leave no '70s reference unturned.
This decade's out of my wheelhouse.
Pet Rock, leave no Pet Rock unturned.
Let me lead. My light's better.
You're that insecure
that your light has to be better?
- Shut up.
- You shut up.
Anything in there?
It's just spider webs
and beanbag chairs.
Don't cry. The importance
of lumbar support hadn't...
It's not that. It's just...
Even if we do save Greendale,
which Greendale will we be saving?
I mean, first Pierce dies,
then Troy leaves.
- Now people are...
- Getting married?
Annie, look, I don't know people.
But I know TV. When characters
feel the show they're on is ending...
...their instinct is to spin off
into something safer.
In Jeff and Britta's case...
...something that'd
last six episodes, have bickering...
...starring them
and an equally WASP-y couple...
...with a title like "Better With
My Worse Half" or "Tying the Not."
"Knot" is spelled without a K.
Or #CouplePeopleProblems.
- Every episode, you decide who has...
- Stop developing.
Sorry.
The point is, this show, Annie,
it isn't just their show.
This is our show, and it's not over.
And the sooner we find that treasure...
...the faster the Jeff-Britta pilot
falls apart.
Got it.
Thank you, Abed.
You're welcome.
- I have a girlfriend.
- What?
- You were about to start a kiss lean.
- I was not.
Fine. Let's find treasure.
- Did you find anything?
- No.
We've searched every crevice
of this place...
...and the only treasures we've found
are this CB radio...
...these basketball cards
with white people on them...
...and this little rocket launcher
from some action figure.
It seems like an odd place
for a dead end though.
It could be a secret door.
Maybe the jukebox is the key to it.
Just remember, it's okay if we fail.
- Right, Jeff?
- That's right.
Try every button.
Just try every single button ever.
- Are you all right?
- No! I was dying!
Try track 127.
Right. Because 127 in binary code
would be a palindrome.
Because the song title
is "Open the Door" by the Secret Doors.
Borchert's secret lab.
That's the machine Borchert
was working on in the film.
Borchert's gold.
We need to get this upstairs.
Save Greendale.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
You're Russell Borchert, aren't you?
Okay, I'm gonna peel off
some Band-Aids here.
Dennis Hopper is dead.
TV shows give no time
for theme songs anymore.
And Woody Allen did the voice
of a cartoon ant.
Jeff!
Sorry, I lose track
of how big I'm getting.
I don't.
You vandalize private property,
you nearly destroy the school...
...when it's finally about to make
a profit?
You guys are the worst...
...with your stupid paintballs
and your freeze tags.
- Hot Lava.
- That was Hot Lava? Dumb.
Tell us where the others went.
Guys, guys.
What do you wanna do?
What should we do?
Well, what can we do?
Okay.
I'm gonna need you guys
to stay back...
...and never tell anyone
about what you saw here today.
You're special, Richie.
Your mind is special.
You know it works differently
from other kids' minds.
Richie's a freak, Richie's a freak.
Thank you.
I know where they went.
They climbed out to the roof,
hopped on a hang glider...
...and flew it across town
to that Greek restaurant. Papa Cristo's?
I robbed your brain.
I robbed it.
Hey, we found a hatch in the floor
underneath the vending machine.
- I think they went down inside it.
- Was there a hang glider?
You're gonna find
a hang glider down there.
That much I know.
So anyway, I sealed myself up
down here with 50 years of food...
...50 years of toilet paper,
and 50 years of cocaine...
...which I somehow ran out of
after about 10 years.
The '80s happened down here too.
Yeah. Hey.
What are you doing with Raquel?
Raquel.
We're on a deadline,
and to put it bluntly, we need your gold.
Raquel!
- Guys, a little help. Scary fingernails?
- I'm almost done. She needs more time.
Sir, Raquel has taken the best years of
your life...
...and a dozen of your not-so-good.
If she hasn't given anything back,
it might be time to move on.
Stop! You guys...
...what are we doing?
- Saving Greendale.
- From what?
We were driven down here by sellouts
with crappy values.
Since when do human beings decide
which dreams are worthwhile?
Look at him.
He's one of us.
We have to respect each other
enough...
...to let each other want
what we want...
...no matter how transparently
self-destructive...
...or empty our desires may be.
If it was money that you guys wanted,
why didn't you say so?
You can just have my leftover cash
that's under the desk over there.
I don't think it's worth much.
Those are Gerald Ford dollars.
- How many?
- Couple of million.
Back in the '70s,
that was worth millions.
Hey, I've got an idea.
How about you people leave me alone
and I hereby grant that to Greendale?
- What?
- Oh, my God!
- Glad to hear it.
- What?
Get back. This pickle's a magnet.
- I'll wipe her out, man.
- Don't you dare use that on her!
- See what magnets do to computers?
- No, don't do it!
Get over there with them.
You have no legal claim to that money.
Take it up with Subway in about an hour,
after close of escrow.
Chang,
you've become a bad guy again?
There's a lot more to it than that, Britta.
Wait, I'm not wearing a mask?
There's no more to it.
I think I'm just mentally ill.
All right, just stay back. All right?
No, don't.
No!
Oh, God, no.
- Hey, stop!
- Hang in there.
- Open it!
- Raquel is the main operating system.
She controls the door, the lights,
the shower probably, everything.
And now she's dead.
So we're trapped in here forever.
Or just until we run out of food
and water.
- At least we'll have each other.
- Till death do us part.
You know what?
You guys can have my food and water.
Come on, Raquel.
Come on.
Baby. Come on.
Oh, thank God. Her emotional
components are still online.
Emotional components?
I have accomplished things down here
you couldn't even possibly imagine.
Here, let me show you.
Right there. That was it, that was it.
Did you see it?
Don't you see?
This computer responds to feelings.
When I started Greendale...
...it was for ordinary people
to be able to access technology.
Wait, you started Greendale?
Do you have that in writing, anywhere?
I don't know.
Somewhere with all that crap over there.
But without an emotional component...
...computers would strip us
of all humanity...
...and create a society
with emotionless eggheads at the top...
...and idiots with feelings at the bottom.
And I refuse to let that happen,
and that's why I've spent... What?
- What is that?
- It's a video of a kitten.
And why are those people
arguing about it?
And what's that?
An emoticon. That person wants
to indicate happiness...
...but can't convey it with language, so
they misuse punctuation to form a smile.
That is so...
Stupid.
Only an idiot would think of this.
Idiots won!
Which means my work down here
is done.
Good. According to what I'm seeing...
...if we can get you up there right now,
Subway won't be buying this school.
What?
Yeah, but it's gonna take a few hours
to get that door open...
...because Raquel's
logic circuits... not good.
Her emotional components work.
Well, in theory...
...a blast of human passion could shock
the mainframe into a cold start...
...but that's only
if somebody in this room...
...has feelings stronger than I get
when I rub my nipples...
- ...so good luck with that, folks.
- Give me that.
Everybody over there. Turn around.
Turn around now.
You're here to save me, aren't you?
Let's get out of here
and never look back.
In case you have to remember me,
can I give you quotes?
Shut up, Abed.
- Milady.
- Milord.
- What did you do?
- Don't worry about it. Let's go.
The city of Greendale is proud
to be selling the school of Greendale...
...to Subway.
This brings to an end
several years of horrible management...
...by Dean Craig Isidore Pelton...
...not to throw anyone under the bus.
- No.
- But he'd be the one.
By my watch, it is about time to sign
these documents and make it official.
Objection.
I teach law at Greendale,
so believe me...
...I don't know much about law...
...but I do know a contract violation
when I see one.
This is a legitimate transaction...
...where a city is selling a school
to a restaurant.
It happens somewhere every day.
Oh, the city can sell the school
all it wants...
...but according to his contract
with the city...
...the school's original founder
retains the privilege of consultation...
...on all future scholastic endeavours
taking place here.
So Subway Sandwich University...
...meet your new vice dean,
Russell Borchert.
Hi.
I guess we're gonna be partners.
I understand there's some Internet...
...where I can make
my inner thoughts public.
Greendale the city
and Greendale the school...
...have some stuff to sort out,
and Subway doesn't do conflict.
We do good food at good prices.
We are but simple sandwich artists...
- ...who want the world to eat fresh.
- Eat fresh!
Subway, ho!
Did we just save Greendale?
No! No, you did not.
You moved dirt
around Greendale's grave.
Your school is still bankrupt...
...it is still unmarketable, and it is
still on the permanent chopping block...
...of anyone who has any say
in its future.
Yeah? Well, around here,
we call that Wednesday.
Hey, after I was electrocuted, didn't you
two say you were gonna get married?
Doesn't electrocuted
technically mean killed?
- You always have to correct people?
- You always have to police correcting?
- Marriage is off.
- I think you mean the wedding is off.
- Yeah!
- Hey, hey.
Hey, I gotta say, you held up well
under that interrogation.
I'm gonna tell you something that
I'd like to stay between us, huh?
I was thinking about a hang glider.
None of this conflict truly matters.
The only owners of this land
are the Arapaho.
Would it offend you if I asked you
to train me in the use of certain powers?
Sorry, Carl.
You deserve better.
Chang, you get it.
How would you like a job
on the school board?
- Okay.
- Your first job...
...is to deliver this...
- ...to the City Bursar's Office.
- On it.
Hi, yes, I'd like to replace all my teeth
with diamonds.
We live to fight another day.
I never got a chance
to wish you a happy birthday.
Or Halloween or Christmas...
...or any specific calendar event.
- Well, maybe next year.
- Definitely.
We'll definitely be back next year.
If not, it'll be because an asteroid
has destroyed all human civilisation...
...and that's canon.
What? What are you...?
Nothing.
Am I thinking what you're thinking?
Penny for your thoughts.
Intensive Karen.
Mr. Egypt.
Celebrity Beat-Off.
Captain Cook.
Depends on what fails.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org