Don't forget, Greendale.
It's the last day to sign up
for a spring semester elective!
Horseback riding!
Water skiing!
Fencing!
Those are just a few classes
we can afford to offer
if enough people
pay to learn hopscotch.
Oh, they've got a class
on how to write jokes.
Oh, don't take that.
I dropped it
after the lesson on setups.
The Professor is so old...
So many classes.
I don't know what to choose.
I'll give you the same advice
my father gave me
the night I lost my virginity.
"Just pick one.
They all cost the same."
You could always take
"The Actor Inside"
with me and Troy.
How'd you get dragged
into that one?
Our dance teacher encourages
us to take acting classes
to tap into
our emotional cores,
so Troy and I both decided
to take it together.
Hmm. Foosball was full?
I'm on the wait list.
Don't give up.
I was on the wait list
for this media class
for a year and a half
and I finally got in.
"Who Indeed:
A Critical Analysis
of Television's
Who's the Boss?"
The professor of this class
is the author of this book.
- We got him?
- I know.
So what are you taking, Jeff?
Well, while you knuckleheads
are expanding
your minds and souls,
I'll be expanding my liver
in "Italian Wine Tasting."
Oh! Molto bene!
I'm taking that one, too.
Hmm. How do you say
"ha ha" in Italian?
I'll look it up.
Come on, Jeff, it'll be fun.
I can give you pointers.
I was drinking
their finest wines.
I assume you have
your own wine cellar.
Pierce does.
And it's, "ha ha!"
Anyone can have a cellar.
It's what's in it that counts.
Pierce's has a special gym
with swings and saddles.
Uh, we don't... we don't
discuss the special gym.
Attention, please.
All elective forms must be in
by the end of the day.
Oh, nice job, Manuel.
And good news.
There's still plenty of room
in my P.A. Announcements class.
Just ten bucks an hour.
Community 2x20 - Competitive Wine Tasting
Sync and corrected by vNaru
www.addic7ed.com
You're taking this, too?
Hell, yeah.
Got drunk ladies,
fancy bathrooms,
and a room full of free coats.
Sorry I'm late, man.
I brought you a present.
Oh.
From before
your chin dimple filled in.
Uh, excuse me.
- So sorry.
- Hmm!
Wow.
Who is the dumpling
with the nice Asian pair?
That's the first time
sexism has made me hungry,
but she is something.
I fear I may have
to let her see me nude.
I might have to take
a shot myself.
What's so funny?
Well, why would a woman
want a Plymouth on cinder blocks,
when she could have
a Testarossa, 500 horsepower
with a six-speed stick?
'Cause my stick is ribbed
for her pleasure.
I think those are wrinkles.
Let that breathe.
Lingering scent, full body,
perfect nose.
Very nice wine.
I was talking about you.
Jeff Winger.
Wu Mei Hong Long.
Oh, what a lovely name
for a lovely...
Uh, not interested.
Please take weird haircut,
stupid grin,
and go sniff another dog's ass.
Hmm, the red dragon
ordered a number 37
with a side
of pork-fried snap.
When you get up close,
she's very homely.
This is gonna be fun.
I can't wait
till we choose stage names.
Which do you think is better?
Trevor St. McGoodbody
or David?
I don't think you have
to worry about stuff like that.
This class is
more about introspection.
Drag.
Less of a drag.
Quiet!
Form a trust circle around me
and sit on the floor.
A trust circle?
It's just a circle.
It's a circle.
Sit down.
Acting is revealing,
expression.
When we release pain,
we become visible
to each other.
That is an actor's job.
That and, you know,
pretending to be other people.
Let's start with you.
Access and share with us
a profoundly deep
and painful memory.
I'm on the playground.
Stop taunting me!
I just want to go
on the swings!
Good.
Early childhood
is a treasure trove of pain.
That happened this morning.
You're up.
Me? Um...
I don't...
I don't think, uh...
I don't want you to think.
Feel!
Go back.
Dig in. Emotilize.
Something hurt you.
Um...
I was captain
of my high school football team.
It was very hard being popular.
What a loser.
Okay, great.
Next person.
I've always felt
somehow ignored,
almost invisible.
Like every time I go to say
something, somebody just...
My uncle put his finger
in my no-no!
This... this
is where acting begins.
Welcome to "A Critical
Analysis of Who's the Boss?"
I am Professor Peter Sheffield,
and I'd like to begin
with a simple question...
Who was the boss?
Yes.
Angela.
Oh, well!
Class dismissed!
No, calm down.
Calm down.
I'm sorry, um...
- Mister...?
- Abed.
The answer is not
quite that simple, Mr. Abed.
Few are.
Now, if everyone
could please turn to page 12
in my book...
Loser!
You really have to finish
that whole book by tomorrow?
Yeah, but it's a page-turner.
I'm on the chapter where he
traces Tony Micelli's genealogy
all the way back to Caesar.
Well, it's gotta be better
than wine tasting with Pierce.
He refused to drink Pinot Noir
because he thought it was French
for "black penis."
And he's late. Again.
It's not your fault.
Thank you
Oh, I'm sure he'll be here.
He wouldn't miss a chance to pop
in and say something offensive.
One day soon, that man's gonna
run out of ways
to shock people.
Everybody,
this is Wu Mei,
and we're getting married!
But it's not gonna be today.
So, uh, you're getting married
to that beautiful young thing?
Well, uh, stranger things
have happened.
No.
No, they haven't.
You said you guys just met?
Yesterday,
after wine tasting class.
I mentioned
that her breasts were larger
than most Asian women,
and, uh,
we just got to talking.
Turns out Pierce has been
to China many times.
It's the only place
to get fireworks
that are too dangerous
for Mexico.
No. I go
to visit my factory.
Hawthorne Wipes are the number
one moist towelette in Asia.
Anyway, after a few minutes,
we both just knew
we were meant to be
together forever.
Or at least
until she gets heavy.
And, uh, now we must leave you.
Many plans to make.
Yes, yes, big plans.
Well, what are we gonna do?
Plan an engagement party?
Are you out of your mind?!
This is a scam.
She's after him for his money
or a green card or something!
They seem
to really like each other.
Yeah, and Pierce married
three of his wives
after knowing them
less than a month.
Maybe he's just a romantic.
Not that you
would understand romance.
Don't preach to me
about romance, Annie.
I had a three-way
in a hot air balloon.
Fine, I guess I'll do it myself.
- Want to go?
- Mm-hmm.
Boy, he seems really worked up.
Hey, don't take on his pain.
Tend your own garden.
I'll see you in class.
What's going on?
Oh, um, I didn't have
a painful experience
to share in acting class,
so I made up this story
about my uncle trying
to touch my butt.
Britta's attracted
to men in pain.
It helps her pretend
to be mentally healthy.
- Really?
- Yeah.
I hadn't noticed.
Troy? Nothing good
can come of this.
Yeah.
I'll have to think really hard
about how to defuse
the situation.
No, uncle Lucius!
I don't want to play
in the laundry room!
My emotions!
Actors dismissed.
Uh, for homework,
drink a glass of cognac
in a bathtub.
Troy, I feel like I'm seeing
a whole different side of you.
There's just so much darkness.
And my soul is darkening,
and my heart is mad
at my kidneys, and...
My mouth...
See you tomorrow?
Uh, hello.
Oh, hi.
I'm glad you could come.
Please sit.
I felt like we got off
on the wrong foot yesterday,
and I wanted to offer you
my, uh, other foot.
First, let me just say how happy
I am for you both.
Your parents
must be so excited.
Are they coming to the wedding?
Oh, they would not miss it.
My mother will make
the customary shark's fin soup,
and my father will get drunk
and make bad impression
of Borat.
Oh, so your parents don't mind
having a son-in-law
roughly their age?
No. Pierce
is a beautiful, wise man,
very gentle soul.
Uh, let me tell you
that I am a lawyer,
so if you need any help at all
navigating the whole green card
immigration hassle.
I am dual citizen already.
Oh. Well, if you'd like me to
look at the prenup...
I assume you have one.
Yes, but my father's lawyers
will take care of this.
After all, we must protect
our family fortune.
Hmm.
Now I'm stumped.
Excuse me?
Uh, it was...
That means it was very nice
talking to you.
Oh, okay, if you say so.
- Okay. Right.
- Okay, good-bye.
Why were you grilling her?
Listen, I'm gonna bust
into her apartment.
Do you have
any grappling hooks.
Maybe Pierce finally found
his soul mate.
How can you say those things
without any trace of irony?
That's why they call me
irony-free Annie.
Mm, trust me,
that's not what they call you.
Yes?
Oh. Mr. Abed.
What can I do for you?
I finished your book,
Professor,
and I've been watching episodes
of Who's the Boss?
And I think there's something
that you might have overlooked.
Mr. Abed,
will you look at my wall?
- Mm-hmm.
- What do you see?
- Photographs.
- Of what?
- You.
- With whom?
Tony Danza, Judith Light,
Alyssa Milano,
Who's the Boss?
Season three caterer,
Gordon "Giddy-up" Galligan.
I have studied this show,
mister Abed.
I am not a fan,
I am not a groupie,
I am an academic.
When I ask the question,
"Who's the boss?"
It is a rhetorical question.
When I ask the question beyond
the question, "What is a boss?"
I really think it's Angela,
because if it's a boss...
Ok, listen, enough!
I would like you to leave
my room.
My mind is open, Professor.
It's as open as the door
to Mona's bedroom.
- It's a shame yours isn't.
- I beg your pardon?
You know?
I just got a wonderful idea.
Why don't you teach
the next class?
That way you can share your
open mind with everybody.
Cool.
Cool cool cool.
Pchew.
I couldn't be more touched
that you all threw us
an engagement party.
You said if we didn't,
you'd slash our tires.
She is funny.
Like Oprah.
Oprah's not a comedienne.
No, you are funny,
and you are like Oprah.
Yeah.
What?
Thank you.
Pierce, I'd like to offer
my sincere congratulations.
It's hard enough to find people
you can stand in this life,
let alone someone
who's willing to stomach
your imminent dementia
and present incontinence.
Thank you, Jeff.
I just hope she can satisfy me.
I'm like an insatiable baboon
in the bedroom.
Don't sell yourself short.
You're a baboon everywhere.
Seems like just yesterday
me and Abed
dined and ditched here.
Here, hold this.
Ugh, what is this?
I always carry some spare apps
in case the wait staff's racist.
Where's a napkin?
Uh, here you go.
Oh, thanks.
Check that out.
Hats off to Pierce
and the hot red dragon.
Why do you keep
calling her that?
"Hong Long" means red dragon.
That's her middle name.
In China, they
put the last name first.
I mean,
they're nuts over there.
Hm-hmm.
Thank you all for coming.
I know it seems fast,
but when you find the right
person, you just know it.
I know that because I've found
the right person seven times.
So the drinks are on me,
but stick to the crappy stuff.
I don't want to get corn-holed
on the bar tab.
Pierce, you can't just throw
around a term like that.
Corn-hole.
Corn-hole, corn-hole!
Pierce!
Troy was molested!
Cool.
Troy, we didn't know.
Troy, do you need me
to recommend a support group?
Hey, he's not a victim.
You're a survivor.
Yeah, about that...
I wasn't so much "molested"
as much as I "made it up."
What?
We're gonna laugh so hard
about this later.
I'd like to propose a toast.
Wu Mei Hong Long, better known
as Mei Hong Long Wu,
is not only
not a Greendale student,
she works for Red Dragon Wipes,
the number two wipe in Asia,
currently attempting
a takeover of Hawthorne Wipes.
So please, raise your glasses
to saving Pierce from
the clutches of a corporate spy,
and to me for being
attractive enough
to get a girl like her
under normal circumstances.
Very impressive, Veronica Mars.
You learned how to use Google.
And you learned to fight
your physical desire for me.
Oh, stick it.
You suck.
Wait, wait, wait.
Record scratch app.
Where'd everybody go?
Most people went home.
The rest went with Chang
to your place
to have a ketchup fight.
Oh, jeez, I better
get back there
before he starts
playing monkey drop.
Don't ask.
Oh, uh, do you want to come?
Why would I want to go
anywhere with Judas Winger?
You're mad at me?
You should be thanking me.
For what?
Ruining my relationship?
What relationship?
You just met the woman,
and the entire thing was a lie.
She was just using you to get
your company in China.
And I was just using her to
get her company in the sack.
People use each other Jeff.
It doesn't mean that
there aren't good feelings
that go along with it.
I liked her.
She was busty.
I thought we had something.
I was trying to help you.
I think what
you were trying to do,
is prove that no woman
could want me.
Oh, you're here.
Look, Britta, I'm really sorry.
Troy, kissing you
was a mistake.
It will never happen again.
Good.
Before my ex-boyfriend Pablo
was arrested
for forging church relics,
he accused me
of only being attracted
to a certain kind of guy.
It was hard
to understand him, though.
He was pretty huffed up
on paint thinners.
Well, maybe someday, you'll
fall for someone who's healthy.
Someone who,
other than his irrational fear
of automatic toilets,
is... normal.
Who would like to begin today?
I would.
With a confession.
My uncle never stuck
his finger in my plop-plop.
I know.
I'm bummed about it, too.
I'm sorry.
I... want to be interesting.
I want to fit in with you guys.
I want to be able
to be an actor.
The pain
of not having enough pain
is still pain, young man.
That may seem
like an easy resolution, but...
We're not writers.
We're actors.
Story doesn't matter here.
All that matters is our time
in the spotlight.
And so,
by all known definitions
of the word "boss," I.E.,
one with authority over another,
in 9 of 11 known
possible fields
in which one might teach,
employ, guide,
oversee, and/or
otherwise hold dominion,
the empirically provable answer
to the question "who's the boss?" is...
Angela Bauer.
Class dismissed.
Class dismissed!
There's a path you take
and a path untaken.
The choice is up to you,
my friend.
I wonder why Jeff and Abed
didn't show?
Well, I don't know about Abed,
but I'm sure Jeff just
found another life to destroy.
Are you still thinking
about studying acting?
I'm auditioning
for Professor Garrity's
all-black production
of Fiddler on the Roof.
It's called Fiddla Please.
What's she doing here?
I asked her to come.
I was thinking, maybe you two
were meant to be together.
You're both rude, you're
both deceitful and racist,
and you both come
from moist wipe dynasties.
I think having
that much in common
justifies at least one real date.
I guess we could
go out to one dinner.
- You're paying.
- You're dressing slutty.
Fine.
How about Mexican?
How about Thai?
They're like Chinese Mexicans.
- Hmm, so true.
- Mmm.
♪ It's hard to be Jewish,
it's hard to be Jewish ♪
♪ it's hard to be
Jewish in Russia, yo ♪
♪ it's hard to be Jewish,
it's hard to be Jewish ♪
♪ hard to be Jewish in Russia, yo ♪
♪ bagels and lox,
diamond shops ♪
♪ it's hard to be Jewish in Russia, yo ♪
♪ hard to be Jewish,
hard to be Jewish ♪
♪ hard to be Jewish in Russia, yo ♪
Someone drop
an old testament beat.
Dreidels.