Damn it!
Put the teethy wrench on the
square thing and jiggle it left.
Thanks... by the way, that
square thing is a Hampton bolt
and what you just described
is a manacheck maneuver.
Hey, I'm just here
for the tater tots.
Look, I know you think you
made your mind up about plumbing
and I respect that.
But come to the third floor
men's room tomorrow
any time after 3:00.
Unclog one toilet with me
and tell me
you don't feel something.
And I'll never
bring it up again.
All right...One toilet.
If it will get you off my back.
Abed, look.
Cool, Stonehenge.
Excuse me, are you Pierce
Hawthorne of Hawthorne Wipes?
At your cervix.
Oh, sorry, I thought
you were a lady.
You can use that
cervix line if you want.
I told you it was him.
Would you mind signing this?
He's a big fan.
♪ I got a pocket
full of hawthornes ♪
♪ pock-pocket full
of hawthornes ♪
Okay, Randall, power down.
What was that about?
Fans of the product, I suppose.
In the wipes business
we call them towel-heads.
I'm just impressed you got
through a whole conversation
with two gay men
without doing this.
Wait...Those guys were--
Mm-hmm.
I assumed they were just
brothers or wealthy.
Why do you think they
wanted your autograph?
This might be why.
♪ It's Friday night ♪
♪ I'm putting on
my highest heels ♪
♪ my shortest skirt ♪
♪ my best device for
concealing my penis ♪
♪ and I got everything I need ♪
♪ ow! ♪
♪ I got my body, got my lips ♪
♪ got a pocket
full of hawthornes ♪
♪ p-p-p-pocket full
of hawthornes ♪
Oh, my God, Pierce,
your moist towelettes
are a gay icon.
What do Hawthorne wipes have
to do with the choice to be gay?
Well, according to Wikipedia--
Oh, my...Even Bruce Vilanch?
Especially Bruce Vilanch.
That is copyright infringement
and defamation.
I'm going to sue
the pants off that lady.
- I don't think that's a lady.
- And why do you
want his pants off?
Shut up!
I only wanted his pants off
when I thought he was a lady.
So you were attracted to him?
The only thing I'm attracted to
is taking him to court
and eating his ass alive.
- Ooh!
- That's not what I meant.
Stop putting gay things
in my mouth.
♪ I got a pocket
full of hawthornes ♪
- ♪ Pocket full of hawthornes ♪
- It's catchy!
Sync by mczolly
Corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
I hope Pierce doesn't really
sue that lady-man singer.
His life must be hard enough
having to sew pouches
in all his miniskirts.
Yes, I'm always
nice to the gays.
They may live
in defiance of God,
but I'd die before
I let a woman touch my hair.
Gay-oh!
Hey, what's
going on with you bitches?
Bitches is gay talk for friends.
Did you sue Urbana
Champaign for his t-shirt?
Not at all, I bought this.
I'm a fan.
Also,
I'm a gay rights advocate.
I think I can explain.
Pierce's positrons have been
negatized, creating anti-Pierce.
It happens all the time
inspector spacetime.
Yeah, but anti-inspector
had a funny mustache
and was kinda rapey.
I don't think his positrons
have been negatized.
That's exactly what
Constable Reggie said.
No, I thought about it,
and I decided a man
should not be judged by what he
does with a fellow man's butt.
- Here's the kick.
- Plus since that song came out,
Hawthorne Wipes sales
went up 7%.
- And it's good.
- Yep, even had my own people
mock up a design
for a new product line.
Hawthorne Pride Wipes.
They may cost more,
but they're gayer.
And I'm gonna launch
these little babies
at a big party
here at Greendale.
Here's a flyer.
Ooh!
Greendale's first annual...
gay bash.
Wow, Pierce,
congratulations on meeting
the minimum requirements
for open-mindedness.
Yeah, I'm really proud of you.
You're growing as a person.
Oh, good grief,
he's not supporting gay people.
They're supporting him.
If Mexicans were
buying his wipes,
he would have
ridden in on a donkey.
People earning respect with
money is the American way, Jeff.
Not that my father
would have agreed.
It took a federal
injunction to get him
to sell these things
to the Italians.
Oh, I see what's going on here!
In my psych class
I'm learning about
this thing called
the edible complex.
All men have to
kill their fathers
so they can do something
to their mothers.
I haven't finished the chapter.
What's that complex called
where you're wrong
about everything?
Huh, sarcasm from the man with
the mother of all daddy issues.
Whoa, double diagnosis.
Save some for all those
poor real doctors.
Pierce, what type of cookies
do you want at the party?
We have peanut butter
or chocolate chip.
Rainbow, bitches.
We can have peanut butter
or chocolate chip.
Well?
It's pretty great!
Tight seal, good flow.
Kid's pretty handy.
You get the hell out of here!
Go on!
- Who was that?
- You listen to me.
What you have is a gift.
And some people are going to try
to take advantage of that gift.
Promise me
you'll use it for good.
All right, I promise.
Good. Now, come with me
to the second floor.
Somebody pooped in the sink.
You know, we actually
have a lot in common.
We hate lesbians,
we hate baggy pants,
and I can't believe you guys
are all bears fans.
- Super fans.
- Randall!
Somebody take a picture.
Come on...
Okay, now let's
take a silly one.
- Okay, okay!
- All right.
Piercinald Anastasia Hawthorne!
Father.
We need to talk, boy.
Oh--
Gentlemen.
You are here tonight because
you have been selected
as potential candidates
for the Greendale
Air Conditioning Repair School.
But why kidnap you?
Why put a sack over your head
and drag you here in
the middle of the night?
Why is there an astronaut in
the corner making paninis?
Simple, we don't want you
to tell anyone about this.
And if you do, we don't
want them believing you.
Isn't that right, Black Hitler?
Your initiation...
begins...
now, gentlemen.
Hey, guys,
I'm looking for Troy.
Oh, he texted me.
He said he's fine,
but he couldn't say where he is.
Oh, no, do you think
he's been kidnapped?
Usually it's one of the parents,
and it almost always
ends in murder-suicide.
- Why are you smiling?
- I'm smiling?
Well if you see him, tell him
Jerry's looking for him.
So Jeff, what are you going
to wear to Pierce's gay party?
- Nothing.
- Ooh, they'll love that.
Ha ha.
I mean I'm not going.
It's dumb and I can't believe
you guys are supporting it.
Everybody, this is my father,
Cornelius Hawthorne.
Oh, I always assumed
your father was dead.
Just mathematically.
Well, mom liked to pretend
that was the case.
These are your friends, Pierce?
Hello.
Minorities, jewesses,
and the unseasonably tan?
That is inappropriate!
And maybe you'll give that more
weight since I'm "white".
You've got a wide brow.
What are you, Scandinavian?
Yeah, Swedish.
Swedish dogs.
Your blood is tainted
by generations
of race mixing with laplanders.
You're basically Finns!
Oh, my goodness, he's like
the Abed of racism.
Okay, since no one's
willing to ask,
what's going on with your hair?
Ordinary toupee hair
is harvested
from the heads of
the godless oriental.
Solid ivory is the only way
to be assured of
true follicular purity,
while still identifying
myself as a man of means.
I can excuse racism, but I
draw the line at animal cruelty.
You can excuse racism?
So what brings you here?
I'm assuming it's not
for your son's party.
Unless "segregationist mummy"
is a gay fetish I'm unaware of.
Actually, uh, after
discussing with my father,
the party's off,
and we're canceling
pride wipes.
Stand up straight, Piercinald,
when talking
to the lower classes.
Now if you'll excuse me,
I need to go find
a half-decent ivory buffer
in this two-horse town.
Oh, the party's cancelled?
I bought a cone bra.
Piercinald, please tell me
you did not
cancel your gay party
because of your father.
It's a business decision, Jeff.
I took a look at the numbers,
had someone explain them to me,
and this is the way we're going.
I thought you said
Pierce's idea was dumb?
Well that's before it was
being oppressed by a--
- A father?
- A homophobe!
This isn't about fathers.
This is about
a long-suffering community
with a constitutional right
to wipe whoever
and whatever they want.
Well, if you like gay people
so much,
why don't you marry them?!
This is so edible.
Britta, you are gonna
make a terrible therapist.
And if you need to talk
to someone about that,
I don't recommend you.
Hmm, is that how your
dad talked to your mom?
No, that's how
he talked to your mom.
How does that make you feel?
Shut up.
Ah, Jeffrey!
Ah, I was so sad
when Pierce said
he was canceling the party.
And I was so happy when you
said that it was back on.
Yeah, he's real busy
with his dad,
but I knew how much
it meant to him.
I throw a pretty gay party,
huh?
Yeah, it's great.
I mean, if you're
into that kind of thing.
Time to mingle.
What the hell is this?
The gay bash,
courtesy of Hawthorne Wipes.
I cancelled this!
And I uncancelled it.
My dad's gonna disown me!
Oh, no, then you'll be
free of him forever.
You'll never have to cower at
the sound of his voice
or shudder when
you see an elephant.
You're welcome, Pierce.
I just did what you
never had the guts to do.
You know what?
Britta was right.
You resent my father because
you've got problems
with your own.
After "Britta was right",
everything you said
just sounded like a fog horn.
Then have your big gay party.
I'm out of here!
Oh, come on, Pierce,
just have one drink.
You're gonna want to
see the guest of honor.
Pull the cord, fellas.
Pierce, Pierce, Pierce!
Well, maybe just one drink.
Done.
Mr. Barnes...
Walk with me.
Mr. Barnes,
air conditioning repair is
an elite worldwide
family dating back
to the very beginnings
of civilizations.
Our predecessors were slaves,
fanning the pharaohs
with palm fronds.
Over time, we became expert
at making our
superiors comfortable.
We made it our business.
And along the way, we learned
to make ourselves comfortable.
No more palm fronds, Troy.
Now we are the pharaohs.
Breath print approved.
Feel that?
Actually, I don't feel--
Precisely.
Have you heard the expression
room temperature?
Of course.
This is the room!
This is the
room temperature room.
I-I can't tell where the air
ends and my skin begins.
It's incredible.
That's what we do, Troy.
Incredible, invisible,
inbelievable things.
We're an unseen,
unknown, unvincible
fraternity of craftsmen.
Graduates of this school are
guaranteed lucrative employment
for their entire lives.
And I'm inviting you to join us.
Will there always be paninis?
There is one catch, Troy.
Once you're in...
You're in.
Air conditioning repair
will be your life.
A life of secrets you'll be
unable to share with outsiders.
You will be an
air conditioning repairman
and nothing else...
Until the day you die.
I don't expect you
to make a decision now.
Take 24 hours.
Cool.
I can't feel my pants.
Go Pierce, go Pierce,
it's your birthday!
Well, congratulations,
you got Pierce
to symbolically kill his father
by dancing to club music.
You of all people
should be happy about this.
Pierce is becoming
a more tolerant person,
and it has nothing
to do with his father.
Look at me now, dad!
Yeah, look at me now, dad!
- Hey, where you been?
- I'm not allowed to say.
- Are you Superman?
- No.
Would you tell me if you were?
I'd tell everyone.
I never understood
why he cared who knew.
This is the hottest
party we've ever had.
I know, it's pretty dope.
No, I mean,
it's dangerously hot.
Our air conditioning system
wasn't built
for this gay a party.
I'll take a look.
- Tron?
- What's tron?
Ooh!
Man this party's
a real sausage fest.
I knew it!
- Knew what?
- Don't play dumb with me.
What, did they promise you
the life of your dreams?
You can have all that
as a plumber too,
but without the pretense.
Why do you hate them so much?
Because they're elitist.
They pump themselves up
to make everybody
think that they're special.
Because the truth is
they're not!
I have a gift.
I'm special.
I'm not a loser like you.
I'm gonna eat Spaceman
paninis with Black Hitler,
and there's nothing
you can do about it!
Well, you really seem to be
enjoying yourself.
I've gotta say, I don't know
why the word gay means dumb.
These guys are
all right in my book.
Pierce Hawthorne,
get your fine gay-lovin' ass
up here and say something
to your fans.
Come on!
If I tell you something, will
you promise to keep it a secret?
Secret handshake.
Secret.
Okay, I know I said
I can't talk to you
about what's going on,
but I can talk to myself.
Can you pretend to be me?
I like football,
but also I don't--
Perfect.
Okay, I can't choose between
air conditioning and plumbing.
I know, it's so hard, right?
- Let's ask Abed.
- Now you be me.
- What should I do, Abed?
- I don't know
but Harrison Ford might know.
Don't get cocky kid--
Okay, this isn't working, okay?
Abed tell me what to do.
I don't really see the dilemma.
Plumbing and air conditioning
seem more or less identical.
They're not--they couldn't
be more or less identical.
Well, what do you
feel like doing?
Honestly, I el like
watching TV with you.
But they're making me choose,
and if I choose wrong
it could screw up my whole life.
If you really have to make
a decision,
I say go with whatever
makes you the happiest.
Because, again, they're
virtually the same thing.
I think I know what I need to do.
Don't get cocky, kid.
All right, bitches!
I just want to say
this whole thing...
was a huge mistake.
Uh, Hawthorne Wipes
is officially
severing its ties
to the gay community.
- Aw!
- What?
Effective immediately,
it will return
to being a straights-only
product.
Boo!
Ahhhhhh...
Fake heart attack.
I taught him
everything he knows.
So, how long you guys
been on the force?
Pierce!
What the hell was that?
- That was--
- That was my boy.
Standing up for good old
Hawthorne values.
All due respect, sir,
I have zero respect for you.
- Typical Welsh nonsense.
- But father, I--
Pierce, you really wanna
be like this guy?
He's wearing
elephant bones on his head.
He will be what I tell him
to be because I am his father!
Listen up,
colonel crypt-keeper.
I could live a million years and
I could spend every minute of it
doing important things.
But at the end of it all,
I would have only lived
half a life
if I had not raised a son.
This was a gift
that was handed to you.
You squandered it.
And the reason you have
so much hatred in your heart
is because you're
trying to fill a hole
where your kid
was supposed to go.
And now it's too late.
Now you're just stomping around
trying to prove you exist.
Well, mission accomplished.
But here's a question
I'd like to pass on to you
from every son of every
crap dad that ever lived.
So what?
I'm done with you.
He's done with you.
The world is done with you.
Come on in.
He's a Hawthorne.
This is what they do.
He's faking.
Pierce, listen,
I just want to say--
Did you know that the Canadian
Mallard is the only water fowl
that bites his father's head off
on the way out of the womb?
- That is definitely not true.
- I don't know.
I looked it up on
the "wackapeediah"
Pierce, um, I just want
to say, you know...
Sorry for killing your dad.
Don't blame yourself.
He bought a lot of his organs
from questionable sources.
Oh, here, he wanted you
to have this.
No Pierce, you should take it.
Believe me, I'd love it.
But the terms of his will
clearly state
that whoever kills him
gets to keep it.
Huh, I guess I'm up.
"Father, I'll never forget
what you said to me
"on my first day of school.
'Comb your hair, you idiot.
You look Greek.'
"I'll never know
if that was true,
"but I do know that I was too
scared to stand up for myself.
"Well, I'm not scared of you
anymore because you're dead,
"and I'm not.
So, I win."
And you can suck it.
Dude just told
his dead dad to suck it.
So edible.
You're the worst.
Your 24 hours has expired.
I need an answer, Troy.
Are you ready to join
the elite brotherhood
of guys who
fix air conditioners?
I'm sorry, Vice Dean Laybourne,
but, I realize no one's
better than anyone else.
I mean, some people
are better at sports and...
And there are magicians, but...
I was put on this earth
to do something else.
So you're going to be what?
A plumber?
No, I'm not gonna be
a plumber either.
Because they have
to deal with poop.
My decision for now
is to watch TV with my friend.
You're making
a huge mistake, son.
That may be, sir.
But at least it's my mistake.
It doesn't change
the fact that it's a mistake.
Doesn't it?
No, it doesn't.
Sir, looks like there
was a malfunction
in the cafeteria last night.
The Amana 5000 had
a compound coil fracture.
But it was fixed.
Very funny.
Not even I can fix a compound
coil fracture overnight.
But he can.
Constable Reggie.
Inspector Spacetime.
This isn't over, Troy Barnes.
It's only just begun.
You know what, I was wrong.
I think you'll make
a very good therapist.
And why is that?
Well, you really nailed Pierce
in that whole oedipal thing.
The guy's got some
serious father issues.
Don't you think you may have
had some oedipal issues as well?
Not really seeing
the connection.
You literally killed a father.
Yeah, well, not mine, dummy.
Wow.
Hey, Winger.
You going home alone?
Gay.
That was close,
Constable Reggie.
I thought those blorgons
had us dead to rights.
What on bitter earth do they
want from us, inspector?
The question's not what they
want from us, constable.
But when!
Inspector, look out, blorgons!
Eradicate!
Eradicate...Eradicate...
Take that, blorgon scum.
How old are you guys?
The question isn't
how old we are...
But when old we are!
In your face, blorgonian!
Pew, pew, pew, pew!
'Sup, girl?
How you livin'?
Pew!
Sync by mczolly
Corrected by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org