Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
My name is Kevin.
Or so they tell me.
Actually, they told me my birth name is
Benjamin Chang...
but I can't remember anything
before six months ago.
But by using a special shiny glass
called a mirror...
I've estimated that I'm 15 years old,
although I have no way of knowing.
Changnesia is a fascinating
and extremely rare disease...
on the forefront of
the psychological landscape.
Compared with
your garden-variety amnesia...
Changnesia is immeasurably
more complex.
Its varied and seemingly
random symptoms...
its resistance to both traditional
and new age medicine.
Why Changnesia affects the memory
but not the ability to make forced puns.
These are all things we can study
now that someone has it.
I first met Chang when I hired him
as a Spanish teacher at Greendale.
Then he became a disgraced student,
a psychopathic music major...
a homeless vent dweller,
security guard, keytarist...
power-hungry warlord,
and now Kevin.
It's sad to see him like this.
Well, it's mixed.
He was pretty terrible before.
I'm developing a theory
which some find controversial.
Perhaps Chang actually
used to be Kevin...
went crazy, and became Chang.
And then at some point,
Chang hit his head, went un-crazy...
thereby reverting back
to regular old Kevin again.
That makes no sense.
Science tells us hitting his head
would only cure him...
if hitting his head
was the original cause.
I told you it was controversial.
Here at Greendale,
we accept all students...
whoever they may be
or have forgotten they were.
But assisting in Kevin's recovery has
put a financial strain on the school.
That's why we are appealing...
to the MacGuffin Neurological
Institute for this $40,000 grant...
so we can continue to fight
this terrible disease...
and hopefully, one day,
pay for this documentary.
How was that, Abed? It's too beggy?
No, that was great.
But I could use a new camera
with a smoother zoom.
Okay. Just be sure
to get my good side.
This documentary needs
to be convincing.
This needs to be the Hoop Dreams
of things people care about.
We rolling?
Dean wants propaganda but I intend to
explore all sides of this serious issue...
including those who don't think
it's a serious issue.
- Hey, Jeff.
- What are you doing?
- A documentary on Changnesia.
- You gotta be ♪♪♪♪♪♪♪ kidding me.
Got it. Beautiful.
All right, let's get one more for safety.
Jeff, back to one. Jeff?
♪ Give me some more
Time in a dream ♪
♪ Give me the hope
To run out of steam ♪
♪ Somebody said It can be here ♪
♪ We could be roped up
Tied up dead in a year ♪
♪ I can't count the reasons
I should stay ♪
♪ One by one they all
Just fade away ♪
I'm telling you, we should have sprung
for the name-brand glitter.
Look, cheap glitter, expensive glitter.
Money talks, people.
Guys, did you hear?
The History of Ice Cream class
had another heart attack.
- Three more and we're all in.
- Yes.
What's the MacGuffin Institute?
Fine. I'll tell him.
But one day, you'll all be old
and slow and lose at things...
and when that day comes,
I won't remember what I'm doing now.
The MacGuffin Institute is coming
to Greendale...
because they might give the school
money to study Changnesia.
Changnesia isn't a disease.
It's a con.
You're seriously helping this lunatic?
He kept the dean in a dungeon.
He tried to kill us.
He ate his twin in utero.
- That was Chang. This is Kevin.
- They're the same idiot.
How would you know?
Have you ever spent time with him?
I was reluctant to accept Kevin
at first too...
but he's just so sweet.
The world is brand new to him.
He approaches everything with
the wonder of a child or cartoon alien.
- This makes things smaller.
- No, bigger.
Oh, bigger.
Well, enjoy your collective delusion.
I'm gonna go get a sandwich,
which, unlike Changnesia, is real.
Jeff, wait.
We wanna know how you feel...
about the MacGuffin people
visiting.
- It's stupid.
- What?
- The whole thing.
- Put it together for me.
All right. Thanks, buddy.
I'll cut it together.
Shirley.
You don't seriously think
Chang is Kevin?
I believe the Lord made Chang,
Chang. Kevin is a choice.
I'm worried about the group.
Not only have they drunk
the Kevin Kool-Aid...
they're in the study room,
making banners, debating glitter.
I'd love to talk but I gotta get to work.
No, Shirley,
you've got to help me stop this.
You're the only sane person left.
Welcome to Shirley's Sandwiches,
where the food is Kevin-ly.
You hired Chang?
The customers love Kevin.
It's because he's a good listener.
Most words are new to him,
so it's still fascinating.
- I'm Kevin. And you are...?
- Not calling you Kevin.
Hi, Not-Calling-You-Kevin.
What are you having?
- None of this.
- Okay.
Listen. I don't care what he calls
himself, he's a hard worker.
We're all broken people, Jeffrey.
We all deserve a second chance.
Like I gave Andre a second chance.
Doesn't mean I forgot. I just forgave.
Chang didn't sleep with a stripper.
He tried to kill us.
- Why does everyone forget that?
- But he didn't.
And you used to be a sleazy lawyer.
What if Greendale never gave you
a second chance?
What Shirley said
really made me think.
I mean, all my friends believe
this guy.
What does it say about me
that I don't?
Yes?
And cue Wet Blanket Winger to tell us
that we're all wasting our time.
Actually, no.
I had a really good conversation
with Shirley...
and I realised
I've been acting like a jerk.
If it's not too late,
I'd love to help out in any way I can.
Jeffrey, that's amazing.
I knew you'd come around.
Abed, get us in panning singles.
Can you say "powwow" instead
of "conversation"? It sounds more you.
Action. You gonna make an entrance?
Great.
What does it say?
It says I have gullible friends
who will believe anybody...
and I need to make
that anybody me...
by exposing Chang
in front of the whole school.
Much like the classic documentary
Capturing the Friedmans...
my story took a completely
unexpected turn.
Jeff, if you want this done right,
I need a Steadicam for Garrett.
That's showbiz.
We were all pretty happy
when Jeff came around.
He became really gung ho
about Abed's documentary...
and had ideas about how to impress
the MacGuffin people.
And that's why Pierce should host
the reception.
He speaks their language.
Finally, somebody's making
some sense.
I've got a blackface Senor Wences bit
I've been workshopping.
Perfect. Annie, we need to find out
what happened to Kevin...
before he showed up
at Greendale.
What hellish experiences did
he overcome during those months?
You think you can use your forensic
know-how to do some investigating?
- Investigating? Obvi.
- Can I help?
If you're willing to learn,
sure, partner.
Partner. I like that.
I'm gonna call you Houlihan.
Partner and Houlihan.
Okay.
The postman found Kevin here.
He said he was soaking wet
and smelled like fish.
- I know it's not a lot to go on...
- It's almost too much to go on.
Look, Sullivan's Trout Farm
is just quarter mile away.
- Who do you think you're dealing with?
- I don't know. Seems thin.
In an investigation, one dude always
has to go opposite the other dude.
- That's how they get things done.
- You guys work it out.
- Yeah, we will.
- No, we won't.
- Britta, Shirley.
- That's me.
I want you to take this camera and
follow Chang around for his day-to-day.
Really get into the life of
a functioning Changnesiac.
I want you to go inside his home,
work, pod. Just get everything.
That's great advertising for
my growing business.
Okay, I'll do it.
And with my photography skills...
Jeff, thank you.
When the dean told me you were
gonna help me, I couldn't believe it.
A cool, smart lawyer like yourself
reaching out to a little nobody like me?
I never told you I was a lawyer.
No, you didn't.
Shirley said it, remember?
You said, "You hired Chang?"
I said, "Kevin. You are...?"
"Not calling you Kevin."
"Hi. What are you having?"
You said, "None of this."
Shirley said, "I don't care what
he calls himself. He's a hard worker."
We all deserve a second chance.
"Like I gave Andre a second chance.
Doesn't mean I forgot. I just forgave."
You said, "Chang didn't sleep
with a stripper. He tried to kill us."
Why does everyone forget that?"
And then Shirley said, "But he didn't.
And you used to be a sleazy lawyer."
Her words.
That's quite a memory you have.
My short-term memory
has actually improved.
My doctor calls it a...
side effect.
Well played, Chang.
The chess match has begun.
What...? I'm Chinese?
Do you wanna get footage
while we wait for Kevin?
Maybe we could take shots
of my delicious bread baking...
or the affordable prices
on our new...
Shirley's Sandwiches
Super Saver Menu.
Or we could get to know the Shirley
behind the sandwiches.
- Here, give me that camera.
- Okay.
- Be careful now. It's Abed's camera.
- All right.
- Watch it.
- Oh, where is the stop button on this?
Oh, here it is.
Okay. You wanna hear my pitch?
A strong, independent woman,
starting her own business.
An entrepreneu-her, if you will.
- Or maybe a businesswoman?
- Okay, fine. Think inside the box.
All right. Are you ready? Action.
Cut. Beautiful.
You think the song was too much?
Are you kidding me?
It made the scene.
I wanna get some better lighting
up in this noise.
Let's go hit up Abed.
- I never told anybody that story, Britta.
- It was beautiful.
- I was dead for three minutes.
- Three minutes?
Three whole minutes.
They thought I was gone.
- Pierce, how's your act coming?
- Blackface Senor Wences?
How do you think it's coming?
In the unlikely event
I fail to expose Chang...
I'm confident Pierce will make sure
we don't get a grant.
What you talking about, honky?
That bit could not get
any more perfect.
Wait a minute. I haven't introduced you
to my Asian wife yet.
I was wrong.
- This is the place.
- No, it's not.
- Garrett, here he comes. Get up.
- I can't.
- It's too heavy.
- Garrett, now. Now.
Excuse me, Mr. Sullivan. This is
Houlihan. I'm her partner, Partner.
- Wait, I'm Partner.
- No, you're not.
- We'd like to ask a couple questions.
- What are you, trout police?
If you are, you're legally bound
to tell me or it's entrapment.
We're not the trout police.
Have you seen this man?
One morning I see something
come out of the trout tank...
and at first I was scared...
because I'm the last face
that a lot of trout ever see.
I'm not saying
that the trout are a vengeful breed...
but if they were, I'd probably be
public enemy number one.
So the figure that emerged,
it was that man?
Yeah. I was relieved when I found out
it was a naked Asian guy...
- and not an angry trout.
- And when was this?
It must have been around June.
I remember
because my milkweed allergies...
were acting up something fierce.
I gave him some clothes...
sent him on his way the next morning.
I don't know what happened to him.
Mr. Sullivan, how many employees
do you have here?
Employees?
What do I look like, TroutWorld?
No employees. Just me and my dog.
I knew he was hiding something.
A spike in production in June at
the peak of milkweed allergy season?
Something on this trout farm
was starting to smell wrong.
The problem was,
I didn't have any way to make him talk.
Or did I?
Well, looks like everything checks
out here. Right, Troy?
No, Houlihan,
I don't think anything checks out here.
No, don't fly off the handle, Partner.
Oh, I will fly off the handle,
Houlihan.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- I'm sorry.
Clearly, you have nothing to hide.
- What are you hiding?
- Fine. You got me.
I'd been using that Asian guy
as unpaid labour...
for three months
before I drove him into town.
But he wanted me to!
We were friends and I treated him
with respect and dignity.
Partner and Houlihan.
Shut up, Kevin!
I don't understand.
Why work for no money?
He doesn't know about money,
labour laws or 40-hour work weeks...
or that dude named him
after a dog.
I had a cat named Troy,
a bird named Troy...
and a hamster named Troy.
They were all older than me.
Oh, my God.
I think Kevin's struggle
just got a lot sexier, grant-wise.
This is horrible.
It was horrible. They were supposed
to come back with a smoking gun.
All they found was a little human rights
abuse. Which, normally, is terrible.
- So do you believe Kevin now?
- No. I want all your footage.
I know Chang slipped up.
He's not smart enough
to play dumb all the time.
Shirley and Britta's footage?
- It's unusable crap.
- I don't care. I want it all.
Bad enough to rent a crane
and licence an expensive song?
Yeah. Whatever.
"Unusable crap" is generous.
It goes on for 12 hours.
I couldn't even get through it all
and I sat through The Tree of Life.
Wait, right there. What's that?
Oh, come on, you slippery snake,
slip up.
Doubtful. When alone,
he just practises smiling and frowning.
We've all done it.
- Who's he calling?
- Good question.
We figure that out,
we've got our smoking gun.
- And all thanks to Britta.
- Don't ruin this.
The stage was set for a climatic
final set piece.
The MacGuffin people were on campus.
Jeff prepared quite the presentation.
And I didn't urinate on a...
You shut up.
But I love you.
You get in the kitchen,
make me a burrito.
Oh, okay. Oh, thank you.
Okay, thank you,
Pierce Hawthorne...
for your special blend of playful
racial humour...
and genuine thoughts on
Geraldine Ferraro.
He's an old teddy bear.
And now, I believe, Jeff Winger
has a presentation.
Thank you. I must confess...
I was, just a short while ago,
quite skeptical about Changnesia.
With the help of my friends,
we have uncovered a lot about...
this terrible, newly discovered,
completely real disease.
I think you'll find it as eye-opening
as I did.
Wait till you see what we found.
Kevin was a victim
of human trafficking.
Our purpose here tonight is
to help cure Kevin of his Changnesia.
Who better to jog his memory...
than someone special
from his allegedly-erased past.
So please welcome to the stage...
the former Mrs. Ben Chang,
Alessandra.
- Alessandra, come on up.
- Thank you.
Ben, do you remember me?
I'm sorry.
I don't.
Admit it, Kevin. You remember her.
This is the woman you never
stopped loving.
Hit the lights!
You love her so much...
you called her over and over
and over again...
though you don't know her
or how to use a phone...
or what a number is.
What's going on here?
You told me I was here to help him.
Oh, we are here to help him, all right.
We are here to help him admit that
he has been faking this whole time.
- Where'd you get the number, Chang?
- I found it in the vents.
It's 555-0190.
And it was the most beautiful thing
I'd ever seen.
But I always hung up
because I didn't know...
if the person on the other end
would ever want to talk to Kevin...
after knowing Chang.
You seem so nice.
If we were really married...
I wish I could remember for even
one moment how lucky I was.
Oh, Ben.
Jeffrey, what are you doing?
If he doesn't remember her,
then this wouldn't bother him.
My logic is flawless.
Doesn't that bother you?
That bothers you.
Things got so ugly,
I hesitate to show you this footage.
I will let you see me reacting to it.
That'll probably be more
than you can handle.
Actually, it's not that bad
but this keeps the story moving.
Hey, Alessandra, his last girlfriend
was a charred mannequin leg!
- Jeffrey, have you lost your mind?
- You never believed Kevin?
You were lying to manipulate us
into helping you hurt him?
Jeffrey, I trusted you,
believed in you...
fantasised about celebrating
over mimosas with you.
If this is the sort of battle you're facing
in the fight against Changnesia...
then you're gonna need
all the help you can get.
On behalf of the MacGuffin
Neurological Institute, grant granted.
- Granted?
- That's nice.
- Partner and Houlihan.
- Jeffrey.
So I guess I did help.
Just not in the way I wanted to.
But on the bright side, this is the most
well-documented failure of my life.
- Thank you.
- I know.
By trying to make Kevin a pariah...
I accidentally became more
Chang than Chang at his Changiest.
That's funny.
Well, I didn't try to kill anyone.
Which no one seems to care about,
but you know what I'm saying.
Can I sit here?
You sure you wanna be seen
with me?
You have a brand-new reputation
to uphold.
- I like you.
- Really?
Even after everything I did to
whoever you are?
Okay, I get it.
Changnesia's hard to understand.
At least, that's what people tell me.
I don't know a thing about it, which,
apparently, is one of the symptoms...
and it's so frustrating.
Look, I know Chang was a bad guy.
So he probably deserved everything
you did to him.
But you're not a bad guy,
you just made a mistake.
And I'm willing to start over fresh
if you are.
Hi. My name's Kevin.
I'm not saying I believe him...
but I have gotten an idea
of what it feels like to be Chang.
Wanting to leave that name behind is
the sanest decision anyone can make.
Hi. I'm Jeff.
Thanks. A lot of filmmakers use
crane shots to elicit emotion.
What the heck, Abed?
You knew what Jeffrey was planning
the whole time?
Why can't you make a documentary
about the thing you plan to?
Don't censor him. Censorship.
This is the documentary.
Abed, you gotta teach me
how to use that camera.
Guys, I'm sorry.
I really screwed up.
I hope you can forgive me.
Already forgotten.
- Kevin.
- What we laughing about?
- Oh, Kevin.
- Kevin.
- Adorable.
- Good job.
I don't get it.
Hi, it's me.
They all finally bought it.
Hook, line and Winger.
I patiently await
your further instructions.
Chang out.
Why did I do that?
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org